#871: You act shamelessly!

Xu Xiaoyan sees Tang Wulin makes that movement the time is beautiful face changing colors, although she has released own Starlight Radiance Soul Skill promptly, innumerable starlight go toward Tang Wulin direction suddenly to launch, covers in which his body instantaneously, but this cannot change Tang Wulin the process that Golden Dragon Spear projects.

The Golden Dragon Tyrant Body Golden Dragon Spear release, Tang Wulin both hands are up and down, in Starlight Radiance shines on own instant, makes a very strange movement.

Both hands to turn into a claw shape of being up and down, palm relative, the left leg steps forward one step to the left front, seemed like has exhibited a close-combat appearance.

Le Zhengyu looks that Golden Dragon Spear suddenly to launch comes, immediately discoloration. His Trial of Light fell on Tang Wulin, but also was similarly slower than Golden Dragon Spear a racket.

Trial of Light by Golden Dragon Tyrant Body absorb, Tang Wulin mirror surface Battle Armor ray of light glittering, at this time, Starlight Radiance arrived at rapidly, decides him is in-situ.

The Le Zhengyu horizontal body keeps off before the Xu Xiaoyan body, in the hand Holy Sword All-Out to go to chop, tries to prevent Golden Dragon Spear. But Golden Dragon Spear has not arrived, he felt that sharp air/Qi must pierce own body, cannot block! He can definitely affirm, even if the own Battle Armor defense strength full, even if currently own had the Bloodthirsty Bean Paste Bun amplification, cannot block Tang Wulin this to strike as before.

Golden Dragon Spear terrifying in this way, who also dares saying that unexpectedly Captain does not have long-distance attack ability.

When sharp sword tip(s) finally from having a side interest in rushes, accurate incomparable from one side punctures side Golden Dragon Spear, dragon spear bursts out dragon roar, ray of light one slow, Le Zhengyu Holy Sword along with it cutting above Golden Dragon Spear.

Although Ye Xinglan has blocked Golden Dragon Spear majority of mighty energy, but when Le Zhengyu this sword cuts strikes, actually cannot help but the whole body megascism, is similar to receives an electric shock generally backs up, nearly hits on Xu Xiaoyan.

Golden Dragon Spear shoots accordingly, Holy Sword to shatter.

But another side, rushes to front of Tang Wulin only, only remaining Yuan En Yehui. Attacks the enemy to rescue, Ye Xinglan that should also clash was disturbed by Golden Dragon Spear, first has chosen eventually the life-saving.

Giant Hammer(s) flies high, the overhead pounds to fall.

It looks like in Yuan En Yehui, this time Tang Wulin by the Starlight Radiance anchorage, moreover his Golden Dragon Tyrant Body because also Trial of Light was stimulated, the words attack strength that although he counter-attacks now will be stronger, but his defense strength only has actually been able to depend upon oneself.

To rush promptly, she has not used Soul Skill, actually All-Out before Gigantic Demon Titan situation struck the Tang Wulin body.

Hit!

In Yuan En Yehui heart one happy. But also at this moment, she only thought that strength of the strange revolving transmits from Tang Wulin, her should shell to be twisted by him in Giant Hammer(s) of Tang Wulin chest place unexpectedly directly, moreover her body is also being turning round revolves. Giant Hammer(s) falls into the Tang Wulin hand at the same time, he also liberates from Starlight Radiance. In the hand Giant Hammer(s) has not gone to control near at hand Yuan En Yehui, but throws to fly once more, goal or Xu Xiaoyan.

Sharp ray of light plunders together from Tang Wulin, almost arrived in front of body out-of-control Yuan En Yehui in an instant, is not just Xie Xie.

Before had Tang Wulin to keep off before the body, even if were Starlight Radiance, had been blocked by Tang Wulin, he has not actually come under any influence. Double Dragon Daggers like lightning act that the critical moment, Storing Power waits. Moreover is an empty reality, changes into two to do several things at the same time, both sides converging attack.

On Tang Wulin hears the spirited dragon roar sound, golden-colored ring of light blooms from the under foot, Golden Dragon King fourth bloodline Soul Ring technique, Golden Dragon Frantic Domain.

Xie Xie itself has meager Dragon Clan bloodline, Golden Dragon Frantic Domain is most intense to his amplification, he only thought that whole body bloodline aura rises suddenly, two did several things at the same time to arrive in front of Yuan En Yehui directly.

„Xie Xie.” At this moment, strange appear(ance).

Yuan En Yehui has not attempted to resist unexpectedly, but is both hands puts down, the personal appearance reduces instantaneously, changes into the original appearance . Moreover, but also summoned a Xie Xie name in a seductive voice.

Her sounds/voices is very gentle, even can with speaking in a coaxing voice to describe.

If currently side Xie Xie has a magnifying glass, certainly can see, is only instant, he had goose flesh.

Two do several things at the same time to interlock, Double Dragon Daggers actually simultaneously receives. Has not fallen on Yuan En Yehui.

The Yuan En Yehui winning smile is sweet, the personal appearance turns over, the a pair of longleg simultaneously tramples, center two buttocks of Xie Xie, directly trampling to fly this fellow.

The aspect that Tang Wulin speechless, must kill, Xie Xie this fellow actually at crucial moments fell the chain.

Two pairs five, on inferiority, wanted to win, must try another method. What threatens to him is biggest is Xu Xiaoyan, therefore Tang Wulin through throwing to limit, the opportunity that then he builds, making Yuan En Yehui complete the order form, and was diverted by own. So long as Xie Xie can strike to subdue. Two pairs four may probably be easier.

But who knows, critical moment, Xie Xie actually sudden atrophy. Not was only trampled to fly, but also knocks down after does not have, was been unexpectedly same as before by Yuan En Yehui, has sealed up bloodline.

Compared with Giant Hammer(s) and beforehand Golden Dragon Spear that Tang Wulin departs, might are many on difference. Without Golden Dragon Spear speed and sharpness, was selected to fly by Ye Xinglan directly.

But a Tang Wulin fist rumbles, although the bang flew Yuan En Yehui, but under the function of Star-time Chains, Injury Sharing, cannot injure to her.

„You act shamelessly, but also has spoken language to harass.” Saying of Tang Wulin grief and indignation.

Yuan En Yehui smiles, „Captain, we graduate from Devil Island. What did you forget to learn there us?”

The voice has not fallen, Yuan En Yehui, Ye Xinglan and Le Zhengyu three people have encircled. Star Wheel Ice Chain also accurate incomparable appear(ance) in the Tang Wulin under foot.

Tang Wulin but, can only use Golden Dragon Tyrant Body once more, simultaneously shows beforehand that strange posture.

Strange saying that after this posture exhibits, whose attack he, by direct belt flew. Yuan En Yehui that strong strength is not good, other people are also same.

Even if Ye Xinglan Star Divine Sword punctures, is similar to pricks vortex to be ordinary, then the human was brought to fly.

Through this strange posture, Tang Wulin can be out of danger once again.

But, he faces is actually besieging of five people! attack of person no longer after the frontage, received Xu Xiaoyan unceasing Control in the presence of everyone, Tang Wulin on the tragedy.

But what makes his speechless is, explains his strange posture, unexpectedly is Xu Lizhi.

Xu Lizhi does not know when ran up to behind him, the a pair of fat hand is bringing purple-black ray of light, printed quietly after him has carried on the back.

When tyrannical incomparable Ruin aura makes Tang Wulin in following directly one time cannot suspend close-combat facing Star Wheel Ice Chain and Starlight Radiance. Then......

After five minutes.

Black and blue Tang Wulin, face depressed sitting in Training Field. Not far away Xie Xie does not dare to visit him.

Le Zhengyu complacent [say / way]: „Captain, you understand now, did not fear that the god same match, fears the pig same teammate. If I you, I may not endure. With his to choose!”

Formerly they ganged up on Tang Wulin time the meaning of not having shown mercy, but, the Tang Wulin defense strength also once again made them shock, under besieging of Three Great Assault System Battle Soul Master, had insisted unexpectedly also five minutes chose the surrender. He more than once seeks for opportunity attempt to break through, was actually melted by Xu Xiaoyan prompt Control.

Without doubt, if no Xu Xiaoyan Super Rank Power Control, even if three pairs one, they also not necessarily certainly can win Tang Wulin, even if wins, will certainly pay the price.

---------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#872: feel ill-at-ease

The extravasated blood on Tang Wulin face is abating fast, by his restoration ability, this small wound is nothing radically.

Xie Xie submissive [say / way]: „Boss, I made a mistake. But I really am not intentional! Yuan En has not crossed like this. I guaranteed, next time cannot like this.”

Tang Wulin stared his one eyes, „not next. Next time if she calls you a husband, you haven't given me backhandedly?”

Xie Xie surprised gaining ground, has a look at Tang Wulin, has a look at Yuan En Yehui again, as if possible, affirmation, meets appear(ance) this situation.

In front of Yuan En Yehui, he truly does not have no fighting strength.

The Tang Wulin direct foot trampled to fly this fellow. Other people actually laugh, [say / way] that a Yuan En Yehui face shuts out: „Who will call his! Wants not to think.”

Tang Wulin somewhat helpless [say / way]: „Your conditions I was roughly clear, turns head I to subscribe the plan with each of you again alone, today arrived here.”

Separates with companion, Tang Wulin returns in the own small log cabin, until this time, on his face were many desolate.

Saw that companion are forms a pair, can say in his heart not to have a point to envy that to be also possible? But, how envies can? Also can only envy. Until now, his Gu Yue and Na'er news does not have. They actually where? Actually where!

Gu Yue, will you really never see me? Is waiting for me, I certainly enough formidable looks for you.

......

A Soul Guide Large Bus rapid travel on the High-speed road, this big Bus seems very ordinary, does not have what difference with ordinary Soul Guidance large bus, what only slightly different is, large bus windows are drawing the window curtains, is unable to make one see inside situation.

, The Shrek City checkpoint must arrive by far, large bus decelerates slowly, lines up according to the order, is waiting for the inspection.

In this time, checkpoint, is walking one to wear the staff of uniform, looks at its epaulet, has certain status in the checkpoint obviously.

He goes out of the checkpoint quickly, then beckons toward that Soul Guide Large Bus, has referred to side one everywhere in off-position passageway.

Soul Guidance large bus reaction is quick, immediately transferred, reverses the direction fast, goes to that passageway.

That staff walk into passageway, turned on inside equipment, the big Bus gate opens, seemed the look ordinary middle-aged man walked from above, arrived in front of that staff, has handed over the own credential.

The staff read his credential, hands over to give back to him, then enters inside handling room, turned on the equipment of impediment, the iron bar raised slowly, the middle-aged person turned around to board, drives Soul Guidance large bus to pass fast, went to the Shrek City direction.

The iron bar puts down, that staff also naturally walked, this road will not pass through as before.

Has not aroused the interests of other vehicles like the situation, after all, where has the privileged class, even if Shrek City is no exception. Others this called special passageway, only then there is relations to use, can avoid lining up, even did not pay the fee.

But nobody notes is, that staff after completing a moment ago this series of matters, returns to the toll station staff rest area directly, has changed clothes, but also greeted with the colleagues, got up Soul Guide Steam Vehicle voluntarily, departs quietly. But direction that he departs, is not that side Shrek City, but goes toward the distant place.

Because the car(riage) on road are getting more and more, Soul Guidance large bus slowed down speed, is marching forward in the stream of vehicles slowly. In the car(riage) altogether several people, appear very silent. They is a black uniform, on the face are all bringing the headgear, only reveals the nose and eye, as a result of their dressing up, making the atmosphere in entire Soul Guide Large Bus appear somewhat gloomy.

Only then driver of that driving , before is , the middle-aged talented person who once got out appears very normal.

Sits in front black-clothed person stands up, arrives at behind fast, the sinking sound track: „Barrier Equipment situation how?”

Another black-clothed person put out an instrument to look, nodded to him, „all as usual, besides background radiation, without any revelation.”

„Is very good.” Then, he returns to front, said to the front driver: „Moved as scheduled.”

„Yes!” Driver respectful saying, in the meantime, in his eyes, is revealing the frantic color obviously. That frantic has been full of the madness flavor.

Soul Guide Large Bus goes continually, quick entered the Shrek City urban district, the distant place can see Shrek City Inner City gradually.

Big Bus has not gone to the Inner City direction again, but turned a quite broad street , after going a while, slowly the deceleration, the roadside, seemed like the construction of Hotel, large door opened slowly, big Bus free turning entered, is hidden after large door.

......

Sea God Island.

Sits cross-legged to sit on the wooden bed, Sky Raising Douluo Yun Ming opens eyes slowly, why does not know, flashes through in his eyeground deep place wipes the color of surprise.

„Ya Li.” He calls one lightly.

„How?” Holy Spirit Douluo Ya Li walked from outside, she listens obviously, Yun Ming sounds/voices some are not slightly right.

„Why does not know, I have the feeling of feel ill-at-ease.” In Yun Ming sounds/voices has several points to have doubts.

Ya Li is surprised, „what? feel ill-at-ease?” Must know that Sky Raising Douluo is Present Generation Limit Douluo, has the name of Continent first person, the great strength of its strength, excels by far Soul Master. Does his feeling know that be more formidable than many times average man, Spiritual Strength already entered Spirit Domain Realm stage, his sensation, almost it can be said that feels some meteorological Transformation on entire Douluo Continent.

Can make him have the feeling of feel ill-at-ease, certainly had any important matter to occur. Like former Heaven Dou City bitter experience attack time, he once some premonitions, even once the accurate premonition was the Heaven Dou City direction had an accident. When what a pity, he to Federation sounds the caution, Federation cannot promptly process, had the occurrence of Heaven Dou City massacre.

„Is very intense? Is where?” Ya Li pursues asks.

The Yun Ming brow is tight, then shook the head, „is very intense, but is also very strange, my feel ill-at-ease suddenly suddenly weak, is unable to take one's bearings, where cannot feel is appear(ance) the issue. This was too strange. Is the disaster?”

Ya Li is also the brow tight wrinkle, „disaster? Doesn't the direction have?”

Yun Ming shook the head, „temporarily did not have. But feeling intense time is actually unprecedented, in other words, if there is disaster to occur, that also will be the unprecedented catastrophe.”

Ya Li holds breath cold air, can make Yun Ming say that it can be imagined this will have the possibility appear(ance) disaster to be fearful. Her sinking sound track: „That what to do?”

Yun Ming said: „Only can warn to Federation, believes after previous lesson, this time they should be have reaction. Meanwhile, you issue the Shrek command, notifies Inner Court disciple that all Shrek graduate, told them my sensation, making them guard carefully, once there is not a good omen, can request reinforcements to the Academy aspect.”

„Good. Can hold the Sea God Pavilion conference?” Ya Li asked.

Yun Ming shook the head, „first does not want. After all I did not have the means to confirm, since present realm, my own strength receives Tianwei suppression unusual is intense, does not remove the sensation to meet the appear(ance) wrong possibility. But is careful a point always right.”

Because already could not feel God Realm existence, since achieves Limit Douluo realm , after is Demi-God stage, Yun Ming meets the appear(ance) absent-minded feeling frequently, as if can feel anything, as if anything is unable to feel.

More to this stage, actually more is to inquire into that God Realm where, to disappear from the scene, is how.

Therefore, his cultivate is the sun has to do, therefore, he does not remove own to be disturbed by the sun. But feeling of that feel ill-at-ease actually throughout existence.

Tang Wulin sobers from meditation, immediately thinks to be refreshing, the whole body has a carefree feeling beyond description.

Since Martial Soul two times awaken, after adding on again two big vortex systems take shape, his cultivate speed can with ten thousand li in a day describe. Daily cultivate, he felt that obviously own will progress.

Not only this in the Soul Power aspect, various cultivation method is also so, for example Purple Demon Eyes. After his bloodline energy vortex take shape, this Purple Demon Eyes cultivate speed has promoted three times. Had achieved him who the bottleneck is very difficult to promote, actually obviously felt that in this time Purple Demon Eyes has progressive, his Spiritual Strength was promoting speed before be quicker.

---------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#873: warning sign(s)

Spirit Abyss Realm Spiritual Strength was quite rare in this age, but can also maintain such speed cultivate is being very few.

Gets out of bed, while he prepares to practice a while forging the time, suddenly, Tang Wulin only thought the own wrist place transmits scalding hot.

This is......

That scalding hot feeling unusual is obvious, his subconscious lowering the head looks that saw only in the own wrist that to come from initially chain bracelet in Dragon Valley, colored gem ray of light of water-drop shape was partly visible, scalding hot was also from this.

Since having this chain bracelet, it does not have any Transformation throughout, this was first appear(ance) reaction. Actually can have what? Can make it give off heat suddenly? Is to receive the bloodline stimulation of own to be the result?

In the heart has doubts at the same time, Tang Wulin gathers in front of own carefully to watch chain bracelet, but that scalding hot feeling actually becomes stronger and stronger, a restless feeling also along with it transmitting.

This was too strange, Tang Wulin not clear this chain bracelet has had anything to affect, but knows that this is in Dragon Valley these dragon soul gives his leaving gift. At this moment, feels is sending out scalding hot, in addition the restlessness of heart, making him somewhat vacant.

Is this is warning?

But, regarding own, what warning sign(s) there is to meet appear(ance)? If there is changed initially them in Devil Islands, or outside, he certainly immediately raises the intense vigilant heart.

But now they in Shrek Academy! In this world, what but also there is compared with a Shrek Academy safer place? Especially, here is Sea God Island, Shrek Academy radically heavy, Super Rank Douluo above stage Elite perhaps over ten, have Sky Raising Douluo this Present Generation to assume personal command greatly. What warning sign(s) will this have?

Certainly was the own feeling makes a mistake.

Stemming from the discrete consideration, Tang Wulin hurries to regard with rapt attention, observes the own bloodline vortex working condition. In order to avoid being because the own Golden Dragon King bloodline appear(ance) issue causes this chain bracelet to have the change.

But, his bloodline vortex functions as usual, own Qi and Blood is exuberant, will not affect his own bloodline vortex circulation.

All good cannot be good. Gets down according to such speed cultivate, certainly will make his whole person stronger and stronger.

For serveral days he started to try four Spiritual Metal to carry on Harmonizing Refinement, the effect was very good, relies on him to achieve the Soul Refinement stage strength, these were not the issues. Even he started to try five metal(s) to carry on Harmonizing Refinement, if can be successful, can let everybody future Battle Armor upper formation building inevitably, even if only Two Word Battle Armor, can the display of certain extent Three Word Battle Armor mighty energy.

In this time, chain bracelet temperature of ignition in wrist is dropping slowly, all as if returned to normal.

Tang Wulin relaxed, shrugs the arm, does not manage, who knows this outcome what's the matter? It is estimated that is only own has groundless fears that's all. In Shrek, can have an accident?

At the same time is thinking, he goes out of log cabin, directly soars own Forging Room to go. Starts today's forging practice.

So long as after he stabilizes lived in the own 7th Rank Forging Room level, he must start for everybody forging metal(s). The design drawing already prepared, so long as his forging has completed, Ye Xinglan and Yuan En Yehui they can simultaneously start for everybody manufacture Battle Armor. Takes their cultivation as, although needs certain process, but will not be slow. After all, they have beforehand Spiritual Metal One Word Battle Armor to take background, so long as carried on the structural transformation to be enough on own original Battle Armor foundation.

......

„Master, you how?” A female of black clothed asked in a soft voice.

Here is the summit, the mountain peak reaches to the sky, takes a broad view to look, is the big piece and big piece clouds. Mountain breeze bone-chilling cold, moved cloud band the moist air to pass over gently and swiftly from the summit a piece by piece, but in their surroundings, did not have the least bit water vapor.

Gu Yuena stands in the cliff edge, a white long skirt serves as contrast her silver-haired to be graceful, in her eyes is revealing vacant, shaking the head of gently, „why does not know, I suddenly have the feeling of feel ill-at-ease. My heartbeat speed has promoted five times every minute compared with normal condition.”

„What?” That black clothed female is surprised, „High Lord, your this is......”

Gu Yuena shook the head, „I do not know. I let thing preparation that you prepare how?”

Black clothed female sinking sound track: „Has prepared 60%, the preliminary work has been completed, Di Tian said that his side does not have the issue. When all preparations finished, so long as High Lord act , can certainly 100% successes. Again then, is waited for that time completed.”

„Um.” Gu Yuena nodded, shows neither approval nor disapproval.

After the black clothed female slightly makes the stop, is probing the [say / way]: „High Lord, that side person contacted with us. The enemy of enemy is a friend, don't we cooperate with them really?”

Gu Yuena has turned round fiercely, right hand wields, terrifying aura erupts suddenly from her, the feeling of that terrifying made the entire summit shiver, surroundings all fog instantaneous to shatter, changed into the fine rain in airborne to surge outward.

That black clothed female directly shelled flew, summit surroundings is reverberating Gu Yuena ice-cold sounds/voices, „I had said many times, these dirty dirty existence, forever do not want to cooperate with me. Mentioned them before me again, I have dug up your dragon hide.”

The black clothed female disappeared, has not returned to the summit again.

Gu Yue complexion sinks to congeal, long time has not spoken, but, in her mind, reappeared gradually that form.

Has distinguished to be so long, he fortunately?

Why I such feel ill-at-ease, in this world, can make me so worry about, as if, only then he......

......

The silent room is very broad, vault assumes the arc, has spread to the surroundings wall from the vault, the demon mark of big piece and big piece covers.

The entire room best pupil has 30 meters, the diameter is about 50 meters, range and broadness. Center the room, altogether 12 people sit cross-legged to sit there, they regarding becoming a circle. In mouth in muttering was talking over anything.

In these 12 person body surroundings, is all ascending Soul Ring, if some people can see them, the discovery that can shock, on these 12 is ascending, unexpectedly is Eight Soul Rings, Eight Rings Soul Douluo, this has stood in Soul Master in existence of peak, is, at this moment, so numerous Soul Douluo in the same place, to do a matter unexpectedly.

They sit cross-legged in the ground that sits, demon mark is more complex . Moreover, what terrifying is, has blood to flow in this demon mark surroundings piece by piece, that portrays gullies that demon mark becomes, in these gullies, is flowing blood unceasingly Transformation.

The room addendum circle, over a hundred people stand there, they all is a black clothed, the head wears the black headgear, only reveals the left hand of own, but that blood, wrist [lineage/vein] place unceasing flowing that cuts open from their left hand, but under becomes.

Light bloody aura fills the air, making in the entire room give people an intense sense of fear, but is this rich courage vigor fluctuates, is actually not able to transmit the half minute outward.

Actually was this? Actually to have what? Will create so the picture unexpectedly?

But in that 12 the Soul Douluo location circle midpoint that sits cross-legged to sit, in the ground is purple-black six glow stars, strong bloody aura outward releases, there, is standing erect the same thing. That is one reaches as high as three meters, presents all over the body is purple-black, above has innumerable demon mark, and is sparkling ray of light existence.

Its peak presents for sharp pyramidal, extends downward, looks like has wing to open a piece by piece, surroundings that huge energy, is all rivers run into sea emerges to it, but it looks like a bottomless pit is ordinary, absorb that huge energy and blood.

#874: Attack suddenly to

Also not only so, in the next room, unexpectedly also has another exactly the same place, but, in that room, that existence of central Nucleus position is actually all over the body ink-green, demon mark strange changeable.

Hundred black-clothed person of addendum circle, are 12 Soul Douluo rank Elite of inner loop, their bodies gradually are becoming because of the outflow of energy withered, may in these two rooms, not have least bit sounds/voices to spread throughout.

Tang Sect.

After Guo Xiaoxu has processed a series of official business, in the eye is revealing color looking pensive. In this time, vigorous sounds/voices is transmitting.

„Does Xiaoxu, what think? Such is enthralled, all right do our two brothers drink one cup to go?” Tang Sect Outer Three Halls Strength Hall Hall Master Zhao Song walked from outside, feels own big bald, on face with a laugh.

He and Guo Xiaoxu relate extremely good, their age is similar, the past years was together cultivate companion, was only afterward cultivate choice of direction different that's all, simultaneously joined Tang Sect, afterward became the Tang Sect high levels. Although Guo Xiaoxu be higher than Zhao Song in the Tang Sect status, but this has not affected among them the brothers friendship.

Guo Xiaoxu said: „Does not drink. In the gate the matter were too recently many, two Hall Master both were not, Worship Hall that side Worshipped was ineffective, can only be I comes.”

Zhao Song said: „That side Heaven Dou City hasn't processed? Wasn't that side aftermath was similar?”

Guo Xiaoxu sighed, said: „Holy Spirit Cult went into hiding these many year again appear(ance), the organization is strict. Although Heaven Dou City that side aftermath was near the end, but, where we actually cannot discover the Holy Spirit Cult main force. Before Vice Hall Master assumed personal command in that side personally, has not discovered the clue as before, but caught cat 2-3 that's all. According to Hall Master analysis, this Holy Spirit Cult recently so large-scale motion, not only certainly aims at Heaven Dou City, where has the possibility, therefore, we must maintain vigilant are good.”

Zhao Song brow slightly pressed, „said is also, this group of hateful bastards. Do not let me find them, making me bump into, must twist to make the chamber pot their heads.”

Guo Xiaoxu he he smiles, „you you, are that temperament. Outside you hall also sufficed recently busily, ok, I accompany you to drink one cup. This relaxation time, must relax. Liang Xiaoyu? Called him together.”

„Good.”

As the night falls, Tang Sect also gradually peaceful.

Tang Wulin has completed the forging practice of own, walks from Forging Room, only thinks outside darkness. Looks up to Sky.

Tonight the night violent wind filled with dust is high, Star Dou all does not have, to human an intense depression.

At this moment, that colored gem in his wrist once again scalding hot, moreover compared with former more intense many, making Tang Wulin almost directly fling to fly it.

What's the matter? Tang Wulin hurries to look down.

In the dim light of night looks is clearer, that colored gem turned into piece of blood-red at this moment unexpectedly, an intense sense of fear, raises from the Tang Wulin moral nature along with it.

This is......

warning sign(s), certainly is warning sign(s). Certainly has any matter to occur.

If daytime time he can also comfort own, may at this moment, this feeling really be too intense, is unable to neglect to him intensely again.

Personal appearance glittering, the Tang Wulin whole person leapt up, directly soars the Sea God Island direction to go, simultaneously has dialed Xie Xie Soul Guide Communication Device fast.

„Xie Xie, are you doing?” Tang Wulin rapid asking.

„Just prepared to start meditation! How Boss? Has any matter to say tomorrow again. Yuan En promises me, today lets me with her together meditation, hey.”

Tang Wulin anxious sound track: „First other meditation, you called Yuan En, then called other people, immediately arrives at Sea God Island. I have not the good premonition, perhaps has any matter to occur.”

„? Boss, what matter? Can you affirm? So was late, but also called everybody?”

Tang Wulin gets angry: „Makes you call you quickly. I did not determine that what happened, but felt that is not very really right. You quickly, we concentrate on Sea God Island.”

Without a doubt, Sea God Island is the safest place.

Xie Xie trusts Tang Wulin after all extremely, hears under the word, hurries saying: „Good, then sees on Sea God Island, we pass immediately.”

Hung up the communication, Tang Wulin arrived at the Sea God lake lakeside, the point of tip of the toe gently in the ground, the human already in the surging waves lake. Goes in the Sea God Island direction fast.

At this moment, the jet black nighttime sky had glistened suddenly, Tang Wulin while toward the Sea God Island rapid vanguard, looks up.

He saw strange one, in Sky, bunch of ray of light are entraining the enchanting eye-catching tail flame, is coming from out of the blue, that ray of light becomes more and more intense, clearly arrives in the Shrek Academy direction.

Missile? Or is Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell? The enemies raid, is the enemy raids unexpectedly!

Shrek City, is the entire Continent first big city, Shrek Academy itself, although is only Academy, but also has the own army in Shrek City, is the Shrek army specially. The population are not many, only then 30,000 people, this is Federation permits the Shrek City army population limit, but actually all well-equipped, only Mecha Master has 5000 people, entire five Mecha Master.

In addition Shrek Academy numerous summits go against the big energy, the Twenty-thousand Years history, here is honored as Shrek that does not fall.

Who can think that some people dare to initiate attack to Shrek City unexpectedly, but that is similar to the meteor shower common missile group, seems has over a hundred unexpectedly fully.

Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell can far, but, the missile defense system in Shrek City is not the ornaments! If these arrive at pill are really come from city, from Shrek City certain range, sufficiently was destroyed.

But, these missiles actually arrived at sky over Shrek Academy, moreover looks at such, the missile is scattered, covers entire Shrek City Inner City sufficiently.

Tang Wulin looks at that just like the meteor shower common missile group, the whole person in the instantaneous delay. What situation is this? The own very soon had a premonition that is unexpectedly correct, unexpectedly real appear(ance) in view of the attack of Shrek, this was simply inconceivable!

Also at this moment, Light and Shadow rise straight from the ground from the Sea God Island direction, breaks in the upper air instantaneously. At the beginning only then seven forms raised, dozens forms followed take-off.

That impressively is the Shrek Academy Inner Court numerous position big energy.

Seven ray of light that raises first are most eye-catching, each ray of light is containing huge might, with their take-off, other ray of light is also in abundance take-off and dispersing, welcomed to that Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell that airborne dropped.

When Tang Wulin is conscientious, falls , on Sea God Island, in Sky the first sound thundered also to make a sound.

Fierce thundering and explosion, look like giant fireworks, is similar to the daytime of sky over entire Sea God Island shining.

The good terrifying explosive force, is this at least also 7th Rank above Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell? Tang Wulin dumbfounded looks, but this time he, is actually anything busy cannot add on, has not arrived at Two Word Battle Armor, he did not have flying ability, can only look helplessly Inner Court Teacher(s) and Senior meet the approaching enemy the powerful enemy.

„Bang, bang. Bang” one after another thunders to resound, in Sky brilliant fireworks blast out.

Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell before Ten-thousand Years is most terrifying weapon, 7th Rank above Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell is induced as existence of strategic weapon.

But at this moment, explodes in the upper air, actually does not have Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell to be lower than 7th Rank.

-----------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#875: Fireworks sea

The initial take-off that summit goes against extremely can be better greatly, the behind take-off Shrek Academy Inner Court students, in that more and more terrifying energy turbulent flow, oppressed crash in abundance return to above the ground.

The explosion of terrifying resounds one after another, but that take-off form, actually these Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell all in the upper air 11 detonations, has not made artillery shell fall into the city.

The distant place, in Inner City and Outer City, more and more forms soar. Shrek City, gathers is not knowing many Elite, not only there are to belong to Shrek Academy, meanwhile has to belong to Tang Sect.

Numerous forms that fly high, but to Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell detonates, time, sky over entire Shrek City, as if turned into the fireworks sea.

In this time, the distant place, forms are grazing to come from the level of the lake, is Xie Xie, Yuan En Yehui as well as Shrek Seven Monsters several other people.

Sees them, Tang Wulin then reaction comes, hurries to release own bloodline aura, guides them to own side.

„heavens! Actually did this have what? This......” Xie Xie already was shocking grinning with ear to ear.

He somewhat was formerly discontented with the summon of Tang Wulin, can have with the Yuan En intimate opportunity with great difficulty, was actually destroyed by him. May at this moment, where he also be able to say least bit question sounds/voices.

Other people complexion are all dignified.

They are very clear, aim in Shrek Academy such attack, is it may be said that unprecedented!

The airborne energy fluctuation starts to drop from the clouds, even if stands on Sea God Island, can feel that terrifying pressure as before. If makes these be full of the destructive assault wave to fall in the ground, perhaps, the entire city will be hit by the devastating disaster.

At this moment, flash raise, changes into screen to jack. At the beginning was Shrek Inner City, Shrek Academy Outer City has also shone, two screen carried the assault wave hardly, kept off them outside, although flood fierce mighty waves, but excluded finally these assault waves.

Tang Wulin has not exchanged with companion, their complexion is a dignity, regarding them, but also is not enough to participate in such battlefield. But, why did Shrek Academy actually like this become the battlefield?

Daytime time Tang Wulin has also thought that Shrek Academy is the safest place, may to the evening, really have the attack arrival of such terrifying.

Over a hundred 7th Rank above Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell, this absolutely is the money of astronomical figures! Is Federation to aim in Shrek City attack? Said that came from Holy Spirit Cult?

Former's words are impossible, after all, in Federation does not know that has many are the high level that graduates from Shrek Academy. Let alone, Shrek Academy is neutral throughout, has not affected the Federation resolution, but protects Shrek City this pure lands.

But if is the latter, was extremely fearful. Evil Soul Master Sect, a terrifying organization, can actually control so numerous Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell, what does this mean? If Federation nobody and they colludes, who believes?

Certainly cannot make Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell fall! Otherwise, Shrek City will face with the Heaven Dou City same terrifying disaster without doubt.

Thinks of Heaven Dou City, the heart of Tang Wulin tightens suddenly, because he remembers immediately, initially Guo Xiaoxu had said to him, Heaven Dou City terrorist attack , because a 9th Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell large explosion causes.

To 9th Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell that stage, but was not existence that urban Guard Screen can resist easily, 9th Rank above Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell, even if were Super Rank Douluo does not dare the frontage to touch hardly.

Thinks of here, the feelings of some of his having a parched mouth, these have Evil Soul Master, actually prepared how the terrifying offensive to them? These that perhaps at present does not see.

Sea God Pavilion.

Sea God Pavilion Master and Sky Raising Douluo Yun Ming stands in the Sea God Pavilion crown, Holy Spirit Douluo Ya Li side him. Similarly in his side also has Light and Dark Douluo Long Yeyue.

Three Great Titled Douluo is looking out the upper air.

Yun Ming understands finally why own will have that intense feel ill-at-ease, originally must have the matter is not other places, but is Shrek City, is Shrek Academy.

Like Tang Wulin how, regardless of unable to think that some people dare attack Shrek City, is Sea God Pavilion Master he has not thought similarly. At this time already was the surface sank like water.

Ya Li has gotten hold of the hand of Yun Ming, does not know that many years have not felt like the present intense. May at this moment, in her heart actually be very anxious.

They know, since Holy Spirit Cult dares to attack Shrek City, that certainly has not the small assurance.

„Good! The time really changed.” Light and Dark Douluo Long Yeyue sneers, „looks like, my Shrek was too long has not shown the fang really outward, any any cat and dog dares to have our ideas. Yun Ming, was effect of Shrek on Federation so weak? So numerous Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell come here, what's the matter? Moreover launches from Outer City close-range, what's the matter? Our Shrek City was defense, so when frail?”

Facing the accusation of Light and Dark Douluo, Yun Ming is dumbfounded.

Yes! Shrek City is really peaceful was too long, Shrek City that does not fall, this has the same thought in each individual heart. Who can think that some people will dare attack Shrek?

By these many Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell close-range attack, this is meant any he is clear, this Limit Douluo also gets hold of the double fist at this time.

But he knows that own is at this moment calm, must control the overall situation. attack of enemy is not only so is at present simple.

At this moment, the earth hears the slight(ly) vibration sound, Yun Ming and Long Yeyue complexion simultaneously changes.

Low and deep thundering, from distant place crack, this time not in Sky, but in ground.

If can discover from the airborne bird's eye view that Shrek City Outer City, mushroom clouds are raising suddenly, the explosions of terrifying as if collected the pitiful yell sounds of innumerable people.

Started, finally started.

Since the enemies can ship Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell to Outer City in the close-range launch, that naturally also has the means in the Outer City direct detonation.

Shrek City is entire Continent first Metropolis, has most numerous population, almost every person takes can become the Shrek City citizen for the honor. May at this moment, an unprecedented catastrophe actually suddenly arrive.

Yun Ming complexion piece of pale white, the entire Shrek City army went into action, when just the appear(ance) danger, he had issued the order, closes off all streets, seals up Outer City, cannot pass and out, investigates rigorously Outer City.

May order to issue for several minutes, fierce explosions have taken the response.

The explosion in Sky is the fireworks, but the explosion in ground is actually devastating! Over 15 explosions, do not know that many innocent common people therefore died.

Without a doubt, this is a long-premeditated war, yes, is the war, but no longer is terrorist attack. This is a disaster, suddenly, without the disaster of any omen.

Any city, has various types of precise detectors, surveys all high explosive cargos. Like Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell this type of dangerous material, is any city, once were discovered must process immediately.

But, in Shrek City, on Shrek that does not fall, actually some so numerous High Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell appear(ance) do not have anybody to discover that what this does mean?

Means that the enemy has the method of practicing trickery, means that Shrek City already was not sheet iron one.

Yun Ming understood suddenly, the Heaven Dou City large explosion, attracted the attention of numerous people, Tang Sect or Shrek Academy, have dispatched many Elite going that side. But the ultimate goal of enemy, actually is not Heaven Dou City.

genuine to Holy Spirit Cult has the huge threat is not Heaven Dou City, but is Shrek Academy, is Tang Sect.

Therefore, the enemy final attack goal, from beginning to end is here!

„I go.” Ya Li drinks one lowly, exits on the strategic place. Actually held on by Yun Ming.

attack of enemy will not stop, Shrek Academy or Tang Sect General Headquarters, in Shrek Inner City. The losses that at this time their attack Outer City, causes are huge, but was also insufficient to injure the Shrek City basis.

Therefore, this attack had not ended absolutely. Once at this moment, they were flurried, was transferred by the enemy, then, can only be a bigger disaster arrives.

„Tang Sect, please save the sick and wounded, Outer City asked you.” Yun Ming sounds/voices passes on by far.

ray of light dodges, in his Light and Dark Douluo Long Yeyue take-off, this could not endure patiently suddenly finally.

-----------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#876: Sky Raising, Shooting Day

Yun Ming lifted the hand, has not prevented eventually. This, he did not prevent.

takes a deep breath tone, Yun Ming calm gets hold of the hand of Holy Spirit Douluo Ya Li, „I am Shrek sinner, but, I must preserve Shrek.”

The Sea God Island edge, the Tang Wulin seven people at this time is a complexion paleness.

The Outer City large explosion they can hear, can see that mushroom cloud that the distant place leaps similarly.

Their brains completely is a blank, matter that this is unable to imagine, where they do not even know the enemy. This terrifying disaster occurred.

The energy storm in Sky has not diverged as before, but that mushroom cloud actually does not know Devour many Life.

„Comes to Sea God Pavilion!” In this time, dignified sounds/voices is transmitting suddenly. Spreads to their ears.

Tang Wulin hit to tremble smartly spirit , the market comes immediately, beckoned to companion, flushed away in the Sea God Pavilion direction fast.

Sea God Island not big, quick, before they arrived at the Sea God Pavilion Golden Tree room, saw hand in hand stands there Sky Raising Douluo and Holy Spirit Douluo.

Yun Ming is very calm, seems looks like anything has not occurred. Saw that the Tang Wulin seven people arrive, Yun Ming goes forward one step, arrives in front of him.

„From now on, regardless has anything, do not leave Sea God Pavilion. Goes, to inside.”

Tang Wulin stares, „Pavilion Master, please let us strive for Academy, we......”

„Shut up. Goes in!” The Yun Ming tian item shouted angrily suddenly, waved, terrifying energy has curled up seven people, sent in them Sea God Pavilion.

„Remember, you are the seeds of Academy, if had the worst case scenario. Future you, are the bases that Academy recovers.” Yun Ming sounds/voices reverberates in seven people of ears.

The Tang Wulin discoloration, has situation gone bad to so the degree with amazement?

At this moment, Tang Wulin suddenly discovered that outside all turned into purple, does not have the omen turned into purple. That was Sky turned into purple, but Sky purple, shone upon the homochromy the earth.

Golden Tree jumps suddenly projects together radiant golden-colored ray of light, covers in which entire Shrek Academy Inner Court. The entire Sea God Pavilion location Golden Tree room has also shone. The unequalled rich Life strength lingers side them, prevents them unable to run out of Sea God Pavilion to go.

Tang Wulin clear incomparable seeing, when that terrifying purple appear(ance), in Sky, that bunch formerly the form that raised from Shrek Academy, all vanished in that purple unexpectedly, without a trace of disappearance, looked like disappears instantaneously general, from this world thorough erased.

Body of Sky Raising Douluo Yun Ming obvious shivered, the next quarter, he is pulling Holy Spirit Douluo Ya Li hand take-off, breaks in the upper air.

Airborne purple became even more rich, even linked golden-colored ray of light that the Golden Tree room bloomed also to start gradually to shatter.

Yun Ming erupts together the unequalled radiant brilliance, tries to clash from that purple, is, that purple light actually so fearful. Also at this moment, huge purple Skeleton appear(ance) in sky.

That purple Skeleton diameter has the kilometer fully, it opens mouth, a flame downward blowout. Top Skeleton, sits cross-legged to sit well nine people, is a black robe. On the black robe has near the green light forward, on them, is all ascending Nine Soul Rings. The person in most Nucleus place, in Nine Soul Rings, unexpectedly orange and four red, surplus also all are black.

„Yun Ming, cannot think that your Shrek also has today. Starting today, in society does not have Shrek again, in society does not have Tang Sect again.”

Huge purple Skeleton first dark-purple flame spurts to fall, collides with the Yun Ming (spear|gun) intent together.

Sky Raising Spear erupts the radiant brilliance instantaneously, ray of light that on under Golden Tree releases collects suddenly in the same place, falls on Yun Ming. Immediately, the body of Yun Ming whole person turned into bright golden-colored.

weighty and magnificent and expensive Four Word Battle Armor covers the whole body, he is at this moment common just like War God.

However, because just Golden Tree energy collects inward, strongly on his body, Tang Wulin they penetrates the window, helplessly looks, Golden Tree surroundings, all on Sea God Island in fast disintegration, under that terrifying purple ray of light shines breaks up.

„12th Rank, you dare to face universal condemnation unexpectedly, start 12th Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell.” The Yun Ming roaring sound from the sky reverberates. energy fluctuation of terrifying in the explosion of entire Shrek Academy sky madness.

Tang Wulin has tarried, his companion also dumbfounded.

Xie Xie does not dare to imagine completely, if own has not listened to Tang Wulin, arrives at Sea God Island promptly, will have what kind of disaster.

The distant place, ray of light shines together, that said that ray of light is green, position that terrifying green, it explodes, is Tang Sect General Headquarters.

Entire Shrek City, turned into a world of piece of death, bird's eye view from Sky, what can see, one green, one purple, vortex that two expand unceasingly in Devour surroundings all, unceasing expansion outward. Entire Shrek Inner City, in fast is vanishing from this world.

All protections, become meaningless between that green and purple.

Does not know many Life, in that terrifying energy storm wreaks havoc is vanishing.

The Golden Tree room is shivering, fierce is shivering, Tang Wulin only thought that at present all became illusory, since two big energy vortex take shape, he believes that own has been able to base in Soul Master. May at this moment, facing so the Tianwei general terrifying energy oppression, he only think own just like the ants.

If without a doubt, at this moment, they are outside the Golden Tree room, then, certainly by energy of that death Devour, certainly will become Sacrifice of this terrifying storm.

Ended, Shrek Academy ended.

Who can think that meets the appear(ance) so terrifying picture unexpectedly, Continent first Academy, Shrek that day does not fall, falls.

Golden Tree room fierce is shivering, unceasing flaking of outer layer golden light (Jin Guang) under that terrifying purple ray of light assault.

Tang Wulin remembers suddenly, initially Yun Ming once severe has said to him, because of his Fifth Soul Ring take shape, absorb Golden Tree room too many energy, makes Golden Tree room energy damage greatly. If own does not have absorb, whether energy of Golden Tree room can block this attack!

Ended, all ended.

golden-colored of Golden Tree room collapses finally thoroughly, that terrifying death energy made the Sea God Pavilion outer layer start irrelevant to shatter.

Tang Wulin stubborn is biting the lip, stretches out the arms, keeps off in front of companion, bloomed his Golden Dragon Frantic Domain.

But he is very clear, in front of such terrifying Tianwei, own anything could not do, did not have the means to protect anybody.

„Sky Raising, Shooting Day!” At this moment, outside transmits sonic boom to drink suddenly.

This sounds/voices hurls the brain, making the terrifying pressure that the Tang Wulin seven people bore suddenly one light. Sea God Pavilion fragment(s) suddenly freeze outside disintegration, at this moment, like the entire space and time for it static.

In Sky, Sky Raising Douluo Yun Ming complexion sinks to congeal tranquilly, but has the endless sadness in his eye pupil deep place.

Is Present Generation Sea God Pavilion Pavilion Master, actually must look at Shrek Academy to ruin helplessly in the own hand, more than 20,000 years of inheritance! Must cut off in light of this, his mood at this moment can be imagined.

12th Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell, this is attack how regardless of being unable to judge.

The ultimate weapon that present age, this was studied altogether has three, in entire Humanity historical also only then three, for these three 12th Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell, Federation made innumerably finally has developed diligently successfully, but Federation once announced at that time that will stop the persistent research and development of this type of Super Rank devastating weapon, by Douluo Continent resources, was impossible manufacture to leave fourth again.

#877: Sky Raising's Light, Final Brilliant Era

These three 12th Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell are born before two Thousand Years, after they are born, the entire Humanity science and technology stagnated of Thousand Years, is resources that because initially they consumed is really extremely huge.

These three 12th Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell, were being protected by strictest way (of life) by Federation, as the entire Douluo Continent ultimate weapon.

Their title, is also called, Kill the Gods! In other words, these three Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell are considered that has to murder Kill the Gods ability. The mighty energy can be imagined.

Nobody has experimented their might, even under 12th Rank, 11th Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell no longer existence. May regarding them, attaching great importance to of Federation forever be most Advanced other. If one day, really must use them, needing entire Federation Parliament unanimously pass, there is a ticket, is unuseful.

Who can think that is such terrifying existence, the entire Continent ultimate weapon, actually meets appear(ance) here, appear(ance) in Shrek Academy, appear(ance) in Tang Sect.

Two 12th Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell mighty energy, sufficiently the entire Shrek City thorough destruction!

That beforehand take-off numerous position Titled Douluo, numerous position Inner Court disciple, all sudden large explosion disappear in this terrifying and. Certainly temporary Shrek Academy, unexpectedly vanishes in puff of smoke in the moment.

This is the terrifying science and technology, after this is the Humanity science and technology studies so the degree, killing that genuine creates.

In the Yun Ming hand Sky Raising Spear holds up high, that came from Golden Tree Life energy is bursting out the eye-catching glory, falls on Shrek Academy the 12th Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell named: Kill the Gods, Ruin the Heavens, Destroy the Earth. Falls that side Tang Sect, named: Kill the Gods, Devour the Heavens and Earth.

At this moment, can see from his angle of view that entire Shrek City is breaking up.

Wipes the mirthless smile to flow from his corners of the mouth place, his 4th Rank Battle Armor suddenly fierce combustion, by his Limit Douluo mighty energy, impossible to contend with 12th Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell the strength of Kill the Gods, but if he wants to run away, does not have anybody to block to block him.

But can he walk? He cannot. Shrek Academy perishes in light of this, as Present Generation Sea God Pavilion Pavilion Master, his Duty-bound Responsibility, he cannot walk.

He can see on distant place that huge Skeleton, in that Evil Soul Master eye cloudy and cold vision of ridicule, can feel in Shrek City clearly, terminations of Life.

How may regret , was unable to reverse the present aspect.

How are all these occur? Why 12th Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell will reveal, why under for many years peace, Shrek City own defense already small and weak in this way. If these two Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell nearby do not launch, if launches outside the city, at least will not cause so the devastating disaster.

In the Yun Ming mind flashes through innumerable thoughts instantaneously, but he can do now, has a matter.

Sky Raising, Shooting Day!

Dazzling golden light (Jin Guang), his own complete coverage golden light (Jin Guang) vigorous eruption, in him behind, golden-colored rays starts appear(ance), these golden-colored rays each other interweave and are outlining, take shape strange huge rune. After this rune appear(ance). Entire spatial suddenly static. On distant place Skeleton nine Evil Soul Master are astonished by it.

Is that Evil Soul Master right hand wields, under the body Skeleton escapes suddenly, instantaneous already to hundred li (0.5km) beyond, his complexion is cloudy, in the mouth puts out two characters, „God Position!”

That golden-colored rays outlined the forming rapidly, sad cry also resounded under the Yun Ming body, „did not want! Elder Brother Ming.”

Yun Ming lowered the head slowly, is full of the attachment looked under one that outstandingly beautiful tender face, „I do not have the face to see the Shrek older generations. Left Ya Li. Looks after own well, is Shrek, retains the final seed.”

Spoke these words, in his hand Sky Raising Spear shakes suddenly, back that [say / way] golden-colored ray breaks up suddenly, while they break up, innumerable radiant golden light (Jin Guang) burst out suddenly, in an instant spreads to entire Shrek City unexpectedly, will put in order sky over Shrek City to cover completely.

Yun Ming enters step Limit Douluo to have dozens years, in these dozens years of time, he was inquiring about is the Humanity limit, is inquiring about the path to another world.

He cannot feel God Realm existence, only then genuine to this realm, understands that God Realm is real, but God Realm is actually not receiving and instructing the world.

Wants genuine Becomes a God, only if, creates God Realm again.

Yun Ming in all previous Sea God Pavilion Master, cultivates for absolute being considered as on is among the best, he does not know whether own this life will succeed, but he has actually been trying hard, at least is paving the way for the posterity, he also believes that the near future, Humanity can certainly walk once more, reconstructs God Realm.

In him behind the position of that Gods, is he newly-established, in the future will plan to roam through the preparation outside outer space. God Realm needs the position of Gods, in old book early has the record. When the position of his own Gods is formidable enough, when to him can formidable homemade God Realm, at least covers Douluo Continent this world, he succeeds.

What a pity, he dozens years of effort, initially peeps the access, even if all normal, this life impossible real Creation leaves God Realm to come, he can do, leaves behind own experience.

But at this moment, Shrek Academy suddenly by so total destruction, when he is outspoken when the position of own that incomplete Gods releases, he is the god of moment.

Gods breaks up, energy that Fallen of god, brings, is the peak that in this life can reach.

Two 12th Rank Kill the Gods Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell have succeeded, they succeed Kill the Gods, but Yun Ming also uses own final strength, is melting their terrifying destructive power.

purple and black, under that golden-colored neutralize, were attracted to absorb in the midair forcefully, three colors collide and pester mutually. Unceasing disintegration and to shatter.

The body of Yun Ming gradually becomes illusory, regardless of Ya Li how diligently, is unable to rise into airborne.

Yun Ming lowers the head, he does not have to watch the collision in Sky again, because he has made contribution, he has all released all that own can release.

But at this moment, in his look does not abandon. He does not give up Shrek Academy, does not give up own Lover.

He can only see Ya Li shape of the mouth unceasingly Transformation, actually could not hear her to say anything, he saw her tears crossflow, saw look that her as if must collapse.

He said in a soft voice: „For Shrek, goes on living.”

Spoke these words, he stretches out the arms suddenly, right hand ray of light one gloomy, Sky Raising Spear drops from the clouds, falls into the Ya Li hand. Under that final superhuman strength in addition holds, this handle Sky Raising Spear escaped the strength finally the Martial Soul range, genuine condense became the entity.

Stretching out the arms Yun Ming, body [gold/metal] ascends Peak, just like round genuine Sun. The next quarter, he flew to shoot to go toward distant place that huge Skeleton.

Sky Raising's Light, Final Brilliant Era.

On Skeleton nine Evil Soul Master have a big shock, that huge Skeleton All-Out accelerates. This time Yun Ming, no longer is Limit Douluo, but is Fallen Gods. The prestige of it Fallen, is not they are willing to collide finally.

But, Gods speed, can it be that they can run away.

In radiant golden light (Jin Guang), that huge Skeleton by Devour, entire Sky was turned accordingly into an incandescent color in an instant! The dark night as if had been scattered by that flash, two Kill the Gods Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell mighty energy , was only attracted finally to absorb by that final god.

Under all white light cover the Life body only to crawl in the place, was oppressed by that terrifying energy. white light is not loose for a very long time, like the Yun Ming unwilling thought.

Tang Wulin lies on the ground, he supports to crawl, how regardless of actually unable to achieve. He hears each character that Yun Ming finally said clearly, in the mind actually as before is a blank.

This all comes suddenly and too to be too sudden. So formidable Shrek Academy, unexpectedly one night, complete disintegration.

In this vast just like the war between Gods, they so small and weak, they can face, only then this logic of war. Under the collision of that terrifying, they are similar to the ants, anything did not do. If no protection of Sea God Pavilion, they already changed into the dust.

Has not known long time, all gradually stopped. Outside ray of light is gloomy gradually, all as if vanished. As before is a silence. When Tang Wulin gains ground once more, what sees is front Sea God Pavilion, the disintegration, changes into the dust slowly, being quietly to four disperses.

Also at this moment, golden light (Jin Guang) flies suddenly from the Sea God Pavilion deep place, drills into the Tang Wulin forehead quietly, is hidden does not see.

Holy Spirit Douluo Ya Li, crawls in the ground in distant place, remains unconscious. Takes a broad view to look, a surroundings deathly stillness.

----------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#878: I also love you

Sea God Island disappears, the Sea God lake was dry, takes a broad view to look, Tang Wulin can see that has a darkness. A piece jet black is similar to the abyss is ordinary, sinks to the bottom to have thousand zhang (3.33 m) endocrater fully.

Is this Shrek Academy? Is this Shrek City? May at this moment, they only be able to see endless darkness.

Shrek Seven Monsters crawls from the ground, their vision are the delay, the expression of everyone is stiff, at this moment, they distinct restored speech ability, actually links a character unable to say.

Shrek, their Shrek Academy, unexpectedly such, erased from entire Continent.

From beginning to end, entire process as if only then the dozen minutes, certainly temporary Shrek Academy, able to move unhindered Continent more than 20,000 years of inheritance, in light of this disappear. The students and Teacher(s), skeleton not saves. Surplus, Holy Spirit Douluo that as if only then their seven people remain unconscious with that.

Scarlet Dragon Douluo Zhuo Shi and Blazing Dragon Douluo Feng Wuyu and Silver Moon Douluo Old Cai and Light and Dark Douluo Long Yeyue, innumerable Shrek Academy Elite, vanished in just that Kill the Gods, Ruin the Heavens, Destroy the Earth. Thorough disappearance.

They are only 20 years old after all, although experienced has disciplined much, may meet the big change suddenly, time some are unable to accept.

They were survival Academy suddenly do not even have depending on the study. Is inheritance of Shrek Academy next generation, Present Generation Shrek Seven Monsters, Shrek that actually behind the company depends upon did not have.

This is not a war, but radically is a disaster! The two big influences of row on front row on Continent, Shrek Academy perishes now, Tang Sect General Headquarters vanishes.

Tang Sect is relatively better, at least they also has the branch in other cities, but Shrek Academy actually alone this! The Continent liveliest city, is living Super Rank big city in light of this Fallen of more than ten million population. Simultaneously Fallen also more than ten million people!

It can be said that since Douluo Continent has had Humanity, this is a biggest disaster, an unprecedented disaster.

At this moment, sky over their top of the head has shone suddenly. That eye-catching ray of light made them not lift the head on own initiative.

Wipes desperately, simultaneously appear(ance) in seven people of eyes. In the sky of their location gulf, sparkles the brilliant light group is being similar to falls at top speed generally toward the pit.

Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell, is Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell. artillery shell has not arrived, they who prestigious imposing manner oppressed breathe difficulties, that terrifying flavor, making them deeply feel arrival of death.

Utterly destroy!

At this time in their hearts, only then these four characters that can think. Comes regardless of today's these Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell from where, without a doubt, the enemies have not planned to let off in them any.

Only utterly destroys, can not leave the future trouble.

Fends? Runs away? They may run away roadless. Here is thousand zhang (3.33 m) abyss. That artillery shell already close at hand. At least is also 8th Rank above Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell. Takes their cultivation as, regardless of how ultra level display, impossible to escape in front of such to destroy the heavens and exterminate the land mighty energy.

They did not have the dependence, does not have the asylum of Shrek Academy, they can only use the body of own, withstands this terrifying attack.

A Tang Wulin first market comes finally, he does not have the hesitation of half minute, his fierce cross previous step, then fierce jumps to jump.

His strength had already been the shocking degree, even if solely depends on taking advantage of strength of body, this leaps, really also fully has 30 zhang (3.33 m). Moreover, huge Vine release from his body, including golden speech (Jin Yu) golden-colored Vine, was added by Blue Silver Overlord Transformation instantaneously holds, since he leaps the next quarter, fierce a brace in ground, this, has delivered to over 500 meters upper air him.

He cannot soar, only the useful this law, making own fly is higher.

He stretched out the arms, welcomes to that dropping from the clouds Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell. He does not know that own can prevent many, but only has so, can own companion the opportunity that catches to live.

At least here, he has no cares and is alone in the world. He only hopes that companion can live. Although hopes as before uncertainly.

Bright golden-colored jumps on him shoots, golden-colored dragon scales covers the body, he from the sky accelerates unexpectedly once again, Golden Dragon Soars, making him clash 50 meters once more, that Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell is only close.

Tang Wulin even can see clearly, on that artillery shell complex traces are bursting out Frantic ray of light. At this moment, in his heart does not have fear, only then misses. Is missing his Parents, is missing Na'er, in his heart that most profound Shadow.

Gu Yue, left. If you are well, is cloudless day. Has forgotten me, I did not have the means to complete in the heart to your promise.

Closes both eyes, two drops of tears fall from the cheek place, he stretches out the arms, all become seem to be unimportant, in him at present, Gu Yue form as if illusory appear(ance) there, he only wants to use the both arms of own, enters in her tight hugging the bosom.

Tang Wulin has satisfied, leaves this world in so illusion, all burden no longer existence. Is having missing, he must walk.

„Wulin!”

„Captain!”

„Boss!”

Shrek Seven Monsters reaction comes finally, may at this moment, they be wants to fly into airborne replaces him also already late.

In their eyes has filled desperately, only has Ye Xinglan fierce moving sideways, dazzling sword light rumbles a big hole in the ground, then rapid all thrusts in companion the pit. Also has drawn Holy Spirit Douluo in stupor.

Tang Wulin must receive in exchange for the opportunity that lives with the Life price for them, can she make his painstaking care waste?

It is not the sad time, they must some people be able to live, makes the seed of Shrek Academy.

A chilliness, spreads in the Tang Wulin chest place, Tang Wulin has smiled, because he feels suddenly that own really grasped her.

Her body boiling hot, is bringing light maidenly fragrance as before. Her breath such as blue, slightly has rapid. Like that evening, after Sea God Fated Blind Date General Meeting, she lies down, in he cherishes the feeling to be the same.

„Gu Yue, I love you.” Tang Wulin twittering was saying, can before have the so real feeling at the point of death, he also has something not to be content?

„Fool, I also loves you.” A vocal cord familiar sounds/voices of endless complex emotion, is resounding in his ear.

Tang Wulin awakened suddenly, stares in a big way both eyes.

During the bosom, has human. He looks helplessly, that beautiful tender face at present.

„Na'er?” Tang Wulin delay, this look so familiar, but, she has as if grown up, has been short of the naivete, is more beautiful.

„Fool, I am your Gu Yue.” She opens red lips lightly, gently a kiss on his lip. But at this moment, endless ray of light, already their body Devour.

Tang Wulin sees finally, is the a pair of huge silver wing, behind draws from „Na'er”, covers their bodies completely. The terrifying explosive force, blooms suddenly, but he actually feels, besides fluctuation, is warm, warm bosom, familiar aura. That in the ear is reverberating familiar sounds/voices.

In the gulf, Shrek six strange are on the rise to look up to all, they see, only then eye-catching brilliance. silver light, just like barrier common cross piece in midair. In that fierce bellow, they as if see together form suddenly baseless appear(ance), has held in the arms Tang Wulin, then uses the back of own, blocks artillery shell that has dropped from the clouds.

The large explosion continued for dozens seconds gradually to stand still, the entire ground undercut three feet, wreaking havoc energy storm madness was reverberating in these thousand zhang (3.33 m) abyss.

------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#879: Eternal Dongfeng

Shrek in gulf six strange, the body was submerged by the soil had half fully, but most assault waves cannot arrive at the ground eventually.

Only the split vision of Ye Xinglan corner of the eye saw, final time that the explosion finished, one group of silver photospheres fly to shoot to go toward the distant place suddenly, without a trace of disappearance.

Had finished, these time seemed the conclusion of genuine. The terrifying large explosion disappears finally thoroughly.

Ye Xinglan dispelling soil, first jumped. Then draws in abundance other people.

„Hum!” The wail resounds, Xu Xiaoyan cannot endure patiently sadness in heart again, the tears flows copiously. Le Zhengyu hurries to hug into the own bosom her.

On the Ye Xinglan face full is the dignified color, the sinking sound track: „Now is not crying time, qualifications that we have not cried. Pavilion Master makes price with own Life, has brought the fresh opportunity to us. Wulin has blocked Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell attack with the body of own, we must go on living, for Shrek. We are the final seeds, we are Shrek Seven Monsters, we must shoulder are the heavy burdens of Shrek revenge. Comes with me.”

At the same time was saying, she turned around fast to run in the abyss wall direction.

Yuan En Yehui holds Ya Li in the bosom follows.

Xie Xie clenches the teeth, follows side her, some fat face distortions of Xu Lizhi, lip min closely.

Xu Xiaoyan wipes off the tears, under lead of Le Zhengyu, follows on the heels.

They cannot be sad, because they did not have the qualifications to go sadly. Meets with the disaster, they must first do now, goes on living. For own, goes on living for Shrek Academy and for Tang Sect.

The heart of Ye Xinglan possibly is how tranquil, how in her heart can not be painful, but at this moment, Tang Wulin to save companion Life and Death does not know that vanishes without the trace. She cannot let his in vain Sacrifice, she must bring companion to leave here first, first lives, is living, has the opportunity.

Disciplining of Devil Island, lets their willpower by far compared with many that the average person must strengthen, not genuine collapse in such pain. So long as they are also living, Shrek has the seed, has the possibility of revival.

......

„!” crushing that crystal Cup falling ground, falls.

Speaker complexion piece of pale white, blood-colored sheds instantaneously completely.

„Shrek City by two Kill the Gods Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell thorough Ruin? Does Shrek Academy, all extinguish?” His body not by Control is shivering.

Is the high-ranking, he should quietly be very right, may at this moment, he possibly calm?

Perishing of his very clear Shrek City means anything, although in his heart already hopes that can the Shrek City genuine control, actually never think wanted destruction inheritance of Twenty-thousand Years Continent first Academy.

Although Shrek Academy is the neutrality, but he without a doubt is also protecting Continent, is the mainstay of Douluo Continent genuine.

Let alone, the Shrek Academy students spread around the world. Shrek City perishes in should by Parliament strict protection two Kill the Gods, Parliament Duty-bound Responsibility. Not only his official career arrived at the end point, perhaps entire Federation Parliament a confusion. Even entire Continent is so.

„, Looks up to me immediately. Three Kill the Gods situations, go quickly!”

The speaker lets the own calm several points reluctantly, is issuing a series of orders, although he knows that this was unable to recall anything. Shrek City Ruin, will let him facing the entire Continent most terrifying pressure.

......

„Why? Why! You told me, why!” Heavenly Phoenix Douluo Leng Yaozhu both eyes are red, the a pair of white hands fall on front table, has a bang, that uses many alloy manufacture, the firm table changes into the powder pink / white extremely instantaneously.

After the table, is standing a middle-aged person , he look is tall handsome, bridge of the nose tall Ting, the eye is slightly small, the body is sending out a formidable deterrent force.

Looks at front eyes scarlet-red Leng Yaozhu, his brow tight wrinkle, „Yaozhu, you calmly. This matter was really too sudden, I did not have the clue. Actually how, but also after must undergo investigation, can be clear.”

„Eternal Dongfeng, you, when I am a three -year-old child? Doesn't your what person I know? Even if that Holy Spirit Cult eyes direct access to the highest authorities, can obtain Kill the Gods easily? Can so easily enters Shrek City so numerous Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell arrangements? Does not have you to support secretly, how to be possible? Are you, you!”

At the same time was saying, Leng Yaozhu lifts finger front this Present Generation Spirit Transferring Pagoda Pagoda Master, one generation of big energies, upbraid with Eternal Dongfeng that Sky Raising Douluo shares the honor said.

Eternal Dongfeng complexion sinks, „Yaozhu, you are my Spirit Transferring Pagoda Vice Pagoda Master, how can the arm elbow turn outward. Let alone, can this matter have the relations with me? You have forgotten, our Spirit Transferring Pagoda founder Ice Spirit Douluo Huo Yuhao once was that generation of Shrek Seven Monsters, our Spirit Transferring Pagoda was Shrek Academy not any conflict, my why strategic point they? Let alone, Spirit Transferring Pagoda is I can decide?”

Here, his expression has relaxed several points slightly, sudden that too „Yaozhu, this matter had, I now am also badly battered, am confused. Who can think that Holy Spirit Cult was unexpectedly bold to so the degree, initiative attack Shrek Academy and Tang Sect General Headquarters. Holy Spirit Cult was formidable, has the advantage to us? I can only be like grieve for like. Now must do, saves the sick and wounded, simultaneously seeks for the Holy Spirit Cult trail, All-Out to go to copes with them. I know that the Yun Ming death attacks to you very in a big way, I am also very regrettable. But, this matter, we must treat calmly.”

„Calm? How calm did you make me?” Leng Yaozhu aura obvious some are not steady, „Eternal Dongfeng, do not let me know that this matter is related with you, otherwise, even if puts together the life not to want, I must with your fight in which both sides perish.” Spoke these words, Leng Yaozhu leaves in a huff. Only leaves behind the stern-faced Spirit Transferring Pagoda host.

Gazes after Leng Yaozhu to depart, Eternal Dongfeng complexion ugly as if must drop the water leakage. His of course knows why Leng Yaozhu will question own. In the past, he once pursued the Leng Yaozhu many years, but Leng Yaozhu is actually persistent to that Yun Ming. Married Holy Spirit Douluo Ya Li to afterward Yun Ming, Leng Yaozhu has never forgotten to him as before, even lifelong has not married.

These years, Spirit Transferring Pagoda and Shrek Academy become estranged day after day, many are because they this intriguing relations.

„Pagoda Master.” A leaf of side gate opens, a look ordinary actually appears terse very middle-aged person half step walks, arrives at side Eternal Dongfeng.

„Situation how?”

„Shrek Academy all extinguishes, does not have one person to return alive. It is said that Present Generation Shrek Seven Monsters also in Academy. The Yun Ming final time from the position of broken Demi-God Gods, had the prestige of Gods temporarily, melted most parts to be divided two Kill the Gods destructive power. Letting Shrek City can have 50% people to live. But as the explosion center, Shrek Academy and Tang Sect General Headquarters, does not have the living witness. They even also supplemented 9th Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell to Shrek Academy that side, as sweeps clear finally. However, this Holy Spirit Cult is the loss is also serious.”

„To start two Kill the Gods, they have offered sacrifices about 20 Soul Douluo rank Evil Soul Master Life, several hundred Mid Rank Evil Soul Master. Yun Ming strikes at the point of death, broke their World Exterminating Skeleton, runs away besides the Holy Spirit Cult host, Holy Spirit Cult has eight Titled Douluo Fallen fully, it can be said that had a fracture.”

Eternal Dongfeng both eyes narrow the eyes, reveals the color of satisfaction unexpectedly, „was very good, Yun Ming has not really disappointed me. Even if this Holy Spirit Cult concealment Ten-thousand Years, the accumulation is so rich. Has planned Shrek Academy such in secret, has paid finally such huge price. Mutually wounded, is the best result. You get down, All-Out organized Foundation Pagoda Elite as scheduled, searched for the Holy Spirit Cult evil trails, once were discovered that executed summarily. Now at this time, must our standpoint clear performance. This Shrek City thorough Fallen, the Parliament aspect decides however cannot bear the pressure to announce dismisses, while this opportunity, we must fight for the Parliament seat.”

„The Pagoda Master illustrious name, answers multiple purpose.” In the middle-aged human eye reveals the admiration of having planting.

Eternal Dongfeng let somebody cool off or calm down looked at his one eyes, „what was answers multiple purpose? Our anything has not done. Regarding Shrek City Fallen, I also feel very regrettable.”

The middle-aged people are understanding immediately, hurry to nod, said: „Yes. We are also regrettable regarding the Shrek Academy bitter experience.”

„Um, goes. Waits a minute me to issue the Spirit Transferring Pagoda warrant for arrest, issues a warrant for arrest all Evil Soul Master. How you know should the concerted action. Remember, do not leave behind any tail. Meanwhile, making the human monitor the cold Vice Pagoda Master whereabouts, do not make her make the matter.”

„Yes.”

The middle-aged people retreated. Eternal Dongfeng arrives at the bedside, looks out out of the window the white clouds of piece by piece, both eyes is narrowing the eyes, looking pensive.

......

#880: Consciousness

Quite sore. The fierce ache makes Tang Wulin awaken.

He only thought that the own entire body as if likely has dispersed general, by his physical quality, such pain, besides when breaks through Golden Dragon King Seal, already few appear(ance).

Died? Did I die?

Is gradually sober with the consciousness, before he recalls gradually, matter that has.

He is really good to hope that this is a dream, when own opens the eye the dream can come soberly.

Yes! This certainly is a dream. Shrek Academy is so formidable, how possibly can by Ruin?

Difficult, he supports is opening eyes.

He discovered with amazement, own sees unexpectedly is eyeful green. Along with the restoration of vision, the sense of hearing also gradually returns. Tang Wulin discovered that own unexpectedly in the world that fills the insect warbler to be said. Here is......, forest?

The whole body severe pain transmits, is quite sore, am I also living?

Blinked, he struggles is wanting to move the body of own, actually the discovery cannot achieve. Inspiration of slowly, then with rapt attention in regards.

Tang Wulin discovered that own Soul Power vortex and bloodline vortex is very weak. Body meridians many breakages, internal organ(s) also already dislocation.

Such serious injury, if has changed the average person, perhaps already died. But he actually obviously feels that own gradually is recovering.

formidable the strength of bloodline walks randomly in within the body, is promoting meridians and internal organ(s) return position originally, each other connection.

Has not died, then, before these matters real? Why own in forest.

The thoughts of various doubts pace back and forth in his mind unceasingly, but Tang Wulin knows that now regarding own, what is most important is restores as soon as possible, only had the body to restore, can 11 open these doubts.

Woke, recovered speed naturally to speed up, under his Control, the first internal organ(s) homing that the strength of bloodline had at one's command, then quick repair meridians, simultaneously revolved Soul Power vortex in Dantian, absorb Heaven and Earth Primal Qi of outside is supplementing oneself.

Luckily, here Heaven and Earth Primal Qi is very sufficient, moreover his own is Plant System Battle Soul Master, fills the Plant place in this, cultivate gets up to be also easier.

Has not known long time, Tang Wulin meridians and internal organ(s) basic repair was similar, the aching feeling vanishes gradually. In Dantian, converged some Soul Power.

Opens both eyes, all of outside really look was clearer. What in the field of vision first sees is the lofty tree of shooting up to the sky.

Stands up from failure, he crawled from the ground.

Fortunately, own restoration ability also. However, at that time that mighty energy terrifying Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell shelled own not dead extremely unexpectedly, this was also considered as is a miracle.

Is thinking, suddenly, he saw in own side not far away, but also is lying down a person.

The white-clothed white skirt, lies down there is motionless.

Sees her flash, Tang Wulin felt obviously the heart of own leaked jumped a racket. The memory continues to reply, he has remembered person of final time that suddenly appear(ance) in own bosom.

Almost is three and makes two steps, he fast arrives at side that female, careful has stood up from failure her.

The familiar face, beautiful is tender face, not just the Na'er appearance? It seems, is probably bigger than Na'er two and three -year-old appearance.

Really, that unexpectedly real!

Tang Wulin hurries to feel her wrist [lineage/vein], the pulse is still beating, but is somewhat weak. Her clothes are also many breakages, many places have revealed the fair flesh.

But at this time Tang Wulin cannot attend to having other ideas, helped to hug her cautiously, poured into her within the body own Mysterious Heaven Skill Soul Power carefully.

meridians of her within the body as if all normal, is only aura is very weak. Holds her Tang Wulin to discover that her back clothes actually absolutely do not have, touch hand unexpectedly is the extremely creamy white and tender flesh.

At this moment, consciousness in his mind sobered completely, his clear remembering, at that time her suddenly appear(ance) in the own bosom. When own was shouting „Na'er I love you”, her appear(ance).

Her sounds/voices is that familiar, why may, she say that she is Gu Yue?

sounds/voices and aura are that familiar, is actually the Na'er look. time, Tang Wulin was also ignorant. He does not know this outcome completely what's the matter.

Yes, right, her aura Tang Wulin is very familiar.

Initially, Gu Yue just started after him studied, they frequently contact, grew up from the childhood together, in time, their close-range contact so was together numerous for several years, she in his mind was so important, Tang Wulin was impossible to remember incorrectly her flavor.

Her flavor is the light fragrance, maidenly fragrance gladdens the heart. But on Na'er is the light milk fragrance, is not same as Gu Yue flavor.

At this moment, how many year of young girls this seems Na'er is bigger than on, the body is actually the Gu Yue flavor, this what's the matter?

Suddenly, Tang Wulin has remembered anything, he hurries the neck place of young girl to the bosom to look, his clear remembering, under her neck, the collar bone above place, the oval birthmark, is very shallow, if were not he had paid attention desirably, was impossible to discover.

Really has! She is Gu Yue!

Tang Wulin was almost one had found that birthmark.

Other can be false, but birthmark actually possibly is not false! But her look what's the matter?

Tang Wulin careful has rubbed several by her cheek as well as the cheek, he has also studied the cosmetics technique, but, is contrary to what expects, the look as before, he could not find any cosmetics trace . Moreover, present Gu Yue, the hair is also silver!

Opens some of her eyelids slightly, eye pupil purple. silver-haired purple eyes, this clearly is the Na'er characteristics.

Tang Wulin also somewhat was then scared.

Gu Yue or Na'er any person comes back, he will be quite inevitably happy, is, at present this miss, actually seems Gu Yue and Na'er aggregate, this simply......

The overall feeling, looks like Gu Yue, but this look......, Does Gu Yue study the cosmetics technique that own could not completely understand to be inadequate? Also only had this possibility.

Is hugging her, time, Tang Wulin has mixed emotions. He cannot think absolutely that at that critical moment, she will arrive at side own. Moreover he still clearly remembers that she was own has blocked that sufficiently fatal terrifying attack with the body of own.

But, why they here? Where is this?

In any event, first revives her is most important.

His cautiously pours into Soul Power to Gu Yue within the body, but the body of Gu Yue actually likely is bottomless pit, how regardless of he pours into, without a trace that Soul Power can vanish, but Gu Yue own does not have any reaction.

Tang Wulin has remembered anything suddenly, he remembers that before Gu Yue appear(ance), the own chest place as if transmits a cool flavor.

His subconscious touching to the own front, just touched Gu Yue initially to leave his necklace. pendant is silver scales, he takes up to come to see scales. In the heart had guess immediately.

The scales that Gu Yue leaves behind, is when own will come across the Life and Death crisis will transmit her to own side?

If so, then, all explained passed, in the own bosom also inevitably was Gu Yue without doubt.

Why bother is your this? Tang Wulin embraces tightly several points of Gu Yue tender body, what if not the front presents is the Na'er appearance, perhaps he really will unable to bear kiss.

At least must wait for her to sober, the ascertaining situation said again.

Gu Yue had not awaked, pours into a while Soul Power, Tang Wulin somewhat cannot shoulder, can only own meditation restore Soul Power first. Although luckily, Gu Yue has not awaked, but aura is stable.

#881: Daddy

Restores Soul Power, pours into Soul Power for her, restores again, pours into again......

Thus and such and such after several times, Tang Wulin starts to feel gradually that Gu Yue aura became concentrates to be solid. This is the good phenomenon, showed that own injects the Soul Power procedure to have the effect.

Weather dark, night arrived.

Day gradually has shone, is a day of daybreak.

Tang Wulin is Gu Yue has back and forth poured into seven Soul Power, unceasing cultivate and injection, making him be utterly exhausted.

After eighth time pours into Soul Power, Tang Wulin feels that Gu Yue aura was basically normal, but the human has not awaked, is dragging the exhausted body, he re-enters the meditation condition.

Soul Power revolves, after having Soul Power vortex, his Soul Power restores speed obviously before be much quicker . After a double-hour, Soul Power restores, the exhausted feeling also reduced.

But when Tang Wulin opens both eyes, sees is actually the big eye of near at hand a pair of purple. Because is too sudden, frightened her to jump, nearly walked to miss the air/Qi. Within the body Soul Power vortex prompt reaction came luckily, tows Soul Power to return to normal.

„Frightens me to jump. You awake!” Looks at front Gu Yue, Tang Wulin pants for breath several talents to stabilize one after another lives in the mind, but quick was replaced by the joy.

Gu Yue animated sitting before him, the upper body also wears his clothes. Having no way that her original that coat damaged wanted, Tang Wulin closes one's eyes to her changes the own clothes. This process on said for the bystander insufficient.

Wears his clothes, somewhat is obviously spacious. Gu Yue sits in him opposite, winked the big eye. Her eye pupil is quite limpid, seems looks like two Wang Qingche Tanshui is common, is producing an inverted image the Tang Wulin appearance.

„Gu Yue?” Tang Wulin was probing calling out.

Gu Yue has smiled suddenly, she was beautiful, this smiles, Tang Wulin that immediately looks is in a daze.

„Daddy.”

„Puff passes!” Just sat Tang Wulin of straight body, directly toward side but actually.

His rapid sits sets out, dumbfounded looks at Gu Yue, „what did you and you call me?”

Because Gu Yue as if he throws down somewhat is also surprised, extends act , holds on his sleeve, the thumb of another hand squeezes in the own mouth to hold, twittering [say / way]: „Daddy.”

Tang Wulin both eyes turn, nearly faints, this what situation?

„Gu Yue, no joking. You......”

„Daddy......” Gu Yue also called one, is only this summon actually obviously somewhat suffering from injustice flavor, in the a pair of attractive purple big eye, the instantaneous mist fills the air, as if the next quarter must burst into tears.

This......

How this saw that likely is not disguises!

Tang Wulin has rubbed the brow of own, „do not cry and not cry. You make me static, I think.”

Gu Yue is flat the mouth, looks at Tang Wulin, both hands grabs his sleeves to swing swung, „Daddy, I am hungry.”

Shrek Academy perishes, in the Tang Wulin original heart has filled sorrowfully, but makes Gu Yue these Daddy shout that at this time, he even continually sorrowfully temporarily forgot.

„Good, I make the point to eat to you.” Tang Wulin has stabilized the own mind reluctantly, hurries to say.

He is bringing storage ring, but as a glutton, in his storage ring will not always lack food.

Takes out some dry rations to give Gu Yue, Gu Yue receives on the big mouth and big mouth has eaten. However, her expression obvious some are unsatisfied, eats, while was mumbling, „was not delicious, is not delicious.”

Tang Wulin is also helpless, this dry rations possibly are too how delicious!

Looks that Gu Yue are obviously more than before does not know many various vivid facial expressions, he awakens gradually.

Was she loses recalls? But, lost had recalled why she does want to manage me to call Daddy?

„Gu Yue, why did you call me Daddy?” Tang Wulin is probing asking.

Gu Yue somewhat at a loss visits him, „first sees, is, Daddy.” Her sounds/voices speaks in an infantile tone of voice, even somewhat did not enunciate clear. But said very earnestly.

first does see is Daddy? Isn't this rule of animal kingdom?

Facing having Na'er look Gu Yue, he has a lot of questions, at this time cannot ask.

Gu Yue has eaten the dry rations, seemed full, but not too satisfactory appearance, „Daddy, was not delicious. I want to eat delicious.”

„Good, I try to find the solution.” The Tang Wulin forced smile said.

Gu Yue immediately excited is hugging his arm, the head by his shoulder, full is the appearance of dependence.

All around the Tang Wulin standing body, has the energy to pay attention at this time. This is big forest of cover, cannot look at the feeling of boundary greatly. In the ground does not have the artificial opening up wasteland trace, everywhere is tall Guo the vegetation. Life aura is very rich, but indistinct, he can also feel some dangerous feelings.

Actually is this where?

If all are not the dreams, at that time own should be Gu Yue together by the High Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell bang, then woke on bewildered appear(ance) in this place.

Ok, walks one step to look at one step, since is forest, always should be able to walk to be right.

Thinks of here, Tang Wulin has patted the hand of Gu Yue, is holding her hand, walks toward forest.

The left hand draws Gu Yue, the right hand is sweeping away the opening with Golden Dragon Spear in front. Insufficient, quick Tang Wulin discovered that Golden Dragon Spear is unnecessary.

Strange saying that in this big forest, surroundings all vegetation as if has felt the warm feelings to him, everywhere one visit, these grass, Vine! Will separate unexpectedly voluntarily, gives him the making way circuit. Walks to be smooth.

This outcome what's the matter? Although own Martial Soul two times awaken became Blue Silver Emperor, before can, as if not so obvious.

Because of own Fifth Soul Ring? That Child of Nature?

Thinks of here, Tang Wulin stops the footsteps, feels surroundings nature aura with rapt attention.

Really, he can clear from numerous Plant, feels very kind feeling. As if they to him were asking that seems.

If here cultivate, will be certainly twice the result with half the effort.

What a pity, this time Tang Wulin point wants the cultivate thought not to have, he only wants quickly to exit, examines the Shrek City situation, seeks for the companion trail, then cures Gu Yue, clarifies her situation.

Meets the big change suddenly, he now very somewhat feeling of mind completely exhausted.

Thinks of here, he turns head to have a look to follow in Gu Yue, has her, he felt better. If only a own person, perhaps will be only more painful.

„Daddy.” Gu Yue sees him to look to own, immediately smiles to him sweetly.

A [say / way] of Tang Wulin face forced smile: „Can do not call me Daddy, do you know that you one such called me, I had goose flesh. This is really......”

Gu Yue digs the mouth immediately, in beautiful pupil tears glistening, suffering from injustice [say / way]: „Didn't Daddy want me?”

„I......”

Tang Wulin is helpless, „, has not had. of course wanted you, clever, you are willing to call to call.”

„Daddy, hugs.” Gu Yue stretches out the arms to Tang Wulin.

Tang Wulin speechless, Gu Yue excitedly has actually swooped, looks like eight claw fish is ordinary, hangs on him.

A silver long hair flies upwards, in mouth exudes the euphonious laughter.

Tang Wulin but, can only be hand cradling her outstanding buttocks, Gu Yue also in he cherishes rubbing to rub, Tang Wulin this that rubs called a pent-up anger ascension also to have no alternative.

The Gu Yue both arms are hugging the neck of Tang Wulin, the head by his shoulder, has filled the dependent flavor.

But in the Tang Wulin heart changes into the tender feelings, gently is stroking her long hair, has not made her get down, such is holding her, at the same time stand forth. Gu Yue this body weight, for him of course was not anything.

-----------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#882: Scarlet Fire Monkey King

What may make Tang Wulin not think, this, Gu Yue depends on him, when he wants to let she got down the time, she said that anything is not willing, finally, by hugging to be turned into the back grinningly, Gu Yue by him to be carried, went to the forest deep place line.

„I owe you really!” Tang Wulin looks to hang in the own front a pair of arm, cannot bear somewhat funny saying.

Gu Yue collects, has kissed one on his face, „Daddy, I like you.”

Tang Wulin has gawked, will speak, suddenly, in the heart warning sign(s) raises suddenly, subconscious vertical leapt to jump.

tan Shadow dodges to pass from his together, if he also in formerly position, definitely by its hit.

„Who!” Tang Wulin gives a loud shout. But that attacks his direction, has not actually seen any trail.

Both eyes narrow the eyes, on Tang Wulin bursts out cold aura immediately, Blue Silver Grass Vine swarm from the under foot, toward spreads in all directions. Here is forest, for him, simply is his main battlefield.

Strange appear(ance), was startled including Tang Wulin own, after his Blue Silver Grass drills into the ground, immediately felt the own sensation spreads suddenly outward.

He has achieved Spirit Abyss Realm Spiritual Strength to have strong sensation strength, the coverage scope sufficiently over thousand zhang (3.33 m). But that is only the general sensation in thought that but at this moment, when his Blue Silver Grass integrates this piece of forest, he actually discovered that own as if opened a pair of God's Eye, Spiritual Strength can the sensation to the wide scope, all within this range, clear and three-dimensional presents in his mind.

Left front 600 meters away, a personal appearance is gigantic, passes the length of body to have the huge form of brown-red hair, just like the star pill caper is ordinary, High-speed moves unceasingly, but the path of migration, seems centered on him and Gu Yue.

Gu Yue somewhat curious looks at surroundings, appeared from the Tang Wulin shoulder place.

Can see the future, deals naturally to be much easier.

That impressively is Scarlet Fire Monkey, but, this and Scarlet Fire Monkey in Tang Wulin impression is completely different.

In him Soul Beast during the understanding, Scarlet Fire Monkey can be considered as on is low rank Soul Beast, majority are cultivates ten years to Hundred Year is, Hundred Year was considered as on is rare. Even if Hundred Year class Scarlet Fire Monkey, attack is also unitary, is quick except for speed, has beside strong activity ability in forest, does not have what extraordinary place.

But this only Scarlet Fire Monkey is actually entirely different, its body type big ten times has continued compared with normal Scarlet Fire Monkey, the height has exceeded about seven meters, the hair of brown-red is also sending all over the body out the light golden-colored flowing light in the march process, what is most surprising, on its forehead, third eye existence. That is golden-colored sets upright pupil, glittering the monster different brilliance, is looking out the Tang Wulin direction, the pupil light congealing reality, although is away from so numerous woods, but Tang Wulin actually as before can feel that this only sets upright the pupil as if to see own.

Variation? Without doubt, this is Variation Soul Beast. After Tang Wulin sees him, when heart regarding this place also had some suspicions.

Soul Beast has bordered on to exterminate on Douluo Continent! Before then, he contacts Soul Beast most places to have one, that is, Spirit Transferring Pagoda Control Spirit Raising Platform. Imitation once Star Dou Forest Spirit Raising Platform. Was own actually brought in Spirit Raising Platform by Gu Yue inadequate? This really has the possibility, by Gu Yue in the Spirit Transferring Pagoda status, bringing own to enter is not difficulties.

Spirit Raising Platform?

In he is surprised time, that only Variation Scarlet Fire Monkey King rapidly flushed in their directions. As if was feels Tang Wulin to his observation, Scarlet Fire Monkey King is only the personal appearance dodges, fled high to a big tree above, step on of both feet on the big tree, just like the flaming-red advantage arrow, dashed to together, but.

Tang Wulin both eyes narrow the eyes, in eye pupil glittering bone-chilling cold cold brightness. Shrek Academy brings forth the disaster suddenly, in his heart is despondent. Suddenly has enemy appear(ance), his innermost feelings are constraining mood, immediately just like blowout general eruption.

„Gu Yue, hold me tight.” Tang Wulin drinks one lowly.

Gu Yue hurries to embrace tightly his neck, the a pair of longleg also tight disturbance in his waist, Tang Wulin own Qi and Blood fluctuation suddenly greatly Sheng, the both arms launch to the body, a pair of Golden Dragon Claw simultaneously releases.

After his within the body completes two circulation vortex, Tang Wulin discovered that own strength of Martial Soul and bloodline could simultaneously existence, completely not need to cut, but can really a genuine fight.

Innumerable Blue Silver Emperor swarm from the ground, was together ordinary just like blue silver forest, has blocked the Scarlet Fire Monkey King way.

That Scarlet Fire Monkey King is quite maneating, both arms open, the whole body is burning the [gold/metal] red roaring flame, hit actually to Blue Silver Emperor.

Blue Silver Emperor after is Plant System Martial Soul, was swung in abundance under its hit, is having the unprecedented imposing manner, it arrived in front of Tang Wulin.

Has not thrown directly, that Scarlet Fire Monkey King armpit are suddenly many a pair of wing, making it should under the potential of throwing from the sky to stop.

Tactic? This is Soul Beast unexpectedly intelligent in this way?

Do not despise this instantaneous stop, lets the match completely miscalculation sufficiently its attack path, at the same time, its that third eye has shone. The powerful spiritual fluctuation comes just like tide immediately generally, is not the direct collision, but is one type the spiritual pressure that from transmits in all directions, is centered on the body of Tang Wulin.

„Raising” Tang Wulin raises head to roar, huge Golden-colored Dragon Head covers the whole body, impressively Golden Dragon Roars.

Scarlet Fire Monkey King body in airborne one stiff, its powerful spiritual assault in Golden Dragon Roars is bringing under Spiritual Strength fluctuation immediately the counter- volume.

But also at this moment, in its golden-colored angry look, together [gold/metal] lightning flash, but, having the blazing high temperature almost to pass through the air of surroundings distortion, arrived at the Tang Wulin front instantaneously.

Meanwhile, under his Innate Body is also flies high throws, a pair of Sharp Claws stretches out, simultaneously covers toward Tang Wulin under.

Tang Wulin right hand Golden Dragon Claw leaves, keeps off before the own body outrageously, has blocked that [say / way] dropping from the clouds rays. The blazing feeling transmits instantaneously, formidable energy assault made the strength that tyrannical Tang Wulin body shake shaking unexpectedly.

That Scarlet Fire Monkey King also here flies high, but, a pair of Sharp Claws grasps from the both sides to Tang Wulin.

„Go away!” Tang Wulin shouted angrily, Golden Dragon Ascends The Heavens! Huge Golden Dragon raises from the under foot, collides with that Scarlet Fire Monkey King together.

In the ear-piercing fulmination sound, forest of surroundings big piece falls outward. Scarlet Fire Monkey King also hit flying high flies, retreat that but Tang Wulin staggers unexpectedly two steps came to a stop.

Scarlet Fire Monkey King distant falling above a bough of big tree, in the eye is revealing the surprised uncertain color. Obviously somewhat was frightened by Tang Wulin formidable attack.

Tang Wulin own manic has also restrained several points, this only Scarlet Fire Monkey King unexpectedly is unexpected hard to deal with, not only attack is tyrannical, but also has Spiritual Strength. Meanwhile, its own defense strength also very formidable, own Golden Dragon Ascends The Heavens and its front impact cannot injure to arrive at it unexpectedly, but compels to draw back it, this is not very simple.

Ten-thousand Years Soul Beast! Without a doubt, this is Ten-thousand Years Soul Beast, is not ordinary, is Variation Ten-thousand Years Soul Beast.

The takes a deep breath tone, Tang Wulin returned to normal the own state of mind, he knows that facing such match, own cannot make the mood affect this fight.

Both eyes narrow the eyes, Tang Wulin is staring at Scarlet Fire Monkey King, own imposing manner starts to continue to increase. He has not used Battle Armor, that is the later method. Unless it is absolutely essential he will not start easily.

If this is Spirit Raising Platform, is Intermediate Spirit Raising Platform or is Advanced Spirit Raising Platform in legend is at least right. Otherwise, own will not face such formidable Soul Beast. Preserved strength as far as possible, to face in the future momentarily possible appear(ance) Elite.

Scarlet Fire Monkey King a pair of eye pupil transferred extension, suddenly, its personal appearance dodges, no longer plunges Tang Wulin, but goes toward the distant place rapid escape. Such ran away unexpectedly.

Tang Wulin has gawked, without doubt, this Scarlet Fire Monkey King is quite only intelligent, after discovering own is not good to cope, chooses unexpectedly escapes immediately.

Tang Wulin own also relaxed, he understands that wants to defeat this only Scarlet Fire Monkey King, own must All-Out to go to is good. Ten-thousand Years Variation Soul Beast, side own also does not have the helper, wants to cope is not that easy.

„Daddy.” The summon sound that the ear hears made fighting intent that Tang Wulin surged upward release immediately. His corners of the mouth twitched, the racket the thigh of Gu Yue, „has been all right, you get down.”

„Good.” Gu Yue some are not willing gets down from Tang Wulin, the appearance that has a lingering fear, „Daddy, a moment ago that was anything! Quite fearful.”

------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#883: It is not good!

Tang Wulin looks at her speechless, in his mind, Gu Yue strength continuously not under him, even be stronger than him, but present she, actually completely turned into the child who need other people have protected.

„All right, I will protect your.” Tang Wulin traces her long hair, Gu Yue has actually taken advantage of opportunity by entering him cherishes, a face satisfied [say / way]: „Daddy was best.”

Tang Wulin palm one stiff, if after this, she wakes, how own must face her!

Sighed one darkly, calmed down, starts to assess the surroundings situation.

Disciplining of Devil Island, making him learn, regardless of as far as possible achieved in the how difficult situation calmly. Even if itself mood fluctuation is huge, must make own calm down in shortest time. Because only has maintains calm, can better going facing all difficult positions.

Calms down, Tang Wulin is feeling surroundings all, is carrying also on the earnest judgment to surroundings all.

Without a doubt, this is piece of Primitive Forest, had formerly the judgment of Spirit Raising Platform, now he more looked that more thought here likely is Star Dou Forest that in Spirit Raising Platform simulates. Only different is, here Plant Spirit Transferring Pagoda Spirit Raising Platform in Plant be more luxuriant than he has experienced, seems the age is also remote.

He has given a own supposition. Assuming that this in Spirit Raising Platform, then, is not Intermediate Spirit Raising Platform. Before Intermediate Spirit Raising Platform him, had gone, if so, then, in Intermediate Spirit Raising Platform, Plant not such cover . Moreover, should also not such easily bump into so formidable, the strength is not inferior under own formidable Soul Beast.

According to ability that Scarlet Fire Monkey King showed a moment ago, wants to defeat it, perhaps Tang Wulin must put on Battle Armor to achieve.

Do not look that his present Soul Power cultivates to have 55th Rank, may be general Six Rings Elite is not his match, in addition Battle Armor and Golden Dragon Spear these amplifications, Tang Wulin now in Soul Master was also considered as on is a young master.

So, that Scarlet Fire Monkey King fully has Twenty-thousand Years to cultivate is Soul Beast stage.

Advanced Spirit Raising Platform? Regarding that existence, he has not understood. Listens to Gu Yue to raise indistinctly, Advanced Spirit Raising Platform, is Spirit Transferring Pagoda most Nucleus resources.

However, some foundation judge him to have, for example, is the formidable Soul Beast inhabit region, the Soul Beast quantity are less. Because each formidable Soul Beast will have the own territory, does not allow other people to encroach. Clearly, their present location place, should be that Scarlet Fire Monkey King territory.

But enters the next stretch of territory, may meet other Soul Beast.

However, now the most essential issue is, how here exits!

If traditional Spirit Raising Platform, has special exits to equip, wants to leave only needs to press the button. Dies at the Spirit Raising Platform civil war, will leave, but on spiritual will withstand some assault.

The issue that now faces is, on them does not have the button that type can leave, cannot exit through normal way (of life). But uses is the method good?

Tang Wulin does not know, moreover this does not have the means to try, what to do died really?

Moreover, Tang Wulin had already heard, existence of Spirit Raising Platform most peak, is the real world, if own now is Gu Yue in that place, once died, was genuine died.

Therefore, whatever, he needs to come facing to be good with most discrete way (of life).

Thinks that these, he instead not too eagerly went forward clearly. This piece of Domain is the Scarlet Fire Monkey King domain, at least this Scarlet Fire Monkey King is he now can contend, on the other hand here also safe. Moreover he has similar God's Eye ability to observe surroundings when necessary, has any danger also to be able the quick discovery. Would rather here first recuperation, then also carefully distinguished under one to say again.

If is really in that legend highest stage Spirit Raising Platform, then, that place likely is also existence Star Dou Forest Core Area, even is the greatly ominous place. May encounter the Hundred-thousand Years Soul Beast place!

If rashly thorough, only needs to meet Hundred-thousand Years Soul Beast, he and Gu Yue ended.

If is really that place, so long as other source is correct to the choice, gradually is separated from Nucleus, walks, should be able to walk is right.

The dependence eye, Tang Wulin of course is impossible to see that which direction own should in walk. May pass Transformation that beforehand Blue Silver Emperor brings, he can actually ask that whom asked? Plant, surroundings all Plant, they understand this world compared with him by far.

Thinks of here, Tang Wulin said to Gu Yue: „Gu Yue, I want meditation a while, seeks direction that can leave, side me, do not walk away.”

„.” Gu Yue complied with one obediently.

Looks at such Gu Yue, Tang Wulin is out of sorts. In his mind, Gu Yue is independent, moreover always worried miss. Among them, has a special closeness throughout. Their sentiments have been for many years influence subtly to train.

This time Gu Yue, already not in Gu Yue like his mind. But he somewhat hopes, if Gu Yue is such naive Wuxie (Innocence), can much less worries. Standing putting oneself in another's place considered in the Gu Yue angle that her departure, own no doubt was very initially painful, so long as she is genuine loves own, the pain in her innermost feelings, only meets wins in own.

Only different is, she knows how can find own, but own throughout is actually not able to find her.

This time she came back, said that anything cannot make her leave again. of course, that wanted him to prove the first guess of own, this has Na'er appearance her at present, was own Gu Yue is really good. Otherwise, even if he wants with her intimate, actually does not dare.

Sits cross-legged to sit, Tang Wulin concentrates spiritual, spiritual thinks of the feeling to release following Blue Silver Emperor outward, with surroundings Plant fuses gradually in together, gradually communication.

Plant before has not opened Spirit Wisdom, simple life form, they look like metal(s) when completing Spirit Refinement are the same, have Life not to have Wisdom.

Once opens Spirit Wisdom, becomes Plant System Soul Beast, that will be likely more formidable than ordinary Soul Beast. Just, the Plant System Soul Beast quantity was really too few, too rare.

However, Tang Wulin has his means that he does not need to relate on Gaining Spirit Wisdom Plant, but only needs them to tell own, which direction danger, which direction was safely enough.

Quick, he got answer!

The ordinary Plant too big feedback in ground, has not appeared completely ignorants, but these big trees transmitted to his information had the explicit direction. In these Plant give in his sensation, a direction is similar to the abyss, another direction is actually positive light flatters. Without a doubt, the answer had.

Some such discovery, Tang Wulin was very immediately joyful, opens eyes, rises with a spring from the ground.

But what makes him terrified one startled is, Gu Yue not in side.

Subconscious hurrying releases Spiritual Strength, seeks through the God angle of view. Fortunately, she goes out not far, is away from him about 300 meters place. Then lowers the head, smiled is looking for anything in the grove, in her left hand, has grabbed a colorful wild flower, seems the in high spirit appearance.

Her happy appearance makes Tang Wulin one feel sad, as the Shrek Academy student, they already did not have the person of same age pleasure. Yes! Doesn't the flower season young girl, who like tweed?

In this time, suddenly, in his God angle of view, two forms simultaneously appear(ance), is swooping to come in his direction, another, is directly soars Gu Yue to go impressively.

These two form appear(ance) is towering, moreover speed incredibly fast is incomparable, not having the least bit to stop.

It is not good!

#884: Divine Dragon reappears

In the Tang Wulin heart cries, immediately is similar to arrow dart, flies to shoot to go in the Gu Yue direction.

Lost the memory, just like child Gu Yue now that frail, Tang Wulin the whole body fine hair explodes at this time stands, speed promoted summit instantaneously, in the meantime, Blue Silver Emperor already by compared with he quicker speed suddenly to launch. Directly soars Gu Yue to go.

Plunges the Tang Wulin direction, impressively Scarlet Fire Monkey King, but plunges Gu Yue that form, is actually one all over the body presents is bluish-green birds Soul Beast, its speed was really too quick, looked like emerald green arrow dart, just on Bind Gu Yue waist while Tang Wulin Blue Silver Emperor, it arrived in front of Gu Yue, the sharp proboscis, directly soared the Gu Yue forehead point to go.

Emerald Demon Bird! Among the Tang Wulin moment identified this Soul Beast name. Also because just identified, the fear in his heart promotes Peak.

Emerald Demon Bird is in birds Soul Beast one of the cruelest centralism, their growth, the complete dependence slurps various life form brain matter. Soul Beast or Humanity, are their goals, Emerald Demon Bird especially like Humanity brain matter. This Soul Beast moves, if the lightning, the rapidness of speed, is among the best in entire Soul Beast. Saves the world quantity not to be many.

Emerald Demon Bird had caused a giant disaster in ancient era, that time they were Colony-Type Soul Beast, piece of Emerald Demon Bird has flown, all life form were the forehead has the hole, brain matter did not have, at that time what kind terrifying scene!

Afterward Soul Beast world appear(ance) one time had exterminated the motion of Emerald Demon Bird voluntarily, under the leadership of several Soul Beast King, has killed this kind of Soul Beast almost, extreme rareness that can escape by luck. Then made threat of Emerald Demon Bird to Continent life form reduce, even if were appear(ance), was only occasionally, moreover unusual being careful.

On the other hand, Humanity does not calculate regarding the understanding of Emerald Demon Bird specially, but has the record in some old books. Because Emerald Demon Bird, when harms Continent, is in Soul Beast ruler Continent that age.

In the past, it is said Emerald Demon Bird King had slurped True Dragon brain matter, evolved unceasingly, became that time most terrifying slaughtering.

Also was being killed because of True Dragon, that age ruler Continent Dragon Clan, concentrates strength, launched the retaliation of madness to slaughter to Emerald Demon Bird one group, thus their thorough Ruin.

When at this moment, Tang Wulin sees Emerald Demon Bird appear(ance), the breath of whole person as if must stop.

Once were pierced the Gu Yue forehead by this fellow, even if were ten Gu Yue cannot live. Moreover its speed is such rapidness.

Tang Wulin is almost puts together completely All-Out backward to entrain own Blue Silver Emperor, simultaneously a claw without hesitation sends out, Golden Dragon Solitude Destruction Claws erupts, racket before the Gu Yue body.

The body of that Emerald Demon Bird is not too only big, pair of wings launches to have more than half meter, height ruler. green-blue, the proboscis is similar to the transparent syringe is all over the body more common. The rapidness of its speed, radically eyes cannot take it all.

Tang Wulin Golden Dragon Solitude Destruction Claws was prompt, Gu Yue was also being pulled retreat by him, but that Emerald Demon Bird actually fiercely in airborne came two acceleration, as if there is green-blue tail flame behind to emit from it, promoting his body almost to be similar to the lightning is ordinary, arrived in front of Gu Yue directly, proboscis directly on point in Gu Yue forehead.

„” Tang Wulin did not call out pitifully, in an instant, blood of his whole person seemed lit.

Gu Yue eyes is vacant, after body by, draws at the same time, but also does not understand completely had anything, but helplessly looks that Emerald Demon Bird proboscis arrived at her at present.

The Tang Wulin pain roared, Scarlet Fire Monkey King that the Emerald Demon Bird ice-cold look, rear area has raided. In an instant, as if entire world has framed, but next flickers, Tang Wulin and Gu Yue destiny as if has been doomed.

Tang Wulin only thinks to be terror-stricken at this time, if Gu Yue such dies under the Emerald Demon Bird proboscis, he forever will not forgive own. What he rather was slurped brain matter is own, does not want Gu Yue to receive a wee bit injuries.

But the strength of bloodline also at this moment, strange appear(ance), Tang Wulin to rush has seethed with excitement made his body surroundings take shape [gold/metal] red light fog, but this light fog on that piece of Gu Yue by his neck was given his silver scales fierce absorb to get up suddenly.

surroundings spatial as if really has stagnated, even if speed such rapidness, the proboscis were arrived at Emerald Demon Bird of Gu Yue forehead, appear(ance) short stagnation.

But the next quarter, the body of Gu Yue and Tang Wulin was actually illusory.

On Tang Wulin bursts out dazzling golden light (Jin Guang), but on Gu Yue was bursts out dazzling silver light, money bi-color has handed over to echo. In the Tang Wulin wrist that may colored crystal also shines radiant ray of light. The next quarter, golden-colored and silver, close up suddenly, instantaneous fusion.

Radiant seven-colored luster blooms suddenly. The body of Emerald Demon Bird and Scarlet Fire Monkey King simultaneously can move. Emerald Demon Bird is ordinary just like a bluish-green meteor, pricks in that seven-colored ray of light instantaneously.

But, with „biting” a resounding, its not big body was rebounded immediately. But another side Scarlet Fire Monkey King forcefully from the sky transformed the direction, fell on nearby big tree, surprised uncertain looks seven-colored ray of light that front burst out suddenly.

Not only it strength, what is more important has Wisdom that many Soul Beast do not have, most is good at making use of favorable conditions and avoid unfavorable conditions. This time looks for Emerald Demon Bird to take helper, this thinks absolutely safe. Has not actually thought of suddenly appear(ance) such Transformation.

But this time Tang Wulin only thought that bloodline energy vortex of own chest place revolved suddenly unprecedented terrifying speed, own whole body bloodline also in appear(ance) strange Transformation.

Huge energy flows in backward just like the rivers and streams floods into within the body generally, he only thought that the own whole person is inflating, terrifying energy makes him unable to bear face upward to send out resonant dragon roar.

Divine Dragon Transformation, in his consciousness very clear own is completing Divine Dragon Transformation with Gu Yue. This is not first was inferior, may in the passing Divine Dragon Transformation process, be Gu Yue carries on as the leadership, he stimulates to movement Divine Dragon Transformation energy to fight at most.

But this time is different, Divine Dragon Transformation seems inspires by him, that incomparably huge energy, so tyrannical physical quality unexpectedly somewhat cannot support by him now, energy that the Gu Yue place transmits, looks like flushes air the ball to blow generally him. Tang Wulin within the body meridians started somewhat unable to withstand, but this as if just started to resemble.

„” dragon roar turned into pitiful yell. Even if when withstanding Golden Dragon King Seal to shatter, Tang Wulin had not felt the death was away from own such near, he has not thought that met appear(ance) such situation unexpectedly.

But also while this pitiful yell resounds, Tang Wulin felt obviously emerges the energy fierce stop of own within the body, his consciousness also returned to normal.

seven colors scales covers the whole body, his body also inflated had five meters high fully, when with former and Gu Yue Divine Dragon Transformation had certain difference, as if their this Martial Soul Fusion Technique have completed evolution.

Tang Wulin remembers clearly that Gu Yue had said that their Divine Dragon Transformation initially were first that carried on changes, Divine Dragon initially awoke. Then, at this time was second changed inadequate?

Back, the huge Seven-colored Dragon wing opens, Tang Wulin only thinks all attribute energy members in trim forest in madness comes toward own to rush, not only emerges the own body, but also energy of big piece said in own body surroundings take shape that momentarily can be transferred by own.

Unprecedented strength feeling, in mind suddenly were many anything, as if belonged to Gu Yue strength also to be able by him to be transferred.

------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#885: Crush double beast

Scarlet Fire Monkey King sees Tang Wulin after Transformation, particularly after listening to him formerly that dragon roar, turns around runs. Changes into together [gold/metal] red Light and Shadow, in an instant already beyond kilometer.

Another side Emerald Demon Bird speed compares it to be quicker. Since the tribal group was extinguished, these surviving many Emerald Demon Bird are good at protecting own, saw that front match suddenly aura becomes so formidable, when at this time doesn't run treats?

Runs?

Tang Wulin has despised this pair of Soul Beast, in just, them almost let the person who he lost most loved!

The right hand wields in the Emerald Demon Bird direction void, the air has stagnated suddenly, terrifying energy madness surges. Emerald Demon Bird speed like lightning, looked like drills into glue water to be ordinary suddenly, is struggling forwarding, but speed actually did not know slowly many times.

A Tang Wulin back Seven-colored Dragon wing racket, the next quarter, the human arrived in front of Emerald Demon Bird, the Seven-colored Dragon claw lays out, direct racket to the body of Emerald Demon Bird.

That Emerald Demon Bird was also, the body blue light put suddenly greatly, blooms bluish-green ring of light, the Seven-colored Dragon claw strikes on ring of light, immediately burst out the ear-piercing fulmination sound. bluish-green ring of light to shatter, but the Seven-colored Dragon claw of Tang Wulin was shot unexpectedly.

Must know that in the Divine Dragon Transformation condition, Tang Wulin this time cultivation to at least promote three big stage, in other words, present he, has been equal to Soul Douluo level Elite, moreover when the power of strength of bloodline, compared with alone is his Golden Dragon King bloodline does not know terrifying many times.

This Emerald Demon Bird is really out of the ordinary, can block own to strike unexpectedly.

But also in next quarter, in Tang Wulin that Seven-colored Dragon claw palm, actually ripples one group of seven-colored vortex.

That seven-colored vortex appear(ance) instant, Emerald Demon Bird bluish-green ray of light instantaneous large scale weaken, it is also calls out in grief one, directly was attracted to fly toward the Tang Wulin dragon claw place that absorbs.

Element Peeling!

This without doubt from Gu Yue ability, Emerald Demon Bird is Wind Attribute Soul Beast, is due to the promotion of wind, it can achieve that terrifying High-speed.

speed quick Soul Beast has two species generally, either is Spatial Attribute, either is Wind Attribute. Spatial Attribute excels at explosive nature increases speed, ever changing. But Wind Attribute Soul Beast had been inferior in fields, but their speed linearity are also more lasting. Excels at various flying Transformation.

But wind or spatial, in front of Element Peeling, their stripped, not only surroundings spatial Element(s), in the Divine Dragon Transformation condition, the Element Peeling might is strips directly Element(s) energy that their own has.

Lost the Wind Element in addition to hold, the Emerald Demon Bird strength drop significantly suddenly.

Saw that it must fall into the Tang Wulin palm. But that Emerald Demon Bird turns head suddenly, the a pair of eye pupil turned into scarlet-red completely, the next quarter, its deep green body turned suddenly fiery red, wind and fire Dual Attributes?

After flaming-red maintains instantaneous, turns into green-blue. All these are among the moment occur. But Tang Wulin actually obviously feels that own Element Peeling attracted unexpectedly is motionless it.

wind and fire Dual Attributes? Resists Element Peeling with the aid of own within the body Flame Vortex. Although this can only continue very short time, actually also gave this only Emerald Demon Bird to catch the opportunity of going on living.

pair of wings All-Out flaps, Emerald Demon Bird speed increases suddenly, the proboscis is becomes slender, looks like the Humanity person sword unites general, suddenly toward front suddenly to launch. In that flash that it increases speed, bursts out intense thundering because of the breakthrough sonic barrier unexpectedly, obviously it has regarding the escape at this moment rigid how.

This is Tang Wulin has seen speed quickest Soul Beast, is, at this moment, in any event, him cannot make it run away.

Some this kind of powerful enemy links raise in the side, its speed such rapidness, this time can escape the disaster, next time? Once Gu Yue is far from own, was attacked by it, must make own cherish hatred.

Therefore, instant, the left hand of Tang Wulin when that Emerald Demon Bird increases speed once more has struck in airborne.

In an instant, spatial caves, surroundings Plant stagnates obviously, but airborne instantaneous appear(ance) black hole.

Under Tang Wulin at this time in the Divine Dragon Transformation in addition holds, regarding energy Control is as wonderful as summit, that diameter one meter black hole, just covers in which Emerald Demon Bird. speed of its breakthrough sonic barrier, entrains in this terrifying, has stopped instantaneously.

Also is this stop, Dark Gold Fearful Claw of Tang Wulin right hand has patted.

Exaggerated seven colors Dark Gold Fearful Claw, the coverage scope has been being the terrifying 50 meters. Five 50 meters dark [gold/metal] Weigu, seven-colored drop from the clouds for the light blade edge of glow, as if to destroy the heavens and exterminate the land is ordinary, struck against the ground it directly.

„Bang” the body of Emerald Demon Bird is almost the tumbling whereabouts place, the emerald-green feather from the sky disperses, what makes Tang Wulin surprised is, this is to depend upon speed Soul Beast obviously, the body intensity unexpectedly is such formidable. Under Divine Dragon Transformation Dark Gold Fearful Claw that in this All-Out to go, unexpectedly has not died. Struck has fainted, the body has left behind a scar, actually sees the bone, is not fatal.

Cannot attend to makes up to it, the Tang Wulin right hand wields, grasps into Emerald Demon Bird the palm. Simultaneously swings the body in a flash, body silver light dodges, next already beyond kilometer, after so several times, front scarlet-red form already at present.

„Gives me to get down!” Drinks in the sound coldly, the Tang Wulin left hand wields like lightning, [gold/metal] instantaneous flash goes together, airborne Scarlet Fire Monkey King is screaming one in High-speed is running quickly, seems wants to fend. May at this moment, it only think that own body surroundings, as if some innumerable energy extrusions come, surroundings all turned into seven colors, its body in the instance of stop, that said [gold/metal] already accurate incomparable has punctured from it.

Strong Life strength madness injects into Tang Wulin within the body, these are supplementing the consumption of his body after Golden Dragon Spear refining powerful bloodline energy fully.

Tang Wulin also along with it dropping from the clouds, the back Seven-colored Dragon wing opens, falls in the ground.

In time that Scarlet Fire Monkey King in short several times breathe, by clean of Golden Dragon Spear Devour, only remaining leather bags.

Golden Dragon Spear as before is golden-colored, but the (spear|gun) glow actually assumes seven-colored, it obviously be much quicker than the normal condition to Devour speed of Life strength.

Such that just like Tang Wulin expects, Scarlet Fire Monkey King died, has not given his Soul Ring to increase Spiritual Power to cultivate is, but is condenses one jet black such as Soul Ring of black ink above the body.

Ten-thousand Years Soul Ring! This is genuine Soul Beast.

The takes a deep breath tone, the Tang Wulin thought just moved, he felt that strength rapid passes from within the body, the form separates together from him, his hurrying left hand holds in the arms her slender waist, is pretty face pale white Gu Yue.

At this moment, she besides some complexion pale white, seems also somewhat received to frighten, is winking the big eye, pours down the appearance that wants to sob.

Intermittent weak transmission, what makes Tang Wulin surprised is, before this time does not have , when they display Divine Dragon Transformation that type intense to wanting weak of stupor. Perhaps because of absorb the Ten-thousand Years Scarlet Fire Monkey King Life strength, he thought that own can also be able to support, at least also 30% cultivate for.

Fortunately!

Emerald Demon Bird that in his hand also one endlessly all solves, if on such stupor, once Emerald Demon Bird restores to come, that may be big troublesome.

Loosens surrounds the hand of Gu Yue, the Tang Wulin left hand lifts, pats directly toward Emerald Demon Bird on.

„Daddy, does not want!” Gu Yue called out in alarm, making Tang Wulin Golden Dragon Claw stop in Emerald Demon Bird top of the head.

„How?” Looks at Gu Yue, Tang Wulin panic-stricken in look vanished at this time, surplus, only then wild with joy.

When initially Gu Yue had saved him in Shrek Academy facing Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell appear(ance), has made Tang Wulin believe very that this is comes through own to his Silver Dragon scales transmission because of her, thus guessed that 70% possibilities, this look is similar to the Na'er young girl is the Gu Yue words. Then, he basically can 100% affirmations, the front be Gu Yue now. If, this Divine Dragon Transformation doesn't come from where? What also has to confirm the status compared with Martial Soul Fusion Technique?

Gu Yue goes forward two steps, has held Emerald Demon Bird from the Tang Wulin bosom, „it is quite lovable! Don't injure it to be good?”

Listened to Gu Yue these words, Tang Wulin under foot to stagger.

Lovable? Is this Little Thing, just may almost slurp her brain matter! She actually said that it is lovable?

However, until this time, Tang Wulin has the opportunity carefully looks at this only Emerald Demon Bird appearance.

That Emerald Demon Bird truly can describe with the adorable son. Its height ruler, all over the body the bluish-green feather is common just like Jade, the proboscis is deep green is bringing light golden-colored, seems very insightful, the personal appearance is slender, streamline excellent. Truly was attractive to Peak. Is closing both eyes, the eyelid is also light golden-colored. The back also has the golden-colored trace together to extend from the top of the head rear.

#886: Daddy is quite cruel!

Tang Wulin still remembers that it has a pair of just like the ruby gemstone general eye pupil. If it stands there is motionless, simply is the most perfect jade carving.

But, this Little Thing is awfully!

„It is not good, was too dangerous. Do you know that this Emerald Demon Bird is eats brain matter to evolve oneself!” Tang Wulin anxious saying.

„Does not give.” Gu Yue tight is holding Emerald Demon Bird, has turned around, to a Tang Wulin back.

Tang Wulin moved sideways to arrive in front of her, serious [say / way]: „Gu Yue, is obedient, this is not the amusing thing. It just may almost want your life!”

„Does not give, Daddy is quite cruel.” Gu Yue partly turns around.

Tang Wulin speechless, am I cruel? I was not cruel it to kill us!

„Gu Yue, is obedient, is good. This Emerald Demon Bird is the famous ominous bird, ancient era, had created the reactionary reign of terror. I thought in this only Emerald Demon Bird and old book described somewhat was different, the strength recorded the old book is more formidable. I have knocked down it, if it wakes, will threaten our Life. We have had more than enough including Divine Dragon Transformation now, when the time comes, we must die under its mouth. Do you want to visit me dead?”

Gu Yue gains ground, looks that the Tang Wulin earnest expressions and to both hands that he extends, blinked, suddenly said: „I remember means probably, can make it not injure us.”

Has not waited for Tang Wulin to open the mouth again, she lifts a hand suddenly, in airborne empty.

Strange lines from the sky show, each is silver light glittering, just likes living creature glittering the strange brilliance.

Gradually, these line condense become silver rune, falls slowly toward that emerald-green Emerald Demon Bird on.

Line emerge, the body of that Emerald Demon Bird starts to shiver. Gu Yue gently is touching its hair, „Little Cui is clever, a one after next was good.”

Tang Wulin surprised looks at Gu Yue, he clearly feels, in that silver rune, is containing extremely huge Spiritual Strength. Takes his Spirit Abyss Realm spiritual to cultivate, is unable to feel Spiritual Strength that in that rune contains to be actually formidable to any degree unexpectedly.

He hurries to ask: „Gu Yue, what did you also remember?”

Gu Yue shakes the head, „does not have! Is remembers this to let the means that Little Cui is obedient. I am only remember indistinctly that probably as the matter stands, it will again not make. Obedient listens to my words.”

Tang Wulin some had not felt relieved, „what to do, if were defeated? It......”

„Will not be defeated.” Gu Yue affirms with earnest saying.

Tang Wulin said: „That this, I promise you not to kill it, but you must make me use Blue Silver Emperor to tie up it, waited for it to awake has taken a look at the situation to say again.”

Gu Yue obvious some do not want, but looks at the look that Tang Wulin insists, finally nodded, has given Tang Wulin Emerald Demon Bird in hand cautiously.

Does not dare to use ordinary Blue Silver Emperor, Tang Wulin has released golden speech (Jin Yu) directly, the golden speech (Jin Yu) tail flings, Emerald Demon Bird Bind.

Sees golden speech (Jin Yu), Gu Yue is also the appearance that is interested in very much, said that golden speech (Jin Yu) is different from before.

The Tang Wulin Qi and Blood separation, after breaking through Ninth Layer Golden Dragon King Seal, on the golden speech (Jin Yu) forehead, grew an alone angle, at the same time, the body also grew 18 meters, seemed is very over the body slender, but the body has covered entirely and Tang Wulin exactly the same golden-colored dragon scales, but no longer was only the texture. Felt that looks like golden-colored little dragon(s) is ordinary.

a pair of golden-colored crystal eye pupil, were obviously more than before might. Looks up Tang Wulin, body aura is fearless.

From golden speech (Jin Yu), Tang Wulin felt very intense intelligence, this once was only the defective product(s) Soul Spirit kid, now grew more and more. Tang Wulin has the feeling faintly, if one day, golden speech (Jin Yu) evolves dragon wing(s), perhaps then, it really can become existence that is similar to True Dragon.

Although Tyrannosaurus also follows his bloodline evolution to evolve, but compares with golden speech (Jin Yu), the scope of Tyrannosaurus evolution wanted to be smaller.

One is because Tyrannosaurus is in itself too strong, what is more important, its after all land dragon, is not genuine True Dragon.

golden speech (Jin Yu) is different, it is Tang Wulin first Soul Spirit, Tang Wulin, when bloodline awakens, with it in the same place. Its bloodline, completely and Tang Wulin bloodline is equal. Therefore, was affected by Tang Wulin, golden speech (Jin Yu) evolution pure.

of course, Tyrannosaurus, if can also evolve in the future dragon wing(s), the situation also will be then almost the same as it, different that's all that just excels.

Soul Spirit regarding Soul Master, the most vital function is to provide Soul Ring, the Soul Spirit function of ordinary Soul Master is not big, but regarding Elite, the function of Battle Armor is much greater than Soul Spirit, therefore their energy are also used to train Battle Armor.

Only then as providing final several Soul Ring Soul Spirit may be is formidable enough, can provide the help in the fight to them. Why this is also Shrek Seven Monsters in the combat process, everybody little releases the Soul Spirit reason. As provision front several Soul Ring Soul Spirit, their it, although along with will also evolve in Spirit Raising Platform absorb Spiritual Power, but the Transformation scope is small, cannot withstand to use.

Only then Tang Wulin golden speech (Jin Yu) is different, its evolution with the Soul Ring evolution, but grows with Tang Wulin bloodline. Tang Wulin broke through nine Golden Dragon King Seal, present golden speech (Jin Yu), became entirely different.

Tang Wulin places on the hand golden speech (Jin Yu), golden speech (Jin Yu) stretches out the tongue, selected in his palm place, in look were many several points of pride. As if is demonstrating to Tang Wulin, it now already very formidable.

Tang Wulin shows a faint smile, „good! That will fight next time time, made you enter the stage.”

golden speech (Jin Yu) unexpectedly very user-friendly nodded to Tang Wulin, then has turned head, look somewhat bad looks to Emerald Demon Bird. As if was considering that takes to bite to death it.

Gu Yue is gazing at fixedly golden speech (Jin Yu), „not.”

golden speech (Jin Yu) looked up her, some vision as if delay, then lowered the head, unexpectedly was similar to complied.

Gu Yue then lights up with pleasure.

That Emerald Demon Bird is damaged heavily, a short time does not wake, Tang Wulin this time very serious order Gu Yue cannot leave his body surroundings ten meters range, this sits cross-legged to sit, meditation restoration.

The thought immerses, in within the body two vortex circulations revolve.

Qi and Blood vortex significantly reduced, revolving speed is also very slow. Without doubt has consumed massive bloodline energy in just Divine Dragon Transformation process, Soul Power vortex is also. But what makes Tang Wulin surprised is, his meridians as if has expanded in just Divine Dragon Transformation process. Because meridians itself enough tenacity, does not have what the trace of breakage.

Can the strength promotion, control Divine Dragon Transformation mighty energy finally gradually? meditation, he when recalls just Divine Dragon Transformation was being triggered the feeling.

That time he, the fear to the extreme, in the heart has thought that had Gu Yue. Rather is willing dead for her. Then Divine Dragon Transformation inspired under his leadership on the first time.

energy that Gu Yue transmits is too strong, after his own energy fuses, his body approached collapses, cannot withstand. But when he called out pitifully, energy poured into actually stops. Should this be Gu Yue subconscious Control lives?

If Gu Yue is the sober condition, perhaps, own and her Control good Divine Dragon Transformation, to use this Martial Soul Fusion Technique together perfectly.

Just that formidable feeling was really too wonderful. What is more important, only then personally has experienced that stage ability, can better understood that on path that the future will promote, little will detour.

This meditation time is not really short, one is to restore to consume, another is the comprehension of settles down own.

#887: What is Soul Beast King?

When Tang Wulin sobers from meditation, discovered that Gu Yue head rest on his thigh, fragrance that rests.

Looks at her resting face, in the Tang Wulin eye reveals the gentle color, gently is stroking her long hair.

Gu Yue Gu Yue, why will you have the Na'er appearance? Also does not have the least bit cosmetics trace. On you, actually what happened?

In this piece very possible is the Star Dou Forest place, he does not have the means to help her treat, only then leaves here first, can help her therapy.

Now can only walk one step to look one step, but after is exits, the entire Continent influence that Shrek City Fallen brings, will make without doubt also the head of this Present Generation Shrek Seven Monsters, sustains the huge incomparable pressure.

His clear remembering, Sky Raising Douluo Yun Ming before take-off, has said to him, they are the seeds of Shrek. Shrek has trained them, without Shrek, does not have today's him. Without a doubt, he shoulders is rebuilding the heavy responsibility of Shrek, shoulders is being the responsibility of Shrek revenge.

Subconscious grips the tight fist, diligently makes own not recall in Shrek Academy that vice- familiar appearance.

The sad any function, he is not strong.

Does not know how companion, after having blocked that artillery shell, they should not have the matter. At the same time is thinking, Tang Wulin Soul Guide Communication Device of own took from Soul Guidance Storing Device, such that just like he expects, Soul Guide Communication Device does not have the signal. Cannot relate the outside.

Sighed, has not awakened Gu Yue, took out the dry rations to eat.

The distant place, the Scarlet Fire Monkey King body is ascending Ten-thousand Years Soul Ring already, because the time relations dissipated. Without doubt, this Soul Ring wasted. But this does not have the means that Tang Wulin and Gu Yue does not need Soul Ring now. But in fact, if not the Scarlet Fire Monkey King driving attack, Tang Wulin does not want to kill it. Now Continent, but also existence Soul Beast, formidable Soul Beast, was really particularly extremely rare.

In this time, in the Tang Wulin heart is moving suddenly, has remembered that only Emerald Demon Bird, turns head to look.

The golden speech (Jin Yu) plate becomes Serpentine Array, side him, Serpentine Array center, Emerald Demon Bird there. What strange is, its wound healed completely, was covered by the feather. At this time it awoke, the eye of a pair of ruby-like, is looking at Tang Wulin. Lives in its body regarding golden speech (Jin Yu) Bind, does not struggle.

Tang Wulin brow slightly wrinkle, is staring at Emerald Demon Bird, is depending on his meaning, should blow away this fellow directly. The Emerald Demon Bird reputation let his direct under killer sufficiently.

Emerald Demon Bird seems felt that his malicious intent, the body shrank shrinking subconsciously, then looked to lie down Gu Yue on his leg. Suddenly sends out several clear sounding.

The Gu Yue body trembled, the long eyelash raised, has opened the dim sleepy eyes.

„Does Little Cui. Others are resting soundly, did you call me to do?”

„Squeek psst.” Emerald Demon Bird also called several,

Gu Yue then stands up from failure to sit up, looks at Tang Wulin, immediately digs the mouth saying: „Daddy, Little Cui said that you want to be disadvantageous . Did you frighten it?”

Tang Wulin one dull, „can you understand its words?”

Gu Yue nods, said: „Yes! I was the Little Cui master, of course can understand.”

Doubts of Tang Wulin face, „real? Did you determine?”

Gu Yue nods once more, „of course determined. Does not believe you to look. Little Cui, am I beautiful?”

Emerald Demon Bird hurries to nod.

Tang Wulin laughs in spite of trying not to immediately, „am that I graceful?”

Emerald Demon Bird stared his one eyes wickedly, then leaves goes excessively, the appearance of that user-friendly, making Tang Wulin somewhat dumbfounded.

„Ha Ha Ha Ha!” Gu Yue has smiled immediately happily, „Daddy, you quickly put it. I ensure Little Cui will not injure my.”

Tang Wulin both eyes narrow the eyes, although he somewhat was worried, but looks at the Emerald Demon Bird appearance, should be also good. Moreover there are him side Gu Yue, did not fear actually.

„golden speech (Jin Yu), lets loose it.”

The golden speech (Jin Yu) tail flings, blue light shoots up to the sky instantaneously, Emerald Demon Bird skyrockets.

Tang Wulin subconscious must lift hand to grasp, actually held on by Gu Yue. That Emerald Demon Bird from the sky circles for one week, then opens pair of wings to drop slowly, put completely speed intentionally, finally fell on the Gu Yue shoulder, intimate very specific use has rubbed then also rubbing in her head.

Real yield?

Tang Wulin or first time heard that some people can yield Soul Beast, let alone, at present this only Variation Emerald Demon Bird at least also be Ten-thousand Years stage existence, if can be really Gu Yue uses, is the help is naturally enormous.

Emerald Demon Bird appears very clever, does not have the ominous severe flavor, submissive standing on the Gu Yue shoulder, but also often has a specific use to rub her long hair.

Tang Wulin then relaxed, golden speech (Jin Yu) wanders side him, golden light (Jin Guang) dodges, integrates his within the body to vanish to disappear.

„Little Cui, later you called this name.” Gu Yue grinning tracing Emerald Demon Bird.

Tang Wulin malicious intent [say / way]: „Might as well call Cui Hua to be good, the green body, the red eye, looks like the green leaf to serve as contrast the safflower.”

„Psst!” Emerald Demon Bird called several angrily.

Gu Yue purses the lips saying: „Little Cui it does not like, called Little Cui.”

Tang Wulin lets somebody cool off or calm down stared Emerald Demon Bird, „you best honest, otherwise, ahem!”

Emerald Demon Bird is actually supinely begins, pays no attention to him.

It before this has injured the own man, may not have the least bit favorable impression.

„Walks.” Tang Wulin releases own Blue Silver Grass, communicates surroundings Plant, is investigating the surroundings situation, while walks toward the front.

Has not walked two steps, he stops the footsteps, said to Gu Yue: „You ask it, which direction from can leave this piece of forest?” Although there is a direction of Plant, but Soul Beast, High Rank Soul Beast cannot have particularly in Humanity Wisdom, this Emerald Demon Bird obviously understand this piece of forest compared with them.

Gu Yue looks to Emerald Demon Bird, in the eye as if has ray of light to flash, Emerald Demon Bird chirp called several, Gu Yue to nod, said: Direction that „Daddy, you judge is right, toward that side, can walk to outside. However Little Cui said that outside has more fearful existence. But said probably is our Humanity.”

Tang Wulin both eyes narrow the eyes, here more and more likely was that place that he judged. If is really, Soul Beast frightened Humanity is also very normal. Is Humanity unceasing seizes their survival spatial originally.

According to his understanding, the entire Star Dou Forest Nucleus circle surrounding, should by with large army defense, formidable Soul Beast rioting that in order to avoid inside is a rear survival. This actually does not come from Federation with large army, but is Spirit Transferring Pagoda.

On Continent, the Shrek Academy strongest place is Prestige, is graduate who its has pupils everywhere. But Tang Sect is strongest, is resources and Business aspect. But Spirit Transferring Pagoda is strongest, then through Soul Spirit as well as Spirit Raising Platform control and so on to Soul Master world.

Spirit Transferring Pagoda General Headquarters, in being away from the Shrek Academy not far place, outside Shrek City. Also is distance that Star Dou Forest not far away. The Star Dou Forest Nucleus circle, the control in the Spirit Transferring Pagoda hand, actually inside anything situation nobody had known that wants to enter, that is must pay to the Spirit Transferring Pagoda extremely high price. It can be said that Spirit Transferring Pagoda quite therefore is rearing in a pen these strongest Soul Beast.

He does not know how own and Gu Yue enter here, but wants to walk from here, not only wants in place forest formidable Soul Beast, in the meantime, before departure, but must run out of the tight encirclement of Spirit Transferring Pagoda to be good.

Thinks of here, Tang Wulin looks to Gu Yue that is here that Gu Yue leads him to enter, moreover Gu Yue should not lower in the Spirit Transferring Pagoda status now. But, her present memory does not have, a pure looks like white paper.

It seems like that only then own is leading her, through the law of seepage learns from Devil Island Old Devil there, was separated to encircle tightly.

Leads the way in forest, Gu Yue through with the Emerald Demon Bird communication, brings many convenience to them. Emerald Demon Bird told Gu Yue, Soul Beast in forest was now few, therefore everybody did not have the struggle of territory basically, respectively lived existence one piece to belong to the own region. Therefore, bumps into the Soul Beast probability not too to be high. It knew with that Scarlet Fire Monkey King that no one how anyone, Scarlet Fire Monkey King is tells it to have the Humanity game to enter here, it comes, mainly to look for food.

Cultivation of Emerald Demon Bird to as if to the bottleneck, have having needed Devour Elite brain matter be able to evolve. In this piece of Star Dou Forest, so long as also existence Soul Beast, is not good to cope, it does not dare to act rashly. Controls this piece of forest Soul Beast King to prohibit strictly among Soul Beast to massacre mutually, it does not dare to defy.

„What is Soul Beast King?” Tang Wulin curious asked to Emerald Demon Bird.

Emerald Demon Bird stayed, then actually shook the head, whole body hair slight(ly) is shivering, as if very fear.

-------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#888: purple-haired female

Gu Yue curious [say / way]: „Little Cui, do not fear that told us quickly, actually Soul Beast King was who!”

Emerald Demon Bird looks up to her, the eye of red winked winking, actually once more lowered the head, this time it was said that anything agree did not say.

In this time, Tang Wulin was only thinking suddenly an invisible pressure from transmits in all directions suddenly, his relied on the Spiritual Strength instantaneously oppressed contraction that Plant are expanding.

This is......

Tang Wulin has a big shock at the same time, hurries to arrive at side Gu Yue, holds on her hand.

Emerald Demon Bird gained ground, in the eye is revealing the scared color. But Sky, actually gloomy.

The beautiful sunlight vanished without trace, what replaces it is piece of darkness, the huge pressure drops from the clouds, to human a panic beyond description. What is more fearful, Tang Wulin discovered with amazement, in the air, other attribute Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces and energy members rapidly are disappearing, even can describe with the escape, surplus, only then black Dark Element.

„Raising” low and deep howling fluctuation trim forest trembles.

„Who is, dares to slaughter Soul Beast. Is, dares to invade Star Dou.” sounds/voices reverberates in trim forest, even if Tang Wulin at this time All-Out and surroundings Plant communicate, Plant is actually in instinct reaction, as if all quiet.

The heart of Tang Wulin also sinks to the valley, so the terrifying pressure, except for can be equal to Humanity Titled Douluo Hundred-thousand Years above cultivates is Soul Beast, does not have other again. This future, simply is unthinkable, absolutely is he has seen in Soul Beast most formidable existence.

If can compare with it, perhaps only then initially went to Star Luo Empire to have the possibility in that only Super Rank big octopus that in sea bumps into.

Sky completely becomes jet black, has the purple light to flash faintly, surroundings rich Dark Element made in the air immediately as if appear(ance) the intermittent strange fluctuation, as if some innumerable sad and shrill pitiful yell sounds got up. Filled Life aura big forest, in an instant unexpectedly is similar to the ghost legendary creature.

surroundings all become incomparably silent, even if linked sound of the insect warbler calling not to have.

Tang Wulin only thought that own breathes difficulties, strength of Soul Power or the Qi and Blood, oppressed stagnation nearly.

Although he already knows that facing genuine Elite, own this cultivates for the basis is nothing, may face at this time, he actually as before fills unwillingly.

He does not fear death, but actually does not want dead, he also has too many matters to do, he also shoulders is rallying the heavy responsibility of Shrek Academy!

But, facing so the powerful enemy, he can also result in escapes the disaster? Perhaps is he can display Divine Dragon Transformation unable to achieve with Gu Yue once more.

Let alone, they just had displayed Divine Dragon Transformation, in short time should not be impossible to display once more.

Turns head to look to Gu Yue, Gu Yue as if is also some fears, hiding of pretty face pale white side Tang Wulin, tight is holding his arm.

In Tang Wulin heart one miserable, they did not strive for living finally really in the same year, similarly was actually buried in this Soul Beast forest?

No, not!

Even if exhausts own last drop of blood, must protect her to be complete.

Thinks of here, Tang Wulin originally suppressed extremely fierce aura starts suddenly becomes powerful, the unyielding thought looked like lights his bloodline to be ordinary.

The bloodline fluctuation that nearly stagnates makes a fresh start to ascend, Soul Power also gives full play to the full of vitality. Gold misty halo, releases from his body surface.

„Before I die, does not make anybody injure you.” The Tang Wulin takes a deep breath tone, the One Word Battle Armor turn over, the rapid coverage whole body, the right hand wipes on the forehead, Golden Dragon Spear falls into the palm. His own imposing manner, is promoting with bloodline eruption madness.

„Well!” sounds/voices of doubts transmits from distant place.

At this moment, Tang Wulin only thought that in front big forest, as if left passageway, this passageway is dark-purple, can only through this dark-purple ray of light, see clearly indistinctly.

The passageway end, the form goes out from darkness together slowly, her whole body is covering the purple-black scales, the figure is slim, the front is perfectly round, the thigh is straight, above the chest, reveals the shoulder snow white flesh and front profound gully. A purple-black long hair hangs loose after behind, calm automatic, naturally ripples from the body. tender face is quite beautiful, her eye is dark-purple, the lip is actually bright purple. Forehead place, jet black such as on scales of black ink, ripples overlapping purple halo, the nature is flowing from her top of the head.

Sees this appearance, Tang Wulin holds breath cold air. If before , he also thinks that this is Hundred-thousand Years Soul Beast, then, he definitely has been able to affirm now, that own faces, should be cultivates to surpass Two Hundred-thousand Years, in the Soul Beast world genuine stands in summit existence, Ferocious Beast! One generation of Ferocious Beast.

When the Shrek Academy study, there is a knowledge about Ferocious Beast they to study many, at that time, Tang Wulin was also interested, therefore specially has also studied.

Soul Beast cultivate arrives at Hundred-thousand Years, basically is the limit. To continue to promote again, only then two methods, one type is repeat cultivation and become a human, remove beast frame, this can have Humanity comprehension and higher Wisdom, to that illusory God Rank sprint, once breaks the limit of this world, then, is dynasty Becomes a God.

Soul Beast is unable Becomes a God, this as if to be a rule, like that story that initially Gu Yue once told.

But most Soul Beast, will not choose this path, after all, formidable Humanity, life also more than 200 years, once breaks through the failure, is unable Becomes a God, to be then same as Humanity, Fallen in river of history.

Another road, must break through, the Hundred-thousand Years big bottleneck, regarding Soul Beast, is just like Heavenly Tribulation general existence, after Hundred-thousand Years, does not need Hundred Year, Heavenly Tribulation naturally to meet. Once is unable to break through, that relationship of form and spirit complete extermination.

These have enough self-confident Soul Beast to oneself, will choose this road to break through, after the breakthrough, may live again Hundred-thousand Years.

Once breaks through a bottleneck, then, the Soul Beast strength will break through, large scale advance, for Ferocious Beast!

If Hundred-thousand Years Soul Beast is equal to Titled Douluo, then, Ferocious Beast quite therefore Super Rank Douluo. The cultivate age limit is higher, breaks through bottleneck number of times many Ferocious Beast, the strength is also terrifying.

In legend, even also has to cultivate to surpass Million Years Ferocious Beast. Breaks through ten bottlenecks, that is what kind existence!

But also has Ferocious Beast, in does not choose in the repeat cultivation and become a human situation, can change into human form.

At present this, the whole body is sending out the ominous prestige illustrious, without a doubt is Soul Beast, but she can transform human form, moreover seems so perfect, naturally without a doubt, is Ferocious Beast, perhaps cultivates to at least have Two Hundred-thousand Years Ferocious Beast. Is equal to Humanity Super Rank Douluo existence.

But Tang Wulin puts on his One Word Battle Armor, is equal to Seven Rings Soul Beast, does not have Martial Soul avatar Seven Rings Soul Saint. His talent different reported again, impossible and front such existence contends. Although he feels that at present this, should be Dragon-Type Soul Beast.

The female more walked is nearer, in eyes, the purple light just likes substantive flows to the both sides, the distance is nearer, she takes to the Tang Wulin pressure to be also bigger. Tang Wulin golden-colored light fog releases are more.

Tang Wulin own is also very clear, the close limit of this degree of pressure, own withstood. Is own that unyielding willpower supports his bloodline to erupt formidable aura unceasingly, this can not be crushed by the opposite party.

„Small Humanity, dares my Star Dou Forest to slaughter Soul Beast unexpectedly. You are really the big courage.” That purple-haired female was saying at the same time, in about 50 meters place stopped the footsteps from Tang Wulin.

------------------------------

Today Tang Sect small companion tells me, our own shop Dazzling Era Tang Sect is taught Zhangwang Teacher(s) design by the Nankai University fine arts department Golden Dragon King scales and Silver Dragon King scales pendant, sales volume of good several days in entire Taobao Star Shop to have placed first continuously. Thank everybody's support. The interested book friend can have a look. I have established the prosperous Tang brand with Zhangwang Teacher(s), is hopes that can create some high-quality the peripheral products to come out. Have a look some interests to our shops.

#889: chain bracelet the light of seven-colored

Suddenly, her pupil has contracted slightly, as if saw anything. Simultaneously looks the color of doubts.

Tang Wulin horizontal in hand Golden Dragon Spear, sinking sound track: „Does not intend to affront. We do not know why will enter here. I come here time already stupor. Shortly after I wake up, that Scarlet Fire Monkey King initiative attack we, this was struck to kill by us.”

That purple-haired female deeps frown, has not continued to open the mouth, oppression aura that but on her formerly transmitted actually clearly weakened.

In this time, Gu Yue is poking head from Tang Wulin, somewhat curious looks to that female.

Four items of relative, the body of female vibrated, the eyeground has flashed through the color of more intense shock. She is almost subconscious must say anything, when but she sees clearly the Gu Yue look, stares.

„You name.” purple-haired female sinking sound asked.

Tang Wulin said: „I called Tang Wulin, this was my girlfriend Gu Yue. We do not intend to affront, if Your Excellency is willing to put us to depart, I am willing to trade with the valuable thing.”

The female looking pensive visits him, the body was releasing killing intent is clearly weakening, as if by the heart movement that Tang Wulin said.

„Exchange? What do you have to be able with me to exchange?” Was asking, she while was pondering. In her opinion, wants to strike to kill Tang Wulin is the easy matter. But in just, who her has recognized him is, what is more important, she later saw Tang Wulin behind Gu Yue. This somewhat troubled.

Tang Wulin stayed, yes! What own has to exchange? Facing this generation of Ferocious Beast, own can make its thing of being interested absolutely not many. What on him are most is rare metal(s). That several types that Heaven and Earth Treasure own gathers for him are the value not poor, may live in Star Dou Forest regarding one has counted Hundred-thousand Years Ferocious Beast, perhaps was not anything.

Suddenly in the Tang Wulin heart moves, has thought a thing, „are you Dragon Clan?”

The purple-haired female eyebrow selects, „good, this is a Infernal Demon Dragon clan.” This does not have anything to be good to conceal. In fact, in front of Tang Wulin this, before Ten-thousand Years, has placed ninth in Ten Great Ferocious Beasts, is Infernal Demon Dragon King. She with the head of then Ten Great Ferocious Beasts, Golden-Eyed Black Dragon King Di Tian, and called Two Great Dragon Kings in Ferocious Beast.

On cultivation for her, although is far from compared with Beast God Di Tian, but must discuss bloodline to be pure, the Innate Body potential, is actually not inferior. Is one of unusual pure blooded True Dragon Dragon Clan inheritance gets down. Therefore can break Heavenly Tribulation, builds Ferocious Beast.

Infernal Demon Dragon?

Tang Wulin holds breath cold air, he immediately has also thought of this status.

Hundred-thousand Years Soul Beast was quite scarce, can cultivate to Ferocious Beast stage, that naturally be very few. Front is Infernal Demon Dragon, how could it not be that is that in legend, she unexpectedly is real existence.

At the same time is thinking, he actually does not dare to neglect, lest the opposite party meets act . Goes on living, is important to him, let alone the side also has Gu Yue.

Lifts the hand, he has picked chain bracelet in own wrist, sinking sound track: „I on another piece of Continent, was once lucky see Dragon Clan Graveyard. Where obtained this string bracelet, may be useful to you.”

Right, he picks that has seven-colored Crystallized Body pendant chain bracelet. Crystallized Body on chain bracelet is sending out gentle seven-colored ray of light, partly visible. If feels carefully, truly can from feels some Dragon Clan aura.

The Infernal Demon Dragon King delicate eyebrows move slightly, lift the hand toward Tang Wulin gently one move, immediately, gentle suction appear(ance), towed that chain bracelet to fly in her direction directly.

50 meters distance already, chain bracelet falls into above the Infernal Demon Dragon King fair palm in a flash. Instance that but moves with her palm in that chain bracelet.

Suddenly, makes situation appear(ance) that they have not thought.

That originally seems very ordinary seven-colored Crystallized Body, suddenly Great Release of Rays of Light, intense incomparable seven-colored ray of light shoots up to the sky.

Jet black such as the world of black ink was exaggerated brilliant seven colors immediately, as if some innumerable Mighty Dragon are exuding the sound of resonant dragon roar.

„” Infernal Demon Dragon King called out pitifully, chain bracelet lets go to depart immediately. In Sky, selects point seven-colored ray of light to condense slowly, changes into huge seven-colored Light and Shadow, that seven-colored Light and Shadow as if dragon-shaped, is having the unequalled dignity.

Then formidable Infernal Demon Dragon King, is crawling unexpectedly instantaneously in the place, the whole body trembles, actually moves cannot move. As if bears the pressure that anything is unable to resist.

But another side Tang Wulin actually dumbfounded. Because, what is entirely different from that Infernal Demon Dragon King, him, anything has not felt. All as usual. The pressure that Infernal Demon Dragon King creates vanished thoroughly.

Bathes in that seven-colored ray of light, he only thinks very comfortable. His behind Gu Yue, at this time also walked, stands with him shoulder to shoulder, in the eye reveals the color of being at a loss, as if also has several points to think.

That seven-colored Crystallized Body from the sky enlarges, next one flickers, changes into together the seven-colored flowing light, returns above the Tang Wulin wrist.

Tang Wulin only thought that willpower of respect transmits, as if has any special connection with him.

But at this moment, the seven-colored Crystallized Body rear incisive place of waterdrop to next, punctured his wrist [lineage/vein] suddenly, wisp of fresh blood flows out, happen to dissolves with that seven-colored Crystallized Body as one.

Immediately, Tang Wulin only thought that an unequalled huge thought breaks to his brain in instantaneously, he stuffy snort, one black has fainted at present.

„Daddy” near ear transmits Gu Yue sounds/voices finally.

The distant place, the body of Infernal Demon Dragon King shivered for several minutes, gradually vanishes with that seven-colored ray of light, this returns to normal.

Sits on the ground, her big mouth and big mouth is panting for breath, surprised uncertain looks fell down, but whole body actually in Tang Wulin by seven-colored ray of light gable. In the eye pupil full is shocking.

What is that? Dragon God Blessing? She clearly solid feeling Dragon God aura, that is not genuine Dragon God, but is a thought that as pure blooded True Dragon, is Dragon God that she believes, all pure blooded True Dragon are so. Dragon God can be said as their beliefs. After cultivation to be certain extent, can draw support from the strength of Dragon God.

But just Dragon God willpower, looked like by the strength of belief is borrowed, after all, all Dragon Clan know, Dragon God already no longer existence. May believe also, but that strong belief, Infernal Demon Dragon self-examines, even if 100 own, cannot summon comes!

Perhaps when Dragon Clan was most prosperous in the past, has possibility appear(ance) such Dragon God willpower to arrive. Is this possible? How possible appear(ance) on Humanity, even if their High Lord cannot achieve!

In the heart shocks at the same time, her vision cannot help but falls on Gu Yue.

Gu Yue at this time is being panic-stricken of face, was summoning to lie down in ground Tang Wulin.

„Daddy? What ghost?” Infernal Demon Dragon King dumbfounded looks Gu Yue there anxious was calling.

She crawls from the ground, arrives by Gu Yue and Tang Wulin quickly, because actually on Tang Wulin is releasing seven-colored ray of light does not dare to approach.

„Host and High Lord......” she were summoning in a soft voice.

Gu Yue subconscious gaining ground, in beautiful pupil full is the tears, „you are an unprincipled person, why you must injure my Daddy. I dislike you......”

„This......” the eye of Infernal Demon Dragon King one was straight. She definitely is unable to believe all that own sees at present.

This is her effective and influential word, overawes many colleagues High Lord?

To, is not right, this has certainly anything not to be right.

Thinks of here, she does not dare to neglect, soars instantaneously, changes into the purple light to vanish together does not see. This matter is not she can decide.

Sky becomes sunny, sunlight shines the earth, forest gives full play to the vitality under shining of sunlight, rich Life aura reverberates in the air, all returned to normal.

Tang Wulin body surroundings seven-colored ray of light is rippling as before, his whole person stupor is very thorough, but does not have no Transformation, seemed looks like falls asleep normally.

time is not long, forms come quietly, Infernal Demon Dragon King that four people, one of them, before left successively fully. Besides her, another three people are female two male.

That female is the look is extremely also beautiful, a bluish-green long skirt served as contrast her to fill Life aura, making one seem will have the feeling of being intimate with.

In two men, one is the look is handsome, but the whole body is actually filling evil qi imposing flavor youth. Another person is the makings concentrates the thick incomparable middle-aged person.

-------------------

------------------------------

Tang Sect small companion told me, our own shop Dazzling Era Tang Sect was taught Zhangwang Teacher(s) design by the Nankai University fine arts department Golden Dragon King scales and Silver Dragon King scales pendant, sales volume of good several days in entire Taobao Star Shop to have placed first continuously. Thank everybody's support. The interested book friend can have a look. I have established the prosperous Tang brand with Zhangwang Teacher(s), is hopes that can create some high-quality the peripheral products to come out. Have a look some interests to our shops. Our all new book entity books will also sell in our own shop, discount.

#890: Dreamland

In four people, obviously by that middle-aged artificial head. In a black hair, wisp of golden-colored long punishes in the cheek front, his appear(ance), surroundings big forest naturally is peaceful. Without any might, is only because of his existence.

„High Lord.” The middle-aged people see Gu Yue, immediately respectful calling out.

Gu Yue gains ground, in the eye is having a fear, „who you and are you? Cannot you injure my Daddy.”

Four people all were similar to petrify generally, stood does not know whether to laugh or cry there.

That handsome youth to middle-aged humanity: „Boss, what's all this about? High Lord this......”

At this time Tang Wulin is the comatose condition, the Gu Yue appearance does not install obviously.

The middle-aged people go forward one step, arrives in front of Gu Yue, Gu Yue frightens immediately lowered the head, actually falls down on Tang Wulin, covers his body with the body of own.

As the matter stands, Gu Yue naturally also fell into that seven-colored ray of light, the hand of middle-aged person just contacted that seven-colored ray of light, immediately the whole body megascism, fell to draw back several steps backward, a shock of face.

But other three people see this, all also shocks in the extreme. They too understood that at present this cultivates. Unexpectedly in that seems in front of very gentle seven-colored ray of light frightened so fierce. What existence that seven-colored ray of light is!

„Really is Dragon God willpower.” The middle-aged person brow is tight, „, but, will have Dragon God willpower to arrive on him? Even if on him has Golden Dragon King bloodline, but he after is Humanity. It is not Soul Beast repairs definitely. Golden Dragon King bloodline was very strange, this Dragon God willpower does he from where come?”

The purple-haired female is also a forced smile of face, „the great strength of this Dragon God willpower, only saw in my lifetime. Di Tian, we what to do?”

Right, this middle-aged person before her, is honored as Beast God, the head of Ten Great Ferocious Beasts, Golden-Eyed Black Dragon King, Di Tian.

Di Tian both eyes narrow the eyes, said to that the man of youth appearance: „Yao Ling, you draw High Lord. I get physical exam for High Lord.”

youth stares, „Boss, you are not good, can I be good?”

Di Tian said: „This Dragon God willpower has the formidable awesome effect to our Dragon Clan, you also do not have Dragon Clan bloodline, naturally unobstructive. However, so long as there are us here, you cannot injure him, otherwise Dragon God willpower will tow us to protect him.”

youth surprised [say / way]: „So is unexpectedly mysterious, is really interesting! Very long not such interesting matter. However, Boss you did not say that this boy should massacre? Has massacred him, High Lord might restore in the past mighty energy of Dragon God.”

On the Di Tian face reveals to wipe the forced smile, „this matter wants High Lord to decide that now on him had Dragon God willpower, did not say. Perhaps, his present condition is the High Lord arrangement.”

The youth half step arrives at side Di Tian, both hands search, has drawn Gu Yue, light blue light in his body surroundings circulation, is very gentle, but Gu Yue does not have the strength of resistance obviously.

Struggling that Gu Yue makes an effort, by that blue light gable, is actually not able to move.

Di Tian searches the hand, according to the Gu Yue forehead, gentle ray of light in his fingertip glittering.

The Gu Yue look immediately becomes somewhat blurred, but on energy with the Di Tian palm ripples, her body surroundings also reappears partly visible silver scales.

A moment later, Di Tian receives the hand, as if relaxed.

„High Lord unobstructive, should by fluctuation, be caused some Primordial Spirit fluctuation fiercely, the memory chaos. By High Lord formidable self-recovery ability, even if no external force to be auxiliary, can return to normal in less than how long to also. With the description of Humanity, was the temporariness loses recalls.”

Other three relaxed, Infernal Demon Dragon King loses says with a smile: „, Indeed, High Lord that Daddy called at that time, I who listens to am fearful and apprehensive! Di Tian, that present what to do?”

After Di Tian slightly makes the thinking, said: „This matter has surpassed the category that we have been able to process. First this. Let High Lord process voluntarily is, by the energy of High Lord, is impossible to receive anything to injure. After her memory natural recovery comes, all are not the issues. But this named Tang Wulin Humanity, we also can only continue to observe. Dragon God willpower appear(ance) on him, should be related with High Lord. Now I somewhat understood why High Lord did not kill him, should to train this Dragon God willpower, has the strength of this belief, in the future High Lord in light of Golden Dragon King strength, will awaken Dragon God to have bright prospects again. To that time, in this Douluo Continent world, we have been able to establish its belongs to our Soul Beast God Realm, not by that Humanity oppression.”

Listens to him to say these words, several other big Soul Beast looks immediately become blazing. Subconscious grips the tight double fist.

Four people retreat quietly, Gu Yue blue light also vanished. Until this time, deep green Emerald Demon Bird, dares to drill all over the body from her silver-haired, has a lingering fear looks at the distant place to vanish that several forms that.

Tang Wulin has been having a dream, his dream to were more.

The limitless giant islands, in Sky are hovering Mighty Dragon, they have various color scales. The personal appearance varies, has the characteristics respectively.

In the ground, huge Mountain Dragon King falls into sea, changes into Continent. In Sky, Sacred Mighty Dragon face upwards to roar, overawes many colleagues.

In sea, water dragon unceasing take-off falls again, splashes piece by piece the water splash.

True Dragon everywhere one visit, the myriad things submit.

Good Dragon Clan beautiful scenery.

Has not known long time, Heaven and Earth turned into red suddenly, huge incomparable Fireball(s) drop from the clouds, falls into sea, to fall on the land.

Personal appearance huge Mighty Dragon take-off, prevent arrival of that Fireball(s) with their statures.

Fireball(s) breaks up, brings innumerable disasters. forest is on fire, Rivers Flow is dry, earth chap. Entire world as if unceasing disintegration in the bombardment of that innumerable Fireball(s).

Mighty Dragon, with their statures unceasing resists arrivals of these Fireball(s), is protecting the entire world with their strength.

The body of Mighty Dragon from airborne Fallen, they seems face upwarding unceasingly sad cry, was summoning a name.

seven-colored ray of light arrived, huge and illusory Seven-colored Dragon horizontally in midair, massive Fireball(s) were prevented by it, blocks this world Ruin huge catastrophe finally reluctantly.

But, Dragon Clan was on the wane, the True Dragon casualty is serious, gives birth to the difficulties race regarding this, is almost Sheng Ji fades instantaneously.

The innumerable Mighty Dragon corpses, overspread the trim earth. Everywhere is dragon blood able to move unhindered.

These by Dragon Clan is protecting other races, under the infiltration of dragon blood, starts appear(ance) all sorts of mutations. Started to have belonged to their energy.

Soul Beast, is that Soul Beast? Is this origin of Soul Beast?

In the midair, that huge seven-colored Light and Shadow flaps pair of wings suddenly, Sky trembles, a appear(ance) giant crack, in the formidable suction hauling tread the innumerable Dragon Clan corpses soar, integrate in that crack.

Most Dragon Clan on earth vanished, surplus is also surviving a True Dragon clan is very few, even if living, already experienced personally the heavy losses.

Airborne crack slowly closed, attains seven-colored Light and Shadow also to integrate without a trace that in the crack vanishes.

A picture revolution. In the Tang Wulin field of vision presents, he had gone to impressively huge Dragon Clan Graveyard.

In that huge Graveyard, Dragon Clan corpse, field littered with corpses.

The years change, the body of Dragon Clan changes into the skeleton under the attack of time gradually slowly, the innumerable Dragon Clan skeletons, are bringing unequalled dismal aura, throughout exposes the corpse wilderness in that Dragon Clan Graveyard.

That seven-colored Light and Shadow assumes personal command center Dragon Clan Graveyard, on it in ray of light glittering, in the Dragon Clan corpse has ray of light to fly quietly to it, integrates slowly.

-------------------

Asked the monthly ticket, recommended the ticket.

#891: Harvest of Dragon Burying

All became illusory, Tang Wulin wanted to hold, is unable to succeed.

„” In screams, Tang Wulin sat fiercely, frightened nearby Gu Yue to jump.

„Daddy and Daddy!” Gu Yue hurries to grab his hand.

Tang Wulin somewhat fierce is panting for breath, is rapid to look to surroundings.

In forest, but that Infernal Demon Dragon King actually vanished to disappear.

takes a deep breath is mad several times, returned to normal own this time mood, Tang Wulin has calmed down gradually, he was intelligent, immediately realized that own and Gu Yue are also living now, should be related with seven-colored ray of light that formerly on chain bracelet released.

That Infernal Demon Dragon King should on seven-colored ray of light by own this chain bracelet run away in fear.

chain bracelet!

Tang Wulin subconscious lowering the head looks that just sees in the own wrist, that chain bracelet quiet lying down there, above seven-colored gem ray of light is as before partly visible, as if any Transformation has not resembled.

Why does not know, at this time Tang Wulin and between it, as if take shape a marvelous relation. His own does not talk clearly is anything, but with was different.

„Thank You (xiexie) and Thank You (xiexie) you have saved me and Gu Yue.” Tang Wulin heartfelt saying. He understands that this is Dragon Clan Graveyard, these dragon bone(s) give his back coupling.

Thousand day Dragon Burying, he has never thought must obtain anything, but Dragon Clan has actually given him the so precious gift. Although he has not known now that the outcome of this gem Crystallized Body representative is anything.

Without pressure that Ferocious Beast has created, the following road should be good to walk. Has a look at face kind Gu Yue, Tang Wulin to get hold of her hand, „I am all right, relax. We walk.”

Gu Yue nods, „scared to death me, just came several people. They said bewilderedly any words, I cannot understand. Afterward they walked.”

Several people? Then was one's turn Tang Wulin to receive to frighten. What concept here are appear(ance) several people? Several Ferocious Beast?

These Ferocious Beast are always impossible is Dragon Clan, but perhaps besides Dragon Clan, own that chain bracelet does not have any awesome effect. Finally they can actually is well, this be also considered as are the miracles.

„We walk quickly, must leave this piece of forest as soon as possible, here was too dangerous.” At the same time was saying, Tang Wulin carries simply Gu Yue, then in the direction that own recognizes, jumps, full speed vanguard.

Takes his cultivation as, in addition the direction of Blue Silver Emperor, full speed marches forward speed to be extremely quick. In forest various complex terrains and Plant, does not have anything to affect to him.

Those who made Tang Wulin somewhat surprised was, this line, unexpectedly again has not met any Soul Beast, two days, did not have any Soul Beast appear(ance) to attack them one after another. As if this is only piece of ordinary forest that's all.

Tang Wulin own somewhat is absent-minded, is this really the Star Dou Forest Nucleus circle? Whenever when he has a look at Emerald Demon Bird on Gu Yue shoulder, completely affirmed that this is not having a dream. Their real in this Star Dou Forest.

, Suddenly, the Tang Wulin heart lives warning sign(s) by far, put completely the footsteps. Because, in his field of vision of that Plant auxiliary reconnaissance, the front, forest arrived at the end finally.

But in the forest end, Tang Wulin saw the picture that made him shock extremely.

The dike, that is the dike, the metal(s) dike.

Beside this Star Dou Forest, actually has a metal(s) dike, the altitude over 300 meters of this metal(s) dike, must be higher than compared with the surroundings highest trees. Moreover, at this time to airborne looks following that metal(s) dike that Tang Wulin discovered that originally above this piece of big forest outside a kilometer upper air, actually has nearly transparent light cover.

Sees these, Tang Wulin first thinks is Prison Cage Two Word.

This Star Dou Forest Nucleus circle, once was surviving the most formidable Soul Beast place, turned into huge Prison Cage unexpectedly?

Nobody genuine knows here situation, because here already belonged to the Spirit Transferring Pagoda forbidden area.

An inexplicable sorrowful feeling gushes out instantaneously from the bottom of the heart. The Soul Beast final pure land, changed into a shackles that Spirit Transferring Pagoda has established unexpectedly.

He has actually studied the history, historically records, in the past, Ice Spirit Douluo Huo Yuhao established the Spirit Transferring Pagoda organization time, the goal was for Humanity and Soul Beast can the peaceful coexistence!

But presents in the present fact actually far from so. Soul Guidance Technology development of Humanity was really too quick. Relied on Battle Armor, Humanity Elite has definitely been able to suppress Soul Beast Elite. Humanity own, withstands the terrifying lethality that the high tech has brought.

Soul Master, once was Continent first profession, noblest profession, most formidable existence.

In the ancient times time's war, which side had strongest Soul Master, almost achieved 50% success.

May with the development of Soul Guidance Technology, Soul Master individual strength start becomes more and more tiny. Before looking like soon, total destruction that Shrek Academy is hit by.

Has that many Titled Douluo and Super Rank Douluo Shrek Academy, before placing Ten-thousand Years, at all some impossible people able its Ruin. But now, in two entire Humanity world most terrifying 12th Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell, without discovery, has brought a devastating catastrophe in advance.

Even if by Sky Raising Douluo Yun Ming, cultivation of one generation of Limit Douluo is, in addition Four Word Battle Armor, in addition Golden Tree strength, cannot block that devastating attack completely.

Humanity, becomes so fearful, can Soul Beast not move toward to exterminate?

Stops the footsteps, Tang Wulin was somewhat vacant, he somewhat is suddenly uninformed at sea, own so assiduous diligently cultivate, finally is the goal for what?

For Ruin? of course is not. He does not think Ruin anything.

Small time, cultivate, he hopes diligently own can change life in Shanjia, can become Mecha Master in dream.

Parents is missing, he tries hard cultivate, for some day, can retrieve the own family member.

But now, at this moment, his effort for what? Is relying on several companion that he and his is a rear survival. Can they rally Shrek really? Even if the energy, then, in the situation of nowadays so science and technology, Shrek can by once more Ruin?

time, Tang Wulin only thought that in heart has mixed emotions, is unable to restrain oneself.

„Daddy, you how?” Gu Yue has poked head, looks to standing there motionless Tang Wulin.

Wipes in the forced smile sound, Tang Wulin shakes the head, „not anything, but suddenly thinks somewhat at a loss. Thinks the road ahead to be boundless, how does not know should.”

Gu Yue blinked, „is not clear. Daddy in that where Gu Yue is.”

The Tang Wulin whole body shakes, so simple a few words, made in his heart surge nondescriptive lofty sentiments.

Yes! How finally, so is really important? The matter that at least, making own wants to handle, shoulders the responsibility that own should shoulder. Walks, even if own cannot arrive at most distant place finally as before, there are why not. At least, side own, she, they.

Gu Yue that Tang Wulin will carry on the back puts down, then has turned round, hugs into her the own bosom, closely is hugging.

The Gu Yue tender body is full of the elasticity soft, hugs in the bosom, enrichment particularly.

Light fragrance lingers in the tip of the nose, all exhausted, paces back and forth, pain and sad, warm burns in this in this moment. Burns flaming fighting intent.

Gu Yue clever bending down in the Tang Wulin bosom, is hugging his waist, on pretty face has, performs satisfies. Said in a soft voice: „Daddy......”

„Do not call me Daddy. Called me Wulin.”

„Wulin......”

The night falls, in nighttime sky, Star Dou glittering. Only then from some specific angles, can see, between forest and Star Dou, has such light light membrane impediment.

Tang Wulin and Gu Yue sit in the forest deep place, among the slit through tree's shadows looks up to Sky, Tang Wulin has not thought must from airborne clash.

Cannot achieve including these Ferocious Beast, why can he achieve?

Then, actually how can leave here?

Cannot assault, only be able to take by strategy.

Has not moved eagerly, without a doubt, that „dike” the defense strength certainly is very terrifying. It is not he small Five Rings Soul King can break through definitely.

But he believes that own definitely has the means to leave.

This several days, he calms the mind, is recalling Shrek City Ruin. In the heart also gradually had some clue.

Cannot indicate that the status leaves here, because, he does not trust the Spirit Transferring Pagoda person.

Spirit Transferring Pagoda General Headquarters and Shrek City are near at hand, but that two Kill the Gods have not actually fallen Spirit Transferring Pagoda, but has chosen Shrek and Tang Sect.

Shrek Academy Prestige and strength, as were been obvious by the strike target, then, between Tang Sect and Spirit Transferring Pagoda, is Spirit Transferring Pagoda must, at least on Douluo Continent be without a doubt so. Why these Evil Soul Master have not chosen Spirit Transferring Pagoda General Headquarters, but has chosen Tang Sect?

#892: Star Dou Stronghold

Did not have impeding of Shrek Academy and Tang Sect, who obtains benefits in a big way? Definitely is not the general publics, is not Soul Master.

Therefore, Tang Wulin cannot believe Spirit Transferring Pagoda easily, at this time, he does not dare to indicate the own status. Because, his status was really too sensitive.

As Shrek Academy Present Generation Shrek Seven Monsters, making that Holy Spirit Cult know that they are also living, without a doubt, they surely are the goals that the opposite party must kill.

Therefore, wants to go on living, first, his own must first protection good own diligently.

But, facing that impregnable dike, can leave here? Without doubt, this leave from the North Sea Corps seepage compared with initially them, is much more difficult much.

The space is not good, underground? Quick Tang Wulin denied the idea of own. Soul Beast many will also dig, on Ten-thousand Years experience by Spirit Transferring Pagoda, must guard against this point.

This really ascends the sky roadless, enters does not have the gate. To leave, is really not easy!

Gu Yue by Tang Wulin, a carefree appearance.

Tang Wulin is probing asking: „Can Gu Yue, show me your Storage Bracelet?” In the Gu Yue right hand wrist, fine silvery-white bracelet, on bracelet is mounting the transparent gem, without doubt portrays very High Rank Soul Guidance Method Array.

„.” Gu Yue handing over.

Looks at her lush element, in the Tang Wulin sudden heart acid, own and she confirmed after Sea God Fated Blind Date General Meeting the lover relates, anything has not actually given to her.

He from own storage ring, takes out together metal(s), this metal(s) presents all over the body is silvery-white, but itself in the slight(ly) rhythm, is unexpectedly ordinary just like the living creature.

The Tang Wulin right hand has pinched pinching on metal(s), strange appear(ance), that metal(s) unexpectedly likely is mud was pinched one by him.

Right hand Golden Dragon Claw springs, careful portray. Before long, a silver ring, on appear(ance) in the Tang Wulin hand.

Tang Wulin brings it on the left middle finger of Gu Yue, said with a smile: „Middle finger representative Passionately In Love. This is first block Soul Refinement metal(s) that my forging leaves, calculates that was very meaningful. Although has not inscribed any Nucleus method, but it is representing me to your regard. Gu Yue, do you like?”

On silvery-white ring not any special pattern, but there are two wraps in the together heart-shaped trace.

The Tang Wulin forging free time, but in this carving, did not have what special ability, can only be considered as on is fair. Only precious, is this is together Soul Refinement metal(s), but Soul Refinement metal(s) does not have a Nucleus method stimulation of movement, is harder than ordinary metal(s) and resiliency strong that's all.

But Tang Wulin looks at this ring, the expression in eye has actually filled gently.

Gu Yue has delivered his silver scales as the presenting a gift faith token, he also makes a return gift now to Gu Yue this ring.

„Thank You (xiexie) Daddy, no, Wulin.” Gu Yue smiles looks at the ring on own, on pretty face is revealing the smiling face of the heart.

Tang Wulin grips her hand, „my this life, will only deliver the ring to you. Entire life wholeheartedly person.”

„Good! Good!” Gu Yue applauds, cheering.

Tang Wulin laughs in spite of trying not, her as before likely child.

At this time, he has picked from Gu Yue wrist general her Storage Bracelet. In Gu Yue this Storage Bracelet, the thing are really many. Some bottles of cans, do not know that is any thing, inscribes Nucleus method metal(s), even also some instruments and so on thing. Actually is Tang Wulin does not know.

Looked for the moment, finally made him find several have been similar to Identification Card and token and so on thing.

It is not clear regarding Spirit Transferring Pagoda internal organizational structure Tang Wulin, but by the Gu Yue status, passes and out here should not to have the issue. Otherwise, initially did they come in?

Tang Wulin bracelet gives back to Gu Yue, then starts to give own cosmetics .

Cannot delay again, Gu Yue loses remembers that they must leave here as soon as possible. Then can find the place to help her treat!

However, now Gu Yue is unconscious, he also needs to carry on training to her, can move.

Two days later.

Spirit Transferring Pagoda Star Dou Stronghold.

Star Dou Stronghold from establishment to the present, already over three Thousand Years history. Before three Thousand Years, numerous position Ferocious Beast of Star Dou Forest Nucleus circle routs after a war loses, Spirit Transferring Pagoda makes use to establish this stronghold, and reaches the agreement with numerous Ferocious Beast, Humanity no longer continues to fell forest. But Ferocious Beast also live here.

If the Ferocious Beast assault Humanity defense line, then, Humanity has the right to strike to kill rashly, but if Humanity enters in forest, Ferocious Beast also greatly may kill it, was not affected by the contract.

It seems, both sides seem to be equal. But when Star Dou Stronghold lasts to count Hundred Year, genuine completes, the Star Dou Forest Nucleus circle, actually won to turn into genuine prison cell.

Soul Beast look like rears in a pen here, but Spirit Transferring Pagoda can actually the sell dear enter here admission ticket. Life and Death is proud, but only here, has Soul Beast of high equivalent to make Soul Master be possible to have Top Rank Soul Ring.

Ferocious Beast want to renege on a promise again, already late. They are not the Humanity matches.

Relies on the Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell array, the Mecha regiment, Top Rank Battle Armor Master is coordinating screen defense, making Ferocious Beast be unable to escape even with wings, can only bear patiently in big forest.

But Spirit Transferring Pagoda does not have to force, after completing the whole has reared in a pen, no longer disturbs these Soul Beast to live, but occasionally allows some people to enter. As for going in whether to be living coming out, was very difficult saying that only if paid the extremely high expense or resources again, can dispatch Elite to protect by Spirit Transferring Pagoda.

But Spirit Transferring Pagoda such procedure, obtained the Federation agreement, the reason is very simple, as the matter stands, Soul Beast will be nothing left regarding the threat of Humanity, during all are controlling.

„Monkey, your side how is it?” Star Dou Stronghold advocates in the screen Control tower, wears the female of uniform to ask through communications device.

„Sister Xing, me all normal. All screen pressurizing valves are normal.” Another side hears a somewhat high-pitched and fine male voice.

„Receives.”

Sister Xing advocates one of the Control tower heads, is responsible for the supervisory work of all equipment, every day needs to conduct the routine inspection, to guarantee that all equipment revolve normally.

Several Thousand Years come, Star Dou Stronghold screen constantly strengthens. Now is legend Elite in Beast God that stage, wants to clash hardly, needs to continue All-Out attack several hours to have the possibility, but had that time words, Spirit Transferring Pagoda already can assemble Elite to come to deal.

Stretches oneself, on the Sister Xing face reveals the color of relaxation, inspects all normally, did not have any issue. Then is relaxed a day.

Although Star Dou Stronghold is similar to the military base seals up generally, but various internal entertainment facilities are perfect, will not be bored. Yesterday evening, she has drunk many liquor in the bar. However, as a profession female, particularly technician, regardless has what kind of life the day before, will not affect her second day work and specialization.

„Di Di!” In this time, the communications device aspect is suddenly resounding.

„Well.” Sister Xing hurries to look to front screen.

„What situation?” Sister Xing hurries to ask.

„Reported the control tower. Prepares Spirit Transferring Envoy(s) Miss Gu Yuena, was requested to return by interior. Simultaneously also has Spirit Transferring Envoy(s) Sir Xu Shengqun to accompany.”

Sister Xing said: „After inspection identification, can allow to pass.”

„Yes!”

Sister Xing shuts off the communication, [say / way] that thought aloud: „These Sir Spirit Transferring Envoy(s), always enter using the privilege transmission of own, did not greet ahead of time. Really.”

„Di Di.”

„How?” Sister Xing ill-humored presses the communication, she only wants to go back to make up now as soon as possible thinks.

------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#893: Enters stronghold

„Sir Xu Shengqun has not carried identification. Sir Gu Yuena identification is normal. How to process?”

Sister Xing has gawked, „doesn't have the identification? What situation?”

„Sir Xu Shengqun said that he forgot to bring......”

In Sister Xing heart one cold, sinking sound track: „Forgot to bring? How possible. Leads them to observation room first, then asked the supervisory brigade to go, rapid repatriation.”

„Yes.”

The front huge metal(s) strobe opens slowly, Tang Wulin and Gu Yue lead the way shoulder to shoulder, this time he, is a face with deep veneration, the look completely is the Xu Shengqun appearance. Stature, to body changed the Xu Shengqun appearance through Control of strength of Soul Power and bloodline. The body has changed an ordinary long gown. Gu Yue follows side him, is very respectful appearance.

„Sir Xu Shengqun, because you have not carried the identification, when therefore we need by supervisory brigade your status, to follow the miter guide to go to the observation room. Sir Gu Yuena, your status verified correct, the approval enters.”

Gu Yuena? Hears to the Gu Yue idiom, the Tang Wulin heart shakes. Subconscious looks to Gu Yue, why did they call her Gu Yuena?

If before, his of course will not produce anything to have doubts, the name is code number that's all. But, present Gu Yue, has the Na'er appearance! This is different.

Although in the heart shocks, at this time he is actually very calm gentle. After all, must first be able to leave this stronghold to be good.

„Does not use, I follow Sir Xu Shengqun to carry on the status confirmation together.” Gu Yue declined directly.

At this time, was similar to square box metal(s) splits the wall place to enter from the front extremely, above had several indicating lamp glittering, „please two adults come with me.”

Then, square box marches forward in front, a metal(s) door opened, leading them to enter a metal(s) road.

Enters here, not having the assistance of Plant, Tang Wulin only to rely on own Spiritual Strength sensation surroundings. But he discovered quickly that this is the futile effort. surroundings metal(s) jade thickness enough over two feet . Moreover the interior has certainly Soul Guidance energy to pour into, it can be said that is impregnable. Even if Titled Douluo rank Elite wants to clash from here unable to achieve hardly. Let alone other.

This stronghold defense so firm, wants not to expose to leave here, the difficulty is really not small!

Follows that robot to pass through the road, enters a leaf of weighty metal(s) gate, then arrived at one similarly is in airtight metal(s) spatial. Can see, in each corner of this room, Soul Guidance Device of many powerful forces is pointing at the room.

This should be the so-called observation room.

Tang Wulin sat on the chair directly, an old god in the appearance, Gu Yue stands side him, the expression is indifferent and calm. Before her such.

In order to makes her maintain such condition, yesterday Tang Wulin may not have really little time-consumingly.

time is not long, the front wall splits, several people walked from outside, they all are fully-armed, grasps Soul Guidance Device. surroundings all Soul Guidance Device immediately have also shone, all aims at Tang Wulin and Gu Yue two people. So long as without a doubt, they have changed, then, immediately by all-around attack.

Is a that person seems over 40 years old an age, goes forward several steps, the facial expression indifferent [say / way]: „Xu Shengqun hasn't Spirit Transferring Envoy(s), why carried the identification?”

„Forgot.” Tang Wulin light saying.

Supervisor complexion serious [say / way]: „You are the Spirit Transferring Pagoda high level, violates the rule, will impose the punishment, please learn about.”

„Knew.” Tang Wulin sounds/voices also completely is imitation Xu Shengqun, it can be said that is lifelike.

The supervisors said: „Below starts to verify your status. Please carry on the fingerprint and iris confirmation.”

At the same time was saying, another monitors officers took the instrument to walk.

Tang Wulin when follows Old Devil to study seepage, had studied, wants to carry on a perfect seepage, must first do, must have way (of life) at least over 60% success ratio. Then in the penetration process, through the observation and adjustment, making the success ratio promote gradually.

Without a doubt, such situation, he observes at present again, does not help matters. To promote the success ratio not to be impossible.

Tang Wulin along with it standing up, seems must carry on the fingerprint and iris test. But flickers below, he has held in the arms Gu Yue suddenly like lightning, simultaneously the personal appearance explodes draws back at the same time, a hand has pinched in the Gu Yue throat place.

Soul Guidance Device of these Defense System series, come on reaction instantaneously, jumps projects innumerable rays, covers to the Tang Wulin body.

But at this moment, Tang Wulin has made very unusual reaction, his whole person draws Gu Yue to go backward but actually. Covers own with the body of Gu Yue. Meanwhile, Huang Mengmeng's halo expands instantaneously, covers above the Gu Yue body.

rays falls above that yellow ray of light, immediately scatters to separate, Tang Wulin also entrained Gu Yue to fall back on the corner. In this position, at least does not need to be attacked by the enemy on all sides.

„Stops attack, otherwise has killed her!” Tang Wulin ice-cold sounds/voices spreads over the audience.

All attack stop suddenly. That several supervisors also had a scare. Such situation they are first time bump into. But Gu Yue coordinates, on face reveals the surprise and frightened look.

Right, Gu Yue is the Tang Wulin last resort. Without a doubt, in Spirit Transferring Pagoda, the Gu Yue status quite did not lower, moreover there is achievement Spirit Transferring Pagoda Vice Pagoda Master Teacher(s). Forces the Spirit Transferring Pagoda aspect to allow to pass with her Life, there are certainly assuring, although this assurance should but actually 60%. But if the Gu Yue comprehensive coordination, that was also similar.

In does not have in other opportunities situations shortly, Tang Wulin can only be this bad plan. Protects yellow ray of light of Gu Yue body, came from his Mountain Dragon King Torso Bone. In order to hide the own identity, does not arrive cannot, he will not release own Martial Soul and Battle Armor.

„Who you are! You are not Sir Spirit Transferring Envoy(s).” The supervisors get angry shout to clear the way.

Tang Wulin cold snort one, „my of course is not, but you should confirm, the girl in my hands, is your Spirit Transferring Pagoda practical high level. Puts me to leave here, otherwise, I have killed her. At the worst perishes together, gives you five minutes, opens the door, puts me to exit.”

[Say / Way] that the supervisors let somebody cool off or calm down: „Useless, you cannot be inescapable. Puts down to prepare Sir Spirit Transferring Envoy(s), opportunity that you have fairly handled.”

Prepares Spirit Transferring Envoy(s)? In the Tang Wulin heart moves, the opposite party did not say that he has not known the Gu Yue status.

He knows that in Spirit Transferring Pagoda, besides Pagoda Master and two Vice Pagoda Master, was Four Great Spirit Transferring Envoys. Has not thought that the Gu Yue small age, arrived unexpectedly has prepared Spirit Transferring Envoy(s) stage, although time of this preparation will be long, but also sufficiently showed that Spirit Transferring Pagoda to her attaching great importance, this regarding Tang Wulin, was more advantageous.

Mountain Dragon King Torso Bone supplements the Soul Skill Mountain Dragon imperial release, Tang Wulin is forcing Gu Yue, while walks toward that several supervisors.

„Few idle talk, open the door. Otherwise has killed her.”

The ear-piercing alarm sound has resounded in entire Star Dou Stronghold at this time.

Sister Xing that must go back to rest hears the warning, has to watch here situation, various internal defense facility urgent starts at the same time, various types of instruments are also carrying on analysis.

„Showed according to the data that invades the Guard Screen protection intensity of enemy is 1065, ordinary rays kind of Soul Guidance Device is unable to break through. Needs to shell by big might Soul Guide Cannon, may rout it. But will certainly injure the hostage.”

The analysis data came out quickly, Tang Wulin Mountain Dragon imperial defense is greatly strengthened, compared favorably with the Seven Rings Defense System Soul Master defense strength sufficiently. In this case, wants in does not injure to the Gu Yue situation in kills him towering, that completely is the impossible matter. Even if ambushes rays unable to achieve.

The supervisors and Tang Wulin are confronting, here situation without doubt already rapidly to the Star Dou Stronghold high-level transmission.

Just like Tang Wulin expectation such, after several minutes, when Gu Yue looks the color of pain, when the Tang Wulin whole body blooms the intense murderous intention. The opposite party compromised finally. metal(s) large door opening.

However, after going out of metal(s) large door, Tang Wulin faces, is actually already densely covered dozens Mecha here, as well as revolving of several Battle Armor Master.

„Gets out of the way, otherwise has killed her.” The Tang Wulin sudden hysteria roars, on the whole person bursts out an unprecedented madness flavor, the a pair of eye turned into blood-red.

Wish makes the match believe that you will kill one held for ransom, enough madness that then, must first display. This initially Old Devil taught the Tang Wulin original words.

------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#894: Clashes

If the match felt that you are not that firm, will possibly seek for the opportunity to kill him through unceasing protracted time. Without a doubt, dragging time more longer, regarding Tang Wulin, is more disadvantageous.

At the same time was saying, he has hugged Gu Yue to jump, directly soars frontage purple Mecha to flush away.

Saw that in front of that purple Mecha, the Tang Wulin personal appearance half revolution, a foot trampled in that Mecha shoulder place.

„Bang” a bang, that Mecha is flown, pounded following several Mecha that his terrifying great strength trampled directly.

„strength judgment, over 150,000 kilograms. Mecha damages 21%.”

Is this Humanity?

On the control tower has concentrated the massive Star Dou Stronghold high levels, after they saw terrifying strength that Tang Wulin releases, first time judges, this seems is similar to Xu Shengqun, but the whole body is sending out the madness flavor fellow, should be Soul Beast is right. Also has Soul Beast, may have so formidable strength.

Ferocious Beast escapes no doubt importantly, but relatively speaking, is prepares Spirit Transferring Envoy(s) Gu Yuena to be without doubt more important. Under the Tang Wulin powerful forces, Mecha successively retreat.

If the request of Tang Wulin is opening entire Star Dou Stronghold Guard Screen, this is obviously impossible to comply, if only its own wants to run, then on easy many. Only needs following to chase down again and that's the end.

Runs out of the Mecha densely covered road, Tang Wulin cannot identify the position, but he knows roughly where is the Star Dou Forest direction, where is the surrounding. Therefore in the general orientation will not have the issue.

Across several roads, although some massive Spirit Transferring Pagoda Elite, but Tang Wulin does not have any meaning of stop.

But, these roads strange eight circle, this way, his sense of direction must have problems.

Without a doubt, these Spirit Transferring Pagoda Elite are waiting for the opportunity, once he exposes weaknesses, or physical exertion oversized time, very possible opposite party to kill to him strikes, thus under rescuing Gu Yue.

Cannot conventional walked.

Tang Wulin stops the footsteps, a hand forces Gu Yue as before, another hand while turning round, shells suddenly to behind wall.

The low and deep dragon roar sound gets up, the strength of bloodline transfers, actually does not appear scales.

Enough over 200,000 jin (0.5 kg) terrifying great strength bombardments maliciously on the metal(s) wall.

In the fierce bellow, that thickness exceeds one foot, the interior also has the energy protection metal(s) wall immediately large scale inside depression. Tang Wulin elbow counter-attack, is.

Voice that only collides, on the scene is fearful and apprehensive on fluctuation numerous Spirit Transferring Pagoda Elite.

So three times, a giant hole on appear(ance) in Tang Wulin behind, has revealed quite open spatial. He is bringing Gu Yue without hesitation flushed. Then before the correct direction in his impression continues clashes, to the place, immediately has shelled with pure strength.

If the Spirit Transferring Pagoda aspect has energy screen appear(ance), Tang Wulin threatens on so as to Gu Yue Life immediately, but does not have in situation that energy protects, his strong strange strength is the unceasingly rumbling broken wall stiffly.

Even if the Spirit Transferring Pagoda aspect indicated that must lead him to move toward to export Tang Wulin not to pay attention, uses this extremely overbearing way (of life), seeks outlet that his own is wanting.

„Bang”, when his seventh bombardment wall, the wall was actually only appear(ance) a small dent. If the beforehand wall has one foot thick, this time, Tang Wulin discovers front metal(s) jade, at least over five meters thick, even if by his strength, was impossible to clash.

But he at this time is actually not startled counter- happy, as armed stronghold, defense strength strongest without doubt is the surrounding. Very possible they to arrive at outer wall.

What to do? Old means. pure strength is not good, he also has other way (of life).

Blocks own by the body of Gu Yue, the left hand releases Golden Dragon Claw quietly, back to the wall direction, to that wall according to going.

Right hand Golden Dragon Claw properties is crushing, but left hand Golden Dragon Claw properties is shredding. Under strength of attention tyrannical bloodline, Golden Dragon Claw unceasing tears down weighty metal(s), flings to fly to the front to surround their these Spirit Transferring Pagoda Elite them again. The free time of a while, was ripped open a crack by Tang Wulin, he and Gu Yue body all hid.

At this time, anything monitored equipment unable to see clearly inside situation, Tang Wulin both hands were uneven, Gu Yue kept off in front of him, Golden Dragon Claw and Dark Gold Fearful Claw All-Out displayed, sufficiently person of general passageway that by his unceasing digging up stiffly.

Can take alloy of stronghold outer wall, the hard degree can be imagined, but don't forget, Tang Wulin was Blacksmith, he enough knew about metal(s), therefore, can see appear(ance) of metal(s) fragment(s) unceasingly before them, the body of Tang Wulin and Gu Yue was actually more and more thorough in.

Spirit Transferring Pagoda Elite are also being in a daze that somewhat looks, simultaneously their also even more affirmation Tang Wulin was the Ferocious Beast status. If outside person seeps, then impossible not to know about here, will not adopt so barbaric way (of life) to break through.

What may let some of their also not knowing whether to laugh or cry, this very barbaric way (of life), actually appears very easy-to-use.

The back, the fresh air from behind assails. Tang Wulin discovered immediately that they were come out finally. stronghold outer layer wall, stiffly had dug out a hole by him. Looks outward, from ground more than hundred meters appearances.

Wipes the light smile along with it reappearing on the Tang Wulin face. Came out.

Gu Yue has turned head, relative Tang Wulin said anything, had actually been covered the mouth by Tang Wulin. At this time, once Gu Yue making noise made the opposite party discover that this Gu Yue non- was other Gu Yue, that may be big on the trouble. These many Spirit Transferring Pagoda Elite, the casualness can rip fragment(s) them.

A hand holds in the arms the waist of Gu Yue, in her screams, Tang Wulin has soared, directly soars in the ground to fall.

The altitudes of hundred rice for him at all are not anything, whereabouts about 60-70 meters time, his right foot treads on stronghold, the human has been similar to arrow dart leaps up, shifts like lightning, bringing Gu Yue to dash to go toward the distant place.

Their this comes out, outside over 60 Mecha come in swarms immediately. And is the head, unexpectedly is Red Mecha.

„You have been separated from stronghold, puts down the hostage, asking you to leave.” The electronic combination tone from the sky reverberates.

Tang Wulin loudly exclaimed: „You don't with me, after one hour, I let loose the hostage. When you I am silly? Now has put the hostage, will you keep the promise?”

„Leave to me, with me, I starts to tear up person qualitative body certain parts again, throws to you.” At the same time is roaring, the Tang Wulin right hand flings, the Gu Yue coat flew.

Gu Yue somewhat discontented digs red lips, but is actually obedient has not opened the mouth.

Really, the Gu Yue clothes fly, behind pursuing troops immediately on slow. Tang Wulin is leading her, All-Out dashes about wildly with lightning speed, being able choose the exact way because of flurry recognizes a direction to flee.

To be separated from Control not to have is so simple, Spirit Transferring Pagoda is having the Federation highest-level science and technology absolutely, the range that only the radar can cover is quite huge, let alone they can also ask the Federation military to coordinate.

Therefore, after Tang Wulin brings Gu Yue is drilling into woods, he immediately releases own Blue Silver Emperor.

With Blue Silver Emperor and communication of surroundings Plant, this all covers their aura. Meanwhile, Tang Wulin digs out a burrow in shrubberies rapidly, bringing Gu Yue to worm one's way into.

Mountain Dragon imperial launches, keeps off the soil in the body outer layer, is relying on the a pair of Golden Dragon Claw downward excavation, at this time Tang Wulin has used All-Out, is only several minutes of time, he has deep cut below hundred meters.

#895: Suffers small alluring woman of person

Strong radar, so long as specifically does not aim at underground, is impossible to survey the bottom deep place hundred meters to have anything.

The Gu Yue volt carries on the back in Tang Wulin, both hands are holding his neck, Tang Wulin by the a pair of dragon claw opening, directly soars the front excavation.

His is not motion of being able choose the exact way because of flurry, but before because, when jumps down from stronghold, he sees not far away to have grand river. This should originally across Star Dou Forest Rivers Flow, because afterward forest was felled, Rivers Flow exposes. The river breadth an approximately hundred meters water depth does not know. But this is the best escaping route that he chooses.

„No. Lost their trail.”

„Rug search. Under land detector.”

The Spirit Transferring Pagoda aspect, has swiftly surrounded this piece of forest. But all surveyed equipment actually not to find Tang Wulin and Gu Yuena trail, as if they baseless disappeared.

After several minutes, the tunnel entrance of Tang Wulin excavation was discovered that but, the tunnel has closed. Needs to unearth is good, words that but, unearths, can find the road cotton suiting that they unearth?

When massive underground Detector ship , after is 15 minutes. Underground within surrounding area dozens li (0.5km) range searches to observe, has not discovered any large-scale Life sign. Tang Wulin and Gu Yuena, such baseless vanished.

„Whish......” in water sound, Tang Wulin and Gu Yue are almost simultaneously appeared from the water.

The cool river water goes downstream, leads their bodies to continue to forward.

Tang Wulin turns head to look, Star Dou Stronghold already in them behind beyond dozens li (0.5km), right, he has dug in the tunnel in the river water, draws support from the river water again the momentum, delivers them, has gone downstream, does not need to take many efforts, has been far away from the spot.

Tang Wulin is holding the hand of Gu Yue, hugs into her the own bosom, the gentle voice asked: „Is cold?”

Gu Yue shakes the head, although she lost has recalled, but cultivated for also, where had is sensitive to cold.

„Daddy, you were quite a moment ago fearful, you to they roared, I frighten.” Gu Yue discontented [say / way].

Tang Wulin said with a smile: „Such words, how cannot make them believe that I truly can threaten your Life! Has been all right, they are impossible to discover our. To a downstream point place, after coming ashore, I help you melt a makeup, then we change clothes again, did not have the issue.”

„Oh, Daddy, I am hungry.” Gu Yue is hugging his neck, at this time, their clothes had been soaked by the river water, this pastes, Tang Wulin feels a whole body dryness and heat immediately. That fills youth aura * in bosom, is not really small to his stimulation.

„Gu Yue, you can think why they will call you Gu Yuena?” Tang Wulin asked. This question, has been similar to his heart the haze is ordinary, for a very long time does not go.

Gu Yue shakes the head at a loss, but embraces tightly him.

In the Tang Wulin heart sighed one darkly, it seems like can only , when Gu Yue restored the memory to say again.

Continues to go downstream about five and six kilometers. When Tang Wulin saw river bank not far High-speed road interlocks, this brings Gu Yue to come ashore.

„Trades to do the clothes, father......, I bring the thing that you look to eat.” Tang Wulin subconscious has almost said Daddy, made his own also awkwardness.

„Daddy, I cannot.” In the Gu Yue big eye full is pure.

The Tang Wulin corners of the mouth pull out, won't change the clothes?

At this time, Gu Yue that graceful personal appearance, because the clothes soak, almost appears in him at present, Tang Wulin only thinks a surface hot heartbeat.

„Your this suffers small alluring woman of person.” Tang Wulin groaned, looked for road nearby corner, took out one set of her clothes from Gu Yue Storage Bracelet fast, blushes trades to her. Gu Yue does not have anything actually, Tang Wulin is reaction is fierce.

„Daddy, are you very hot? Your face so is how red!” Gu Yue winks the big eye to ask.

„!” Tang Wulin lifted the hand to clap a palm of the hand on her outstanding buttocks, „shut up.”

„Not!” Gu Yue discontented digs red lips.

When Tang Wulin with is not inferior in restraining the Golden Dragon King bloodline breakthrough the painful certainly big will, has not made own do any impulsive matter.

Even if two sentiments likes each other, he does not hope, when Gu Yue loses remembers makes anything to her.

After she changes the clothes, Tang Wulin also fast has changed dry clothes to own. Then was drawing on Gu Yue road, then released his Tang Sect Combat Car, camouflage became the appearance of ordinary vehicles, was bringing Gu Yue along the road the line, was far away fast.

Had Combat Car, this speed quicker must much, through identifying the street sign, Tang Wulin discovered quickly their this roads march forward to the East.

Has not returned to the Shrek City direction eagerly, he drives to a High-speed road after the recent small city, has gotten down High-speed, enters the city. To own and Gu Yue put on make-up on the vehicle.

„Daddy, how you aged.” Gu Yue looks that completed senile cosmetics Tang Wulin to own, frown asked.

Tang Wulin helpless [say / way]: „You always manage me to call Daddy, this most nature! Later you little spoke.”

„, Is this is unattractive.” Gu Yue mumbled one.

Tang Wulin leads her to get out, enters small Hotel, opened two rooms, first has settled.

Turns on the Soul Guidance television screen of Hotel room, his complexion also gradually becomes sinks to congeal.

Shrek City had such giant disaster, he believes that at this time in the television should all be the related news.

Experienced the drastic change, then also had the experience in Star Dou Forest, Tang Wulin now the heart was completely calm, the matter occurred, many sad and painful not any significance. First must face the present situation, then finds the way to change. He lives here, mainly for must clear off the mentality, must clarify own then to make anything.

He is very clear, own can such quickly live in the mood on the stability, cannot separate in the side with Gu Yue. Some Lover, him have certainly the big power.

„Shrek City encounters to the unprecedented catastrophe suddenly, Federation Duty-bound Responsibility. Federation Parliament announced dismisses, will pick a lucky day again the election.”

„Shrek City slain population initial statistics are over 12 million people, the wounded about 2 million. The scope of large cities preserves less than one-third, loses is hard to count. Shrek Academy disappears thoroughly, Tang Sect General Headquarters broken not entire. Shows according to the eyewitness and satellite image. If the non- final time, Shrek Academy Present Generation Sea God Pavilion Pavilion Master Sky Raising Douluo Your Excellency All-Out to go to has blocked two Kill the Gods Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell majority of mighty energy, perhaps the company was more remote Spirit Transferring Pagoda General Headquarters to be exploded affects.”

„The Federation military has formed investigation group, investigates two Kill the Gods Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell missing reasons. The commander in chief said that certainly not at any cost will find the murderer. This inhuman massacre, is Continent is unprecedented. The military deeply mourns for the victim.”

„Across Continent, Shrek Academy graduating cadet holds the mourning activities, the victim of express profound condolence Shrek massacre.”

„Tang Sect announced that declares war to Holy Spirit Cult. But according to the insider news, Tang Sect this loss is serious. General Headquarters was destroyed, at least has over four Hall Master Fallen, Tang Sect Douluo Hall Hall Master is missing. At present this station reporter is following up the newest news.”

„Holy Spirit Cult expressed that is responsible for this terrorist attack, but so far, does not have, no matter what how trail. Here, this appeal, all people, once were discovered the suspicious personnel, immediately reports to the local administration official mansion.”

„Some hearsay said that third Kill the Gods Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell also with another two same missing. If this is real, then, next by Kill the Gods Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell attack, which city will be? Is the Federation government, actually doing?”

Various chaotic news broadcast in Soul Guidance television each channel unceasingly. Tang Wulin looks at the same time, his both hands have gripped tightened the fist. The nail falls into the palm not to be unconscious.

Even if before this time, he also places hopes in all these is illusory, like initially them on Devil Island, all was illusion that Old Devil made. This is just Nightmare.

But, the fact puts at present, without a doubt, this is not Nightmare. Looks in the picture, in Shrek City that two giant gulf, looks at surroundings broken Shrek City that remnant of destroyed building the appearance. Tang Wulin eyes flood red.

12 million people slain! This is 12 million living Life! Such did not have.

Shrek that the Continent first city, day does not fall, has more than 20,000 years of inheritance Shrek Academy fully, such did not have.

The enemies are how ruthless spicily. Brutal.

Closes the television, sits there, Tang Wulin is motionless for a very long time. He is returning to normal the own state of mind, these news that analysis was just obtaining.

#896: He is also living!

Judging from the present situation, Shrek City suffered the heavy losses, Shrek Academy all extinguished basically, Tang Sect General Headquarters all extinguished. The loss is countless.

Currently speaking, without any report about companions.

Holy Spirit Cult!

Alone is Holy Spirit Cult, can make such degree terrorist attack? Does the military eat without working really? 12th Rank is Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell so easy to be stolen? Involves, perhaps is not only Evil Soul Master Sect is so simple. In this has certainly more things.

Shrek City existence, in Federation is a different number. But Federation does not dare to Shrek City, after all, its status so to be how lofty.

But from this large explosion, Federation is relying on these Super Rank weapons, in fact already had to cope with Shrek ability. But they do not have the means to do. Can this be Federation wants to remove Shrek, but borrowed the Evil Soul Master name? Also or, Federation certain people and Evil Soul Master cooperated, have destroyed Shrek City.

This evil reputation buckles on Holy Spirit Cult, Holy Spirit Cult does not matter, they are the targets of universal detestation. But the goals of certain people have also been achieved, does not have influence of Shrek Academy on Continent, certain careerists obviously the matter that is easy to be them to handle.

But specific situation Tang Wulin is not clear, after all, he to political not any research.

Tang Sect General Headquarters also suffered the attack of devastating, is very obvious, Tang Sect is the same with Shrek Academy, very much receives the hierarchs to dread. This time massacre is not certainly simple.

Spirit Transferring Pagoda?

Tang Sect, Shrek Academy and Spirit Transferring Pagoda, are the Super Rank organizations that and said. Why Tang Sect and Shrek Academy were hit by the total destruction, but Spirit Transferring Pagoda doesn't General Headquarters have anything near at hand?

From the threat angle to Evil Soul Master, Spirit Transferring Pagoda must surpass Tang Sect, at least outwardly on strength is so. Moreover Soul Master quantity and strength of Spirit Transferring Pagoda General Headquarters accumulation, certainly above Tang Sect. But second Kill the Gods Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell has not actually looked for Spirit Transferring Pagoda, but falls on Tang Sect General Headquarters. Doesn't have what dirty in?

Although Tang Wulin is not suspected that Spirit Transferring Pagoda and Evil Soul Master collude, but at least this possibility is not nonexistent.

Therefore, present Spirit Transferring Pagoda is fly-by-night. Why this is also he not in the reason that in Star Dou Forest indicates the status. At present, nobody knows that their Shrek Seven Monsters is also living. In this case, hides in wants on to be much better in secret absolutely outwardly.

The Holy Spirit Cult strength is more formidable than the imagination, on that day that huge Skeleton head of appear(ance), above at least had cultivation of Evil Soul Master to should not be inferior in Sky Raising Douluo many.

Let alone, starts such disaster -type terrorist attack, the trace vanished in the large explosion basically. To nose is very difficult, but is looks up, present they are weak, could not make anything.

After thinking clear these, Tang Wulin understands, matter that now he most should handle actually only then, is, bears patiently!

He needs, not only individual strength, must have enough influence, is good with the influence of Evil Soul Master resistance.

Opens both eyes slowly, before Tang Wulin arrives at window. Although opened two rooms, but at this time he and Gu Yue in a room.

Gu Yue rolls up on the bed, had already rested ripe, the whole person is binding the quilt, the long hair hangs loose, the long eyelash builds on the cheek, beautiful looks like a foreign-style doll of large size.

Looked at her one eyes, in the Tang Wulin heart has stabilized several points immediately. Looks again to out of the window. He puts out own Soul Guide Communication Device slowly, starting.

Allocates the number.

Tang Wulin heartbeat inexplicably somewhat anxious, if this number is unable to put through, for him, will have the enormous influence. This number is deciding, he is whether lonely.

„Wulin?” Somewhat rapid sounds/voices transmits from another side, when Tang Wulin hears this sounds/voices, the whole person slightly shakes.

Forcibly takes a deep breath tone, but his sounds/voices unconscious shivering somewhat, „Xinglan, I am all right.”

Another side suddenly peaceful, in Tang Wulin somewhat anxious inexplicable, therefore time, the deafening cheers transmit from the receiver suddenly.

In an instant, Tang Wulin has tears streaming down the face, he heard their sounds/voices. In that sounds/voices has Ye Xinglan, has Xie Xie, Yuan En, Le Zhengyu, Xu Xiaoyan and Xu Lizhi. They, freely their sounds/voices, because excessively excitedly becomes some hysterias, but Tang Wulin actually as before can distinguish each of them's sounds/voices clearly.

Is they, is they. They are living, they are good.

Tang Wulin only thinks in the own throat to sob, could not speak completely.

Regarding them, this is survivor of disaster absolutely!

„Boss and Boss.” Xie Xie wept and wailed is transmitting sounds/voices from the microphone.

„Um.” Tang Wulin has complied with one, suppressed the own mood reluctantly, ability that this restores to speak.

„Where Boss are you at? Are you also living really? I am not am having a dream.” Xie Xie sounds/voices fierce is shivering, Tang Wulin can definitely feel his sounds/voices at this moment that excited.

„I am also living, I am all right. Was Gu Yue has saved me. She left my faith token to transmit her promptly, then also led me to transmit the distant place. I am all right now, in being away from Shrek City in about 200 kilometers small city. I do not even know the name of city, you? You now where? Is everybody good?”

Ye Xinglan brings back Soul Guide Communication Device from the Xie Xie hand, „we are all right, now in Heaven Dou City. Holy Spirit Douluo Your Excellency is also all right, is only her mood......”

Holy Spirit Douluo? The Tang Wulin whole body shakes, yes! On that day Holy Spirit Douluo probably was also only the stupor, she was also living. Some such Super Rank Douluo are also living, this simply was good. But thinks of her and Yun Ming sentiment, a Tang Wulin anxiety.

Puts oneself in another's place, if Gu Yue had an accident, own will be painful?

„You comfort Your Excellency first well, I come to converge with you as soon as possible. Also, Xinglan, now at this time, do not relate any side, including Tang Sect. Academy has destroyed, but we are strong. Like such that Pavilion Master finally said that we were the Academy final hopes. Only has us to live well, Academy is hopeful. Now, we must protect good own first, yes? Therefore, cannot expose the status. Best is the time is maintaining cosmetics .”

„Yes, I also think.” Ye Xinglan said: „Before we come Heaven Dou City, is cosmetics , has not contacted with anybody. On that day we saw probably are Gu Yue appear(ance), but we did not determine that you were also being lived by that Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell Ruin. Therefore after arriving here, we have been waiting. Wulin, you come, we are waiting for you, you also pay attention to the security.”

Tang Wulin can hear, calm calm Ye Xinglan, at this time in sounds/voices actually has always been full of the feeling of being mentally and physically exhausted.

„Good, waits for me, I pass as soon as possible. Maintains the contact.”

Hung up Soul Guide Communicator, Tang Wulin has wiped tears on face, then long air vent.

Finally, companion are also living, at this time, what ratio this better news but also there is?

In his heart also gradually had has decided the idea. First converges with companion, then finds the way to treat good Gu Yue. Again, how to look for the opportunity to restore Shrek.

Must use resources that all can use, Heaven Dou City, truly is a good place.

Is taking Soul Guide Communication Device, after he hesitated slightly one next, closed communications device.

At this time, he can think can help own, two people, one is his is Innate Body Sect Sect Master Teacher(s), another naturally is his Divine Craftsman Rank other Senior Teacher.

But now at this time, he eagerly had not contacted them, first arrived at Heaven Dou City to say again. Moreover, Holy Spirit Cult act is so vicious, the Senior Teacher situation perhaps will be very then unsafe. As Continent only Divine Craftsman , he although directly does not threaten Holy Spirit Cult, but he can actually continually make Four Word Battle Armor Master.

Returns to the bedside, when Tang Wulin lies down on the bed, an exhausted feeling spreads over the whole body instantaneously. It is not on the body, but is on spiritual.

Until he is away from the quilt, holds in the arms Gu Yue, was better. Quick on heavy has rested.

This thinks that has rested to the second day late in the morning, two talented people wake. Has eaten the thing, Tang Wulin and Gu Yue is driving Tang Sect Combat Car , to continue to extend High-speed to go.

Tang Wulin had looked at the navascope on vehicle, he chose one quite to go a long way around, the route that but actually and Shrek City direction ran counter went to Heaven Dou City. At this time, he can only be careful again careful.

------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#897: Seven Monsters convergence

All the way, six times, Mecha has flown from their top of the head. Three fighter aircraft have flown. It can be imagined, now Shrek City nearby atmosphere is tight.

This large explosion, has affected the heartstrings of countless person, now entire Continent perhaps is the condition of being frightened by the slightest sound.

To the evening, Tang Wulin drives to enter Heaven Dou City finally. Has related Ye Xinglan once more, finally saw everybody in remote small Hotel.

The people are almost clash, everyone has given him a big hug. Xu Xiaoyan and Xu Lizhi are choking with sobs of crying.

They are very clear, if on that day were not Tang Wulin jumps, blocked that not to know that with the body of own perhaps the rank formidable Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell, all of them will die. But at that time, Tang Wulin does not know that Gu Yue may appear(ance) rescue his!

„You came back finally, you came, I can also put down the heavy burden. Captain, welcome you to return to the unit.” Ye Xinglan serious said to Tang Wulin.

Yes, they are Shrek Squad, is the Shrek Academy final glory, is Present Generation Shrek Seven Monsters.

Revives Shrek, their Duty-bound Responsibility.

„Daddy, who are they?” In this time, bringing several points of doubts sounds/voices behind to transmit from Tang Wulin.

The somewhat dignified atmosphere instantaneously changes.

Gu Yue behind pokes head from Tang Wulin.

„Boss, is your this? Does the role act?” Xie Xie dry saying.

Tang Wulin is holding the hand of Gu Yue, draws her to own side, smiles bitterly, „you thought that what role I can have the thoughts to play to act? Gu Yue helped me block that large explosion, at that time specific had any me unclear. But when we wake, she lost recalls. Has called then me Daddy.”

„Lost recalls? Is she Gu Yue? This and aren't this Na'er?” The Xu Xiaoyan restraining weeping sound, looks to Gu Yue.

Tang Wulin is smiling bitterly shaking the head, meets the Gu Yue later matter own, as well as her look is the same with Na'er, was actually distinguished by own is the Gu Yue process simply narrated.

Xie Xie is probing asking: „Gu Yue, do you also know me?”

Besides Tang Wulin, is he and Xu Xiaoyan knew that Gu Yue time is longest.

„Did not know.” Gu Yue vacant shaking the head.

Always strong Ye Xinglan eye socket one red, „to save us. Her present appearance, what to do? Can treat?”

The Tang Wulin forced smile said: „I do not know. After being out of danger, I first chose to meet with you. Then if wants the means to treat and cure her. I am not clear, she can this situation, now......”

„I have a look.” Very hoarse sounds/voices resounds. The inside room, a person walked.

When Tang Wulin sees her, cannot believe the eye of own simply.

Ya Li changed, the whole person completely changed the appearance, she looked like has dehydrated generally, the surface did not have blood-colored, the whole person seemed to the human an emaciated feeling. Outstandingly beautiful appearance originally even several points of withered feeling, a long hair completely turned into grey white at this time.

A night of old age, but such as is.

„Your Excellency, you......” Tang Wulin surprised visits her.

The Ya Li step even somewhat staggers, gradually arrives in front of Tang Wulin, shakes the head to him, her eyes is red, does not have the least bit appearance. Lifts the hand slowly, is bringing gentle white light, gently according to the Gu Yue forehead.

What the people are most fearful is loses hope, without a doubt, the heart of this Holy Spirit Douluo, followed Sky Raising Douluo.

In white halo that in Ya Li releases, Gu Yue appears somewhat at a loss loses presence of mind, but clearly, she as if no what feeling.

A moment later, Ya Li receives to reach behind the back slowly, brow slightly pressed, „her situation is a little special, body function not any issue. Should be the sea of Soul receives assault, causes cranial nerve Variation, thus has sealed up her memory storehouse. Caused this losing to recall the condition.”

Tang Wulin somewhat anxious asking: „Can this situation treat?”

Ya Li said: „It is not easy. The human body most complex organ is the brain, the brain is extremely mysterious existence, according to the Federation research, the development of human body brain is limited throughout, is unable the ascertainment to be completely secret. Only can general carry on some simple districts to the brain. How may involve these districts, until now does not have the conclusion. This is also one of the Soul Guidance Technology important research directions. Cannot treat rashly, otherwise, is not good to cause her cranial nerve to damage, will have the irreversible injury to her.”

Listened to her words, Tang Wulin to hold breath cold air, must know that front now on Continent most Top Rank Cure System Soul Master, including her said the Gu Yue situation was very troublesome, that may really trouble.

Looks at the Tang Wulin color deterioration the face, Ya Li said: „Do not be worried that this situation does not have the means completely. On the other hand, encounters this situation, so long as found just right Heaven and Earth Treasure, can help her strengthen the body function, includes the cranial nerve, strengthens the body's natural resistance and removes harmful factors, making the cranial nerve return to normal, the memory naturally also restored. I can think can treat this issue Heaven and Earth Treasure to have one type, named Singular Velvet Sky Chrysanthemum, is rare, moreover at least wants above Ten-thousand Years is good. If Shrek also, but can also use Academy strength to seek, but......” speaks of here now, her look instantaneously became gloomy.

The people were silent. The heart of everyone such as falling lead ingot. Shrek did not have, their roots did not have.

The Tang Wulin takes a deep breath tone, „Your Excellency, we will certainly reconstruct Shrek, making Shrek reappear magnificently. I guaranteed!”

The pressure slight bow, on the face actually reveals anguished, „the future will depend on you. Support that I can All-Out to go to you.” Spoke these words, she turned around to move toward the room.

She can insist is living, is the huge will, only for hope of Shrek that reconstruction, for just before the end hope of Sky Raising Douluo.

Is Present Generation Sea God Pavilion Pavilion Master, saw that Shrek Academy was destroyed, the Yun Ming pain can be imagined. If not complete the last wish the thoughts to support for him, Ya Li already together with him.

Ten-thousand Years Singular Velvet Sky Chrysanthemum.

Tang Wulin holds on the hand of Gu Yue, mind is firm, this Heaven and Earth Treasure association found. Certainly can cure Gu Yue. Now he is the pillars of all people, in any event, he cannot be dejected, Shrek likely only remaining their this strength. As Captain, his Duty-bound Responsibility must lift up the expectation of this huge pressure and Shrek.

„Everybody spiritual gets up, the sky has not collapsed. Shrek, we. Since Academy has chosen us as Present Generation Shrek Seven Monsters, means that we are outstanding enough, mean our future should be able to haunch entire Shrek. This is our responsibility, is our duties. Academy has trained us, we take is a Academy member for the honor. In my heart, Shrek forever is present age first Academy, in my heart, no matter, we must march forward courageously. Where tumbles, where crawls.”

Ye Xinglan steadfast standing Tang Wulin, her sinking sound track: „Wulin, you said that how should we then do?”

Tang Wulin sinking sound track: „Now outside situation is complex, Academy was destroyed, Federation Parliament dismisses, entire Continent is in the chaotic condition. In this case, we do not have the means to depend upon, is everyone cannot believe. In childhood, my Father had spoken a few words to me, making me still have a vivid memory. He said that the human this life can completely depend upon has own, I deeply to be so. Now, we can trust and dependence completely also only then we.”

#898: Teacher(s)...

„I do not fear death, but we are the Academy kindling materials, now in this situation cannot appear easily. All people think that we died, with the Academy altogether life or death. This is our only superiority at present, we also in hidden place. Therefore, following time, I decided that temporarily lie low gets up, does not contact anybody easily, watches changes quietly. At least after waiting for outside situation to stabilize, we again continue to scheme. Meanwhile, we want analysis, which people can trust, which strength will be we can draw support in the future. Also must observe, after observing this big disaster, who is the biggest benefit winner.”

„Two Kill the Gods Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell, I do not believe that only Holy Spirit Cult can steal them, and detonates in our Shrek City. Certainly also has other influences to add fuel to the flames. At least we must the pathfinding, after finding the goal first, we can a better preparation. In lie low the time, we must try hard to promote the own strength, completes the promotion of Two Word Battle Armor Master. Only then Two Word Battle Armor Master stage, we have the strength of self-preservation reluctantly.”

At this time, Tang Wulin when narrated that own idea, not with the meaning that everybody discussed. Now needs is not the democracy, person but who can have the resolution, eagerly anticipates their to walk forward. Without a doubt, only then Tang Wulin can do this matter.

Listened to his these words, in people eyes were many immediately several points of appearance, had the pillar, has matter that wanted to handle, at least they can be no longer confused.

„Our where does lie low get up?” Le Zhengyu asked.

Without doubt, the pub that at this time they live is not suitable, here does not even have the means to help them promote Two Word Battle Armor. Promotes Two Word Battle Armor to need resources also to have peaceful the enough place.

Tang Wulin said: „I try to find the solution.”

At the same time was saying, he has put out own Soul Guide Communication Device, has dialed a number. This is he besides relating own companion, first time contacts with other people.

„Wulin?” Somewhat rapid sounds/voices transmits from Soul Guide Communication Device.

Hears this sounds/voices, the eye socket of Tang Wulin somewhat was instantaneously moist, he is constraining the own excited mood reluctantly, said in a low voice: „Teacher(s).”

Person of first relation yes, he chooses, is one of his Teacher(s), Innate Body Sect Present Generation Sect Master, Innate Body Douluo Mu Ye.

Mu Ye anxious sound track: „You where? All right. Shrek......”

The Tang Wulin forced smile said: „Teacher(s), I am all right. You where? Also, my Senior Teacher he fortunately?”

Listens to Tang Wulin such to ask that Mu Ye was silent immediately, „your Senior Teacher he......”

Tang Wulin heart one tight, „Senior Teacher did he have an accident?” Really so? He had already guessed correctly, Holy Spirit Cult links Shrek and Tang Sect will begin, how possibly to let off Senior Teacher this Continent only Divine Craftsman?

Mu Ye said: „Luckily at that time I side him, the rapidness that we ran, he also had the tone. However, the injury is serious, body receives the Evil Spirit corrosion of Evil Soul Master, now also stupor. We in the mountain of Heaven Dou City suburb. Here has a Sect safe house.”

Listened to the Mu Ye words, Tang Wulin instead to relax, at least Senior Teacher was also living.

Tang Wulin both eyes narrow the eyes, „can Teacher(s), give me an address? We pass.”

Mu Ye has stopped, seems is thinking, after the moment, „Wulin, you need to prove your status to me first. In the official death list, you were qualify.”

Tang Wulin said: „of course. You said that how to show.”

Mu Ye said: „What stage was your present forging rank?”

Tang Wulin said: „Saint Craftsman Rank, previous time followed that time that you and Senior Teacher studied just to promote in Heaven Dou City. Meanwhile has studied with you to Innate Body strength slight Control. To each muscle, you taught me to say precisely, I can own body Control as slight as the degree of cell, my Innate Body Sect secret method built.”

„Not!” Mu Ye as if grows the tone, „good, I also prove my status to you. Initially, when went to Star Luo Empire, 49 days of preliminary cultivate, making you overcome solid foundation.”

The Tang Wulin corners of the mouth twitched slightly, „Teacher(s), told me the address, we will overtake as soon as possible.”

„Good.”

Mu Ye told the route that a Tang Wulin address and went.

Hangs up the communication, Tang Wulin relaxed obviously. At present he can think that most trustworthy several, naturally were his several Teacher(s) and Senior Teacher.

Mu Chen Teacher(s) in Shrek City, now Life and Death does not know, he first thinks that can relate, is Mu Ye and Zhen Hua.

After having hung up and Mu Ye communication, he has broadcast immediately a number. When broadcast that this number, his hand somewhat shivers slightly.

The ting resounds, enough four, Wu sound, nobody puts through as before, the heart of Tang Wulin sank to the valley.

When he prepares to hang up the communication, the communication has put through suddenly, „who?” Another side transmits somewhat low and deep hoarse sounds/voices.

Hears this sounds/voices, the Tang Wulin whole body megascism, Control does not live in the own mood again, sounds/voices became sobbed instantaneously, „Teacher(s).”

„Wulin?” Another side sounds/voices improves eight degrees instantaneously, „Wulin, are you also living? You, you where?” Huge sounds/voices can hear including Tang Wulin surroundings companion.

Yes, this sounds/voices belongs to Mu Chen, genuine leads Tang Wulin to step onto one generation of Saint Craftsman of broad road in the forging world.

„Teacher(s), is I, I am also living, I ran away. Is a long story, you were too fortunately good. You where?”

Mu Chen aura is obviously excited, after the loud breathing has continued for several seconds, under he reluctantly returns to normal the own mood, „I in Heaven Dou City, am looked for your Senior Teacher. But Heaven Dou City Blacksmith Association General Headquarters was just hit by the attack the day before yesterday, your Senior Teacher was missing. Now General Headquarters is also a confusion, I assume the general situation here. However do not come, now where cannot ensure the security. When me straightened out said again that you found the place to hide first. Is all right well, is all right well! You could rest assured that I and your Senior Sister is all right, before I led her to return to Eastsea City, happen to have evaded this great misfortune.”

Finally had a good news, Tang Wulin big relaxing , the whole person relaxed several points.

„Good, Teacher(s), you also pay attention to take care.”

Has hung up the communication, the Tang Wulin big mouth is panting for breath, his subconscious wants to dial a number again, actually put out a hand to block by nearby Ye Xinglan.

„Wulin, calm.”

The Tang Wulin heart shakes, stops hand. Without doubt, person who now they contact with are more, the possibility of exposition is bigger.

Puts down communications device and closes down, „was sorry that I was too excited.”

Regarding them, regardless of now carefully not to be how excessive.

„Rests for day, tomorrow set off, we will look for my Teacher(s) and Senior Teacher first, settles. When the time comes also asked Holy Spirit Douluo Your Excellency to have a look for my Senior Teacher, could help him cure the injury.” Words of Evil Spirit attack, Holy Spirit Douluo should most be good at coping.

A night does not have the words, the second day very early in the morning, the people have the breakfast to start off quietly. In the Tang Wulin Tang Sect Combat Car normal condition can accommodate eight people, now adds on Holy Spirit Douluo Ya Li, was nine people. Slightly is crowded. Only can be several thin females sits in rear one row.

Everybody is very the way silent, this attack regarding everyone was really too big, they cannot even think that these had taught their Teacher(s) and had studied together companion. Luckily, they at least have the spiritual pillar, each other Lover also in side. Only has Holy Spirit Douluo Ya Li to sit on vehicle, glassy-eyed looks to the glass, the whole person completely likely lost the soul.

Has Gu Yue, sits appears very happy on the vehicle, often smiles to Tang Wulin, called one „Daddy” sweetly, only then at this time, in the presence of everyone person vision strange looked at to Tang Wulin time, the atmosphere was relaxed.

After entering the mountainous area, the path started to be not so good, the Tang Sect Combat Car name will follow reality, almost can march forward on most paths luckily, finally, in the distant place level area, house appear(ance) that a piece of stone build became in their field of vision.

If no detailed way that Mu Ye gives, wanted to find here really very not to be easy.

When Tang Wulin sees to open the door, walks Mu Ye that from inside, the eye socket once more was immediately red. After the disaster, must see the feeling of family member, making his nearly Control not live in the own mood.

-------------------------------------

Sought the monthly ticket and recommendation vote support.

#899: Holy Spirit Cures

Mu Ye saw that he similarly is also excited, the personal appearance dodges, arrived in front of Tang Wulin, has given him a big hug.

„Good, I have also thought that outstanding disciple that Innate Body Sect Thousand Years does not meet on such Fallen. Luckily, you are also living.”

Besides Ya Li also has Gu Yue that loses recalls, other people naturally know Mu Ye. Goes forward to salute.

„Good, entered the room to say again.”

This stone house, even if looked from the satellite, because looks like to return with the surroundings mountain massif is neglected. After they enter the stone building, the discovery is different.

Behind the stone building directly enters the mountain massif, mountain massif, there is quite not small spatial. At least ten several cultivate for not weak Soul Master here, some characteristics from them can see, these are Innate Body Sect Soul Master.

„Teacher(s), my Senior Teacher he now how?” Tang Wulin asked.

Mu Ye said: „Situation is stable, sign that but has not changed for the better. act , is Evil Soul Master of close Limit Douluo rank. If not your Senior Teacher this Three Word Battle Armor, perhaps he hung. Walks, I lead you to have a look.”

Tang Wulin changes Holy Spirit Douluo, „Aunt Ya Li, you......”

Is Ya Li makes them call like this, but did not call Your Excellency again.

„Um.” Ya Li nodded.

Mu Ye looked at her one eyes, looks at Ya Li complexion, in the heart sighs one darkly, has not said anything, when guides in front first.

Place that Zhen Hua heals from a wound in mid-hill, static lying down on stone bed he, the eyes gold coin, complexion piece of pale white, surface layer the face, green aura is partly visible, making in the entire stone chamber appear somewhat gloomy.

Mu Ye sinking sound track: „Battle Armor to Four Word this stage, itself had the intelligence of considerable degree, even can be said as a second body of Soul Master is not overrated. Now the Zhen Hua situation, was his Battle Armor helps him seal up the important region of body, has blocked the Evil Spirit attack reluctantly. But this Evil Spirit is extremely formidable, I have tried many means that was nearly hit into the body by them, has to give up. By his Four Word Battle Armor mighty energy , can only most make him maintain under this equilibrium state now. But how time grew anyone unable to reach an agreement.”

Ya Li arrives at the Zhen Hua bedside, sees the green air current on Zhen Hua face, in her look were finally many several points of appearance. Soul Ring raise from the under foot slowly. Gradually strengthens with her Sacred aura, gloomy aura in stone chamber dissipated immediately.

But along with the release of Martial Soul, the body of her own as if also obtained moistening, the withered appearance restored the outstandingly beautiful appearance, Mu Ye that the command stands looked one dull.

The Soul Ring ray of light sparkle, the Ya Li body sends out gentle white light, covers on your Zhen Hua, these gentle white light are such as the silk drills into Zhen Hua within the body like the wisp first, then, above his body, white vortex started appear(ance).

In the green air current of his within the body, such as wisp of attracting by such as the silk was absorbed stubbornly immediately given that white vortex, vanishes in white light quietly.

The sad and shrill howling starts appear(ance), that as if is really resentful spirit(s) in roaring to roar, may in front of that white vortex, these resentful spirit(s) roaring sounds be getting more and more weak.

One group takes one group of green photospheres to be attracted to absorb from Zhen Hua within the body, and was twisted broken in white vortex, vanishes. Zhen Hua complexion also starts to change for the better gradually.

Mu Ye surprised looks at Ya Li is the Zhen Hua treatment, in the heart shocks. Fluctuates he to feel from Ya Li aura that this is Super Rank Douluo stage Soul Master! Moreover, Ya Li is not ordinary Super Rank Douluo, but is Cure System Super Rank Douluo.

What does this mean? At least in his impression, but also has never seen this stage Cure System Soul Master.

Cure System wants cultivate not to know that to Titled Douluo is difficult, let alone was Super Rank Douluo.

Let alone Holy Spirit Douluo Ya Li Soul Ring rank is quite not weak, enough two Soul Ring present is red, other Soul Ring all are black. Even if Mu Ye own, had also been inferior on Soul Ring stage.

This isn't certainly low in the Shrek Academy status?

After the last group of green photospheres were attracted absorbs, the Ya Li look instead becomes dignified, at this moment, golden-colored ray of light sparkles from her, first is extend of pair of huge golden-colored Wings from her comes, golden-colored armor starts to reappear, proliferates the whole body rapidly, covers her whole person completely.

golden-colored ring of light appear(ance) in her, in that golden-colored ring of light, is the pattern composition of another piece by piece golden-colored feather shape. Its appear(ance), the entire stone chamber was all shone upon golden-colored, beforehand sweeps away gloomily, in the meantime, in the entire room has filled Sacred aura.

The resonant hymn resounds, singing sound reverberation, could not say delightful interesting to listen. Presents everyone to have the mind washed feeling.

On Ya Li were many a imperial crown, the imperial crown peak, three Little Angel are dancing lightly. Her right hand lifts, a handle shining scepter falls into the palm. aura of whole person promoted company Mu Ye instantaneously also stage that wanted Lofty Mountains to admire greatly.

„Four Word Battle Armor!”

Presents all people are first time saw that this Holy Spirit Douluo All-Out to go to releases Battle Armor and Martial Soul. Her aura is no doubt formidable, does not have any oppression strength, instead made everyone have the feeling that Soul sublimated.

The finger of scepter on toward Zhen Hua, immediately, the skin of Zhen Hua whole person turned into purple unexpectedly. Then these purple start to swarm to gush out, changes into a huge purple Skeleton head in the air. Roars toward Ya Li.

Ya Li eyes changed into Sacred golden-colored similarly, in eyes fills was indifferent and angry, „Holy Spirit!”

Scepter peak of radiant golden light (Jin Guang) from her hand projects together, on purple Skeleton the purple light puts greatly, has actually insisted the flash, to shatter in that Holy Light and purification.

But is full of the Evil thought also to reverberate in the stone chamber along with it, „hasn't Holy Spirit died?”

golden light (Jin Guang) restraining, Ya Li Four Word Battle Armor also restrains into the body, powerful aura of her whole person vanished, what strange is, her grey white long hair turned into black, the look also fully restored beautiful. Life strength that before consumed, as if with her Martial Soul release self-recovery.

In fact, to Ya Li this stage, when she releases own Four Word Battle Armor, cultivates to can also reach Limit Douluo that level similarly. Takes this to cultivate, even to die is not easy, let alone was the Life strength passes.

Zhen Hua complexion returned to normal, moreover gradually becomes ruddy, all gloomy aura all vanish.

Mu Ye shocking look Ya Li, has a look at Zhen Hua again, then serious [say / way]: „Many thanks Your Excellency.”

Ya Li is only shaking the head of gently, then arrives at the one side, her look becomes the delay gets up. Just like good-for-nothing.

When Tang Wulin they thought that Zhen Hua also needs time to restore, lies down on stone bed Divine Craftsman unexpectedly grows the tone, has opened a pupil slowly.

Has saying that in treatment, Holy Spirit Douluo absolutely is present age first.

Zhen Hua sits to set out, has a look at own, has a look at Tang Wulin and Mu Ye again, surprised [say / way]: „Was I good? That Evil Spirit......”

Here, he saw nearby Holy Spirit Douluo, hurried to get out of bed, respectful [say / way]: „Holy Spirit Your Excellency.”

Ya Li looked at his one eyes, but nods the head slightly, has not said anything.

Zhen Hua returned to normal the state of mind, he knows that own can restore to come, without a doubt is this act at present, but he can also be able to see from the Ya Li look that this greatly was attacked inevitably.

-------------------------------

Don't be anxious everybody., slowly looks. The darkest before dawn, broken then stands. In fact, Shrek Academy underwent the development of Twenty-thousand Years, early has achieved the bottleneck. Moreover, many concealed wiring cloths, the following plot bit by bit belt will come out. What I cannot the play pass future Shrek am, what can say, future Shrek, will certainly take to everybody to be pleasantly surprised.

#900: Divine Craftsman analysis

Tang Wulin walks to go forward on own initiative, first after Zhen Hua salutes upon meeting, this Shrek Academy bitter experience attack that day all narrated.

Mu Ye and Zhen Hua are listening to his narration, on the face the expression was more and more dignified.

Shrek City at that time the specific situation of accident, only then present Tang Wulin they are clearest, in front of that Kill the Gods Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell, other all disappeared. Shrek Academy depending on protecting own Golden Tree thoroughly vanished.

The atmosphere in stone chamber becomes somewhat constrains.

Zhen Hua looks to Tang Wulin, „Wulin, what do you have to plan?”

Tang Wulin sinking sound track: „First watches changes quietly, waits for the Continent situation to stabilize to find the way to reconstruct Shrek again gradually. We first planned to promote to Two Word Battle Armor Master stage to say first again. Senior Teacher and Teacher(s), you know where has Singular Velvet Sky Chrysanthemum this Heaven and Earth Treasure? Aunt Ya Li said that only then found this type of thing, can help Gu Yue restore to remember.”

Without doubt, Divine Craftsman and Innate Body Sect Sect Master is experienced, therefore Tang Wulin somewhat anxious inquiry.

Mu Ye wrinkled frown, shakes the head slightly, „has heard, but has not actually seen this type of thing.”

Zhen Hua said: „I have also heard. Soul Master of this Singular Velvet Sky Chrysanthemum to cultivate body technique will have the advantage. However, I want a place certainly to have. Because in there, has on now Continent many rare Heaven and Earth Treasure. Especially Plant kind.”

In Tang Wulin heart one happy, „where?”

Zhen Hua said: „Tang Sect putting out mystical place. Still remembers previous Excessive Love (passionate) Douluo to your Tang Sect Ice and Fire Decree? That token goes to that place. But you need to relate the Tang Sect high level to be good first.”

Speaking of Tang Sect, the Tang Wulin look immediately a dimness. Tang Sect General Headquarters was attacked similarly also by devastating!

„First should not be sad, Tang Sect is different from Shrek. Shrek Academy all in Shrek City, the Shrek City destruction, were equal to Shrek most Nucleus strength all Ruin. But Tang Sect is different, although in Tang Sect General Headquarters also gathered massive Tang Sect Elite, but more importantly, what by Ruin is resources, but is not the human. As far as I know, Excessive Love (passionate) Douluo and No Love (heartless) Douluo at that time not in Tang Sect General Headquarters. Otherwise, although is two Kill the Gods Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell. If their two collaborates with Sky Raising Douluo, not necessarily cannot block, even if cannot, lose is also insufficient so seriously.”

Listened to his such saying, Tang Wulin immediately the eye one brightly, if Tang Sect can also retain has strength of certain extent, will reconstruct Shrek regarding them in the future, inevitably was the enormous boost. Only by their these eight and nine people, was really extremely weak.

Zhen Hua both eyes narrow the eyes, ponders moment, said: „This Holy Spirit Cult erupts suddenly, is everyone cannot think. We are not completely clear, Holy Spirit Cult has controlled so the terrifying influence unexpectedly. But this time they also quite therefore completely exposed. Bombs Shrek City, their losses will not be small. I understand Kill the Gods Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell very much. After that three Kill the Gods Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell were studied, has sealed, because not only they destructive power is too strong, is because, wants to actuate their extremely difficulties, needs to consume extremely huge energy. Simply speaking, entire Shrek City City Operations energy adds, reluctantly can promote these three Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell. Therefore, Holy Spirit Cult launches this attack, their own consumptions certainly are also huge, but I have not known that artillery shell that now they are any way (of life) that uses to actuate.”

„At present this aspect, outside is chaotic. But the Federation government should be able to stabilize in certain time. When the time comes, we must observe, after this event, who is the benefit obtains a biggest side. Very possible they to have been connected with Holy Spirit Cult. You now also young, young means hopefully. Although now Soul Master, even if Battle Armor Master, because of the High-speed development of Soul Guidance Technology, the status on Continent was not lofty. But I must tell you am, does not want, because this time Kill the Gods Rank Soul Guide Cannon ball loses the confidence to own.”

„Limit Douluo stage Four Word Battle Armor Master, in fact, the essence will not be inferior in Kill the Gods Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell. But to Continent resources, Federation not be at present impossible to develop this stage weapon again. Holy Spirit Cult for this attack, even likely prepared on Thousand Years to succeed. Therefore, in any event , to promote your own strengths diligently is very important. Therefore, I thought that you promote to Two Word Battle Armor Master realm are very correct choices.”

„But similarly, you also need to seek for a future path to own. Shrek was destroyed thoroughly, wants to reconstruct is not certainly easy, is not individual strength can solve, but also needs you to have the enough huge influence to be good. Even if Tang Sect is complete, is impossible to have enough strength to support you to complete this matter. Because once Shrek was really too formidable, to entire Federation must formidable for the degree that it dreaded. This Holy Spirit Cult Ruin Shrek City, Ruin numerous Elite, not necessarily did not have Federation the trace that adds fuel to the flames in behind. Therefore, you want to reconstruct Shrek, then must have certain right to speak to be good in entire Federation.”

Here, Zhen Hua stopped, Tang Wulin [say / way] looking pensive: „Senior Teacher, you suggested how we should do?”

Zhen Hua [say / way] without hesitation: „Enlistment. If I have not remembered incorrectly, your once goal must after Academy graduates enlists in the military. This choice is correct. The military system is the independence beyond political system, although in military system, has divided many factions. But on the other hand, these factions are quite independent. In this case, so long as you can grasp certain military resources, and words that has developed in the military, in the future, you have controlled suitable martial strength, has to rebuild the Shrek possibility.”

Ye Xinglan frown said: „Your Excellency, our Shrek Academy has that many Senior to graduate, walks into the high level of Continent various trades and occupations. When we reconstruct Shrek, won't they stand?”

Zhen Hua said indifferently: „Child, should not be naive. You said right, Shrek Academy has pupils everywhere, calls from a high place, has hundred responses to a single call absolutely. However, this is wants, when Shrek Academy existence, can have such good effect. This is also the Shrek Academy genuine formidable reason. But Shrek Academy , the Shrek person did not lose Nucleus now. When then, you call from a high place, you thought how many people your rallying points can summon?”

„A person enters the society, will be contaminated by the society surely, the body will also bear more community responsibility. They will have the family, will hobble. Then, in this case, will how many people be wholehearted accompany you to reconstruct Shrek calmly together?”

„From another perspective, you, although is the talent outstanding young people, but, you may once think, your present cultivation are are just Soul King and Soul Emperor. But in your Senior does not know that has many to cultivate for above you. What qualifications do you have to summon them? What qualifications also there is representative Shrek? By Present Generation Shrek Seven Monsters these characters is not enough. Only if one day, you all can become Four Word Battle Armor Master, has is overawing a side the strength, has this possibility. You remember, want to reconstruct Shrek, the strength and influence, indispensable!”

------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#901: Plan

Categorical and forceful that these words Zhen Hua said. Also is similar to is filled with wisdom general, made Tang Wulin and his companion looks the color of vibration.

Yes, just like Tang Wulin said that now they can depend upon has own. But their own, but also is not very by far formidable. It is not able to revive and reconstruct Shrek, reason has one, that is they is extremely small and weak.

„I understood.” Nod of Ye Xinglan makes an effort.

„You cannot enter the military with original status, status aspect, I will try to find the solution, haven't you studied the cosmetics technique? You need another status, before is not formidable enough, walks with your another status in the society.”

Zhen Hua complexion dignified [say / way]: „Perhaps is because peace was too long, some people must be ready to make trouble eventually. Not only you hope of Shrek, even is also the Douluo Continent future hope. If I have not guessed that wrong, this Shrek City was destroyed, then comes to power, can be War Hawk of main action. They can resist the terrifying nominal expansion of armaments and expanded weaponry. Since the goals of some people have been unification entire Douluo Star. Perhaps the war soon can appear(ance). Not only internal, likely also foreign. of course, this is only my current guess, actually to move toward which step, but must look at the following situation.”

Mu Ye said: „You? Goes back?”

The Zhen Hua forced smile said: „Does not know. At least at present cannot go back. Without frightening of Shrek Academy, did not have the Tang Sect General Headquarters support. I rashly go back now, is a target.”

Tang Wulin said: „Senior Teacher, Mu Chen Teacher(s) in Heaven Dou City Blacksmith Association General Headquarters, Teacher(s) says him now in Control the aspect.”

Zhen Hua eye one bright, „Mu Chen in? That was too good, I do not need to go back. Is comparing in secret well in public. Some arrangement of Association, have not thought that must apply. Wulin, you stay here, when to Two Word Battle Armor Master, I will give you diligently some manufacture Battle Armor instruct. After you complete Two Word Battle Armor, contacts Tang Sect again, helping your this young girlfriend treat. Once treats for her, you enlist in the military.”

The mentality straightened out, Tang Wulin also cannot help but spiritual inspires. The aspect so, now is to walk one step looks one step, and strives every step to walk enough solid.

Tang Wulin and companion lived, and starts again forging under Zhen Hua instruct their Battle Armor, Zhen Hua to the opinions of some instruct nature, the specific operation is their own carries on.

Two Word Battle Armor, must first all promote Spirit Refinement Stage their Battle Armor metal(s), then increases Wings. Again, is a law portray.

But in the entire manufacture Two Word Battle Armor process, is most difficult, is not the following law portray. Yuan En Yehui and Ye Xinglan can quite relaxed completes this work, they are cultivation of Soul Emperor rank are, has enough Soul Power support to complete a law portray. forging is most difficulties!

Said accurately that initially made the plan from Tang Wulin, wants, when One Word Battle Armor with Spiritual Metal, he many pressures will have placed on own.

One Word Battle Armor with Spiritual Metal, can saving resources of enormous degree, not need to waste the manufacture One Word Battle Armor material, when Two Word Battle Armor can also continue to use. Portrays a Nucleus method difficulty markedly to reduce, only needed to supplement some law complex degrees and special effect is OK.

May regarding forging, the difficulty actually be more difficult than direct manufacture Two Word Battle Armor. First, Tang Wulin cannot have any fault, because he cannot be defeated. Without any test opportunity, must succeed at one fell swoop. Simultaneously must unable to affect Nucleus method originally in forging, meanwhile must join new metal(s) Harmonizing Refinement to go in again, even if before , he is 6th Rank Blacksmith time, does not have the absolute assurance to complete.

But now, of course is different! He is Saint Craftsman, entire Douluo Continent in history, youngest Saint Craftsman!

dual hammers dexterous falling on front golden-colored armor, every time raps on Tang Wulin to send out gentle aura naturally. Not only this aura Soul Power fluctuates, there is Qi and Blood to fluctuate, under his powerful Spiritual Strength in addition holds, is adjusting Battle Armor under forging hammer perfectly.

In Tang Wulin hand this before forging hammer and compared also had not small Transformation, Spirit Refinement Heavy Silver Hammer originally changed into Soul Refinement Heavy Silver Hammer now. The difference of Soul Refinement and Spirit Refinement, lies in Soul Refinement, not only has Life, had Wisdom. But has Wisdom metal(s), can be interlinked with the master regard.

Therefore, when this to Soul Refinement Heavy Silver Hammer falls, it raps Battle Armor sounds/voices every to strike is different, its Innate Body meets the distortion of appear(ance) slight(ly), according to the Tang Wulin regard, dexterous avoids these complex patterns, is insufficient the wound to originally the trace, increases the effort in the place that some needs aggravate.

A hammer got down, is equal to the effect of past dozens hammer, this was the advantage that Soul Refinement brought. Moreover more precise control, lets probability big reduction of failure.

Two Word Battle Armor needs to promote metal(s) stage to arrive at Spirit Refinement, but also needs to increase metal(s) to achieve stronger alloy. Only has Saint Craftsman, can complete all these perfectly.

Other people stand in not far away visit him, includes one generation of Divine Craftsman Zhen Hua.

Tang Wulin promotes to complete under his direction to Saint Craftsman stage, even if in his opinion, Tang Wulin forging has also felt the artistic feeling at this time.

Mu Ye regarding training of Tang Wulin, making he many years of accumulation be well-prepared finally, after genuine has controlled own that strong strength, Tang Wulin has compared to own control was outstanding before are too many, but the control and forging of this perfect strength unified, make him in several months time, has stabilized Saint Craftsman stage completely. Although was unable compared with Mu Chen such senior Saint Craftsman, but completed this Two Word Battle Armor forging is actually very relaxed.

But as other Shrek Seven Monsters people of layman, looks in forging Tang Wulin, thought before compares, his present forging appeared with ease was more optional, as if was not earnest, but each hammer got down, was actually similar to plays music general, resounded delightful sounds/voices, did not have past heavy thundering, but this marvelous forging let the feelings of some of their feeling at ease, looked like own Soul also while his forging hammer gently struck sublimated.

Xu Lizhi is first sits cross-legged to sit down, in listening respectfully to the Tang Wulin forging knocking, in his heart has clear comprehension.

companion also sits down successively, silently enters the meditation condition. Only has Gu Yue, the big eye looks at steadily looks at Tang Wulin, often askew head, in look is at a loss seems being is thinking deeply about anything.

Tang Wulin first carries on forging, is own Battle Armor. It is not he is selfish, because he just started first time to carry on this Battle Armor promotion forging, own has not grasped at heart absolutely, cannot be test sample with companion Battle Armor, in the meantime, he is also most familiar with own Battle Armor.

But in fact, after his Harmonizing Refinement starts, entered the condition, all naturally completed.

first block forging completes, impressively when his right hand Golden Dragon Claw, with One Word Battle Armor compares, this time Golden Dragon Claw seemed weighty several points, the pattern was more profound, Golden Dragon Claw itself slightly has also increased, above left behind many spatial to carry on the Soul Guidance Method Array portray.

light golden-colored Battle Armor, along with integration of third rare metal(s), the color became profound several points. The entire feeling has been full of flavor, from the Thousand Refinements sublimation was Spirit Refinement, metal(s) starts to have the Life strength, Tang Wulin even can feel that on this metal(s) as if had the pore to be ordinary, along with the breath of own, but Transformation.

In his beforehand plan, is planned, when Two Word Battle Armor joins two rare metal(s) to carry on Harmonizing Refinement, but under the opinion of Zhen Hua, decides only to increase rare metal(s) finally.

Reason that Zhen Hua makes him such do is mainly because forging level promotion of Tang Wulin was too quick, the rapidness that the forging level enhances, means the near future, he will also break through in the forging aspect. Two Word Battle Armor, is the start of Battle Armor genuine, Tang Wulin is Saint Craftsman, fuses two metal(s) to achieve, but he also after all just entered to Saint Craftsman this stage. Fusion metal(s) are too much, among different metal(s) each other mixing is not adept.

In order to makes their Battle Armor in the future more perfect, only joins metal(s) to carry on forging, Tang Wulin can achieve the perfect degree, behind also has Three Word Battle Armor and Four Word Battle Armor forging process in any case, at that time, carries on forging in the situation of having confidence is better.

-------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#902: Worry of Shen Xing

In the Two Word Battle Armor normal condition needs Spirit Refinement metal(s), can use alloy Two Word Battle Armor Battle Armor Master is extremely rare, let alone, their this is three alloy.

Two Word Battle Armor compares in One Word Battle Armor is the huge sublimation, uses the function of alloy also gradually to show. Regarding their present cultivation is, this was enough.

Tang Wulin completes Battle Armor forging, Ye Xinglan takes it to go to another dead room to carry on manufacture together.

Saint Craftsman Rank forging becomes along with the time passage more and more skilled, regarding Tang Wulin, promoting Battle Armor also to have very important meaning to his forging, under premise that in cannot be defeated, his forging must concentrate on, forging, although accomplishes a task with ease, but also lets his profound to own present realm understanding.

No matter what the outside is earth-shaking, in this mid-hill, has one crowd of All-Out to promote the own young people.

......

Bright Capital City.

Here is the Douluo Federation capital, once Continent second Metropolis, was next to Shrek City. After Shrek City was destroyed, here has promoted Continent first Metropolis.

Recently for serveral days, the Bright Capital City atmosphere has been very tight.

Shrek City was destroyed this matter simply not to have the means to conceal to the people. Without a doubt, regarding Evil Soul Master, is the innumerable years that they most hate has been suppressing their Shrek Academy, that dispatches Battle Soul Hall Battle Member to exterminate Evil Soul Master Tang Sect in Continent unceasingly.

Then, placed third? Without a doubt was Douluo Continent Capital City Bright Capital City.

Some lot of people chose to move to the countryside after that terrorist attack or are the small cities, they worried that the own security, is worried about the current political situation.

Federation Parliament announced dismisses, the government fell into the temporary half paralyzed state. Then is the Parliament reorganization, simultaneously aims at Evil Soul Master this unprecedented terrorist attack, revenges the big search.

Holy Spirit Cult as if already had expected that the possibility of this situation, after completing that terrorist attack, suddenly all went into hiding, has not stayed behind including a wee bit traces. Therefore, in searching that although Federation military All-Out to go, actually harvests few.

The Parliament reorganization has been completed after three months of time finally, without a doubt, Hawk Faction of main action got the winning side. War God Temple captured seven seats in Federation Parliament, the seat of military increased one-third many.

After the Parliament reorganization had ended, has promulgated many laws, does not adopt the appeasement policy in view of Holy Spirit Cult, once were discovered Evil Soul Master, anybody has the authority to kill him, after confirmation, but can also obtain Federation to reward generously, has to provide news also same to have the reward.

Meanwhile, Parliament decided that strengthens War God Temple to invest, simultaneously the expansion of armaments, to aim at Holy Spirit Cult to carry on a series of follow-up actions.

Again was matter of primary importance, An Min.

Federation Parliament authorization army carries most advanced Detector to enter various Metropolis, carries on the comprehensive scanning to each city, to guarantee that does not have potential threat existence.

The multiple actions get down, finished six months at the Shrek City large explosion, the Douluo Continent situation has stabilized finally gradually. Only had in that once Shrek City, has left behind that giant gulf as before.

What sounds queer, Tang Sect after this large explosion, has not made too many reaction, instead is other Metropolis Tang Sect Company closes. Dazzling Era Tang Sect Branch Technology Limited Company of Tang Sect ascending pipe closes down comprehensively. All became quiet. This once on Continent most formidable Sect, because as if this large explosion came under the extremely serious attack to be unable to recover.

This absolutely is most people undesired. Students who also some Shrek Academy graduate express various fervent opinions, pledged that must be Academy revenges, must reconstruct Academy.

Also some people proposed to Federation recently established Parliament that must reconstruct Shrek City. But currently Federation temporarily did not have this plan. In short time as if cannot attend to here. Shrek City the region, as before is maintaining that giant gulf.

„Elder sister, you said that Federation this time won't make really Shrek Academy establish?” Shen Xing hangs Elder Sister of two generals to ask to the side.

Shen Yue this time was pushed up onstage by the military, as one of the young guard important army generals, she also after this Parliament re-elects had the qualifications of Member of Parliament. Simultaneously was recalled the military headquarters, holds the post of the key post.

Shen Yue brow micro pressed, „is very difficult. Moreover, even if the Shrek Academy reconstruction can be what kind of? The Shrek foundation did not have, Sea God Pavilion did not have. Shrek that reconstructs will not be original that time-honored Continent first Academy.”

Although this Lieutenant General came from Sun-Moon Royal Soul Guidance Master Academy, is the Shrek Academy enemy, when knew this Continent first Academy vanishes in light of this, in her heart moved.

In some sense, Shrek City is one of the Douluo Continent symbols, regarding the government, such an independent and neutral place is really such as the burr, may regarding the general publics and more influences, it actually be the important flag of management democracy.

Now did not have Shrek, the Federation government will be without doubt easier regarding the control of Continent, but same, the supervision and restriction will reduce greatly, regarding the long-term healthy development, is not the good deed.

Shen Yue is in itself not military Hawk Faction, she belongs to the position to guard Continent resistance outside Dove Faction. This unprecedented terrorist attack made the Hawk Faction large scale superior, but Dove Faction also made use to obtain some territories, she was pushed by Dove Faction.

In the Shen Yue heart somewhat was actually worried, after Hawk Faction gets the winning side, the Continent situation will be perhaps unstable in the future. Is the senior military, her of course knows that some unifies planet sounds/voices. But on Soul Guidance Technology, Douluo Continent truly throughout is in the lead.

Shen Xing looks at frown Elder Sister, her heart actually flew to the day. In her mind, deeply is remembering that face. She can never forget, in which time almost can fellow of appear(ance) every day in own dreamland.

Did he also die? Also died in this large explosion? own unexpectedly including retaliating his opportunity lost.

Why does not know, in her heart is very sad, was very since recently long time, the condition of her whole person is not good.

......

A man and a woman, walk hand in hand on the broad street, their figure is slim, but the look is very ordinary. The youth height exceeds one meter nine, the long arms waspwaist shoulder wide back is extravagant, the figure of young girl is also slim, the a pair of longleg is especially conspicuous. The skin is somewhat dim, the look is also very ordinary.

„To.” youth has referred to the front teahouse, drew the young girl to walk.

The young girls opened mouth, wants to say anything, has actually borne, pursing the lips of cannot help but, as if has discontented as.

Enters the teahouse, immediately has service personnel to welcome.

„Two?”

youth nodded, said: „We want to drink the dahongpao.”

The attendant look moves slightly, „wants several to soak?”

youth said: „Three soak just right, are many insipidly was tasteless.”

„Good, two please come along with me.” Then, attendant turns around to walk toward building.

youth and young girl follow on the heels, go upstairs.

attendant has not opened the mouth again, but led them to go to two buildings, has come to the road end, he actually suddenly gently pressed on the wall, the wall split unexpectedly, revealed a gateway.

Hand signal that attendant has compared invitation. youth drew the young girl to walk.

The indoor is a teahouse, inside actually sat a person, is sitting cross-legged to sit on the tea table following rush cushion steeps tea.

„Sits.” His gentle saying.

--------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#903: seven-colored miasma

That person of look that sits is handsome, seems the 30-year-old appearance, the body has to plant the dust aura.

youth sees him, the expression immediately becomes excited, walks to go forward quickly, sat in his opposite, „Vice Hall Master.”

The middle-aged people advance in front of one cup of tea him, „tastes.”

youth has gawked, but also immediately calms down, carries the teacup, blows the above steam, then tosses down.

Light delicate fragrance following the steam inflow abdomen, immediately, he only thought that comfortable of whole body warm not being able saying that the body fragrant was also lingered by the tea.

„Knows that you are living, I was very happy. At least, Shrek has preserved eventually the fire seed of recurrence. At least Shrek inheritance has not cut off.”

The eyeground of middle-aged person flashes through a sorrow.

youth lowered the head, eyes flood red, sinking sound track: „Vice Hall Master, our Tang Sect present situation how?”

The middle-aged people shake the head, „is not very good. After General Headquarters was exploded, all Dazzling Era Tang Sect divided Company to suffer forcing out of various levels, cooperated the close military also to cut off the communication with us, in darkness in Ming, the multiple attack also arrived. This is carries on obviously deliberate. Hall Master decided that all branches temporarily close, Tang Sect has many deals with the crisis plan, now starts is one of the plans, moreover is aims at the most grave circumstance that.”

youth said: „Besides Holy Spirit Cult, but also who?”

The middle-aged person light [say / way] of: „Have you heard a few words? The wall people push but actually. This time plot fears the history to be glorious, simultaneously aims at Shrek and Tang Sect, this is not one generation of can achieve. Holy Spirit Cult was pushed by the stage, but actually many people, I can only tell you secretly, the place of seeing is an enemy. Tang Sect and Shrek status was too aloof in Continent, in fact, we had already thought that Federation will cope with us one day, but has not thought that the method so will be intense, moreover such rapidness that comes.”

„Shrek Present Generation Sea God Pavilion Ancient, is our Tang Sect present leader, is sinner. We immersed in own background are too long and are too long. Felt to have the possibility crisis to meet appear(ance) obviously, always thought that nobody dares to act rashly. But the fact showed that we have made a mistake, the enemy imagines cruel many compared with us, even is willing to come to be buried along with the dead to us with thousands of people.”

youth gains ground, in his eyes has golden light (Jin Guang) glittering faintly, „Vice Hall Master, how does Tang Sect later prepare?”

The middle-aged person light [say / way] of: „Nobody can after coping with Tang Sect has not paid the price. Magnificence of Tang Sect, not because these attack die out. Shrek is also same. I listened to Zhen Hua to say the goal of your this time coming. Tang Sect background, even is Shrek background, even if these people not completely is also clear. You are in the future, Tang Sect and Shrek future. In your hands, Tang Sect and Shrek, will certainly reconstruct.”

„Previous time I give your Tang Sect Ice and Fire Decree, became invalid. But the Tang Sect mystical place, Ice and Fire Yin Yang Well, will open to you. Tang Sect in secret, All-Out will support your superior. These people can, even be on Thousand Years time plan us with several Hundred Year. We do not care, with one generation, even is several generations of effort, brings back thing that we earn. Perhaps, beforehand Tang Sect and Shrek extremely in observing the regular reason, will make these people so unscrupulous. 10 million Life, such will not die in vain.”

The middle-aged people said these words, the temperature in entire teahouse dropped, the prestigious imposing manner dodged to pass.

youth makes an effort has selected, „our Duty-bound Responsibility. Can Vice Hall Master, when go to Ice and Fire Yin Yang Well?”

„Immediately.” The middle-aged people stand up, „Wulin, we meet your companion now. Then goes directly.”

„Yes.”

Tang Wulin that youth put on make-up, but follows in his young girl, naturally is Gu Yue that loses recalls.

At this time Gu Yue stands side Tang Wulin, is winking the big eye, seems is listening to Heavenly Book to be ordinary likely.

But Excessive Love (passionate) Douluo Zang Xin that middle-aged person, Tang Wulin once had met, Present Generation Tang Sect Douluo Hall Vice Hall Master. Also is the Tang Sect second person.

Two seem very ordinary Soul Guide Steam Vehicle drives into the street, stops in the teahouse front.

Zang Xin in going out of the flash of teahouse, muscle Transformation on his face, the image of whole person changed a person.

Does this is completely necessary, because to Continent Soul Guidance Technology, the satellite even can at present relaxed person who through look searching to assigning.

Tang Wulin and Gu Yue with Zang Xin on same car(riage).

Excessive Love (passionate) Douluo light [say / way]: „Now Tang Sect comprehensively changed over to underground, after Ice and Fire Yin Yang Well, you enlist in the military according to the plan. Other you do not need multibarreled.”

„Yes.” Tang Wulin listened to his words, immediately felt the shoulder pole on own shoulder light several points, although did not have Academy, may have the dependence eventually, Tang Sect was the backing.

Zang Xin by the chairback, closes both eyes, „Wulin, you remember. If your anything has not done, or has not achieved enough degree. Then, you have been isolated on Continent. After you make certain progress, you will look like the loadstone to be common, once Shrek background, Tang Sect background, will attract absorbs in your body surroundings. In official investigation, in these person of hearts, you already nonexistent in this world, but your potentials and your status, actually most suit lead Shrek and Tang Sect rise.”

„Now you, not only Shrek Seven Monsters, is Sea God Pavilion Present Generation Ancient, will be the Tang Sect future hope. After leaving Ice and Fire Yin Yang Well, do not contact Tang Sect again, for your own does not expose. Under certain options, Tang Sect will contact you on own initiative. Yes?”

„Understood.” Tang Wulin was saying at the same time, in the heart also slightly vibrates, Zang Xin this turns the words is telling him actually, their responsibility are important, in the meantime, they most times, can only depend upon own.

It seems like that perhaps this large explosion, the loss of Tang Sect, must be bigger than the imagination.

After a half hour, joins other Shrek Seven Monsters six people of Heaven Dou City suburbs, two altitude camouflage Tang Sect Combat Car drove the main road.

The glass along with it grow darking, front partition board falls. Has blocked from the line of sight of people. Ice and Fire Yin Yang Well is the Tang Sect most important mystical place, even if in view of them, the route also needs to keep secret.

Tang Wulin has not known how long, approximately after is his twice meditation time, the car(riage) stopped slowly.

The Gu Yue volt rests fragrantly on his leg.

„To.” The glass brightens, can see outside all again, Tang Wulin discovered that Combat Car arrived in piece of forest.

The people because of the adaptation ray, narrow the eye to get out.

forest seems very primitive, had not been developed appearance. In addition, could not see other.

Excessive Love (passionate) Douluo said: „Comes with me. From now on, you must listen to me to direct, on the road is unsafe.” Then, when he takes the lead first.

Tang Wulin draws Gu Yue to follow, other people follow on the heels.

speed that Excessive Love (passionate) Douluo leads the way is not quick, the people can follow. After walking into forest, the people look at surroundings unavoidably curiously.

All seem are very ordinary, does not have what strange flower and grass.

About two childhood, the topography suddenly became rugged.

„With my step, do not go astray. Here has many deadly poison Plant, poison will be very troublesome.” Zang Xin said.

surroundings all do not know when suddenly starts becomes illusory gets up, Tang Wulin only thought that own as if strided in a fuzzy world, only has Zang Xin before to see clearly.

This is......, illusion?

#904: Dragon Moon Tang Wulin!

As if very wise illusion.

light golden-colored glittering the starlight chains the people are all linking, official Xu Xiaoyan Star-time Chains. Even if has encountered any danger, the chains will also make the people share the injury.

„Daddy, where this is! Quite strange.” Gu Yue asked near the Tang Wulin ear in a low voice.

Although Tang Wulin had urged her many times, do not call Daddy. But how Gu Yue actually changes, the final result can only such not call in person many places.

Also walked time, front Zang Xin stops the footsteps, surroundings all also suddenly become suddenly see the light.

Tang Wulin they then discovered that they arrived at a piece of cliff unexpectedly. Turns head to look, place that they just passed through, is piece of forest, but is actually piece of colored forest, many Plant are they are unprecedented. Without a doubt, this should be deadly poison Plant that Excessive Love (passionate) Douluo said.

deadly poison adds on illusion, this without doubt is the natural blockade of this place.

„Your Two Word have Battle Armor completed? Place in valley.”

Tang Wulin has selected under.

Zang Xin said: „Makes me have a look, your Battle Armor.”

In the Tang Wulin eye golden light (Jin Guang) dodges, the slight(ly) dragon roar sound resounds on him, in his each joint as well as the forehead, chest and other important Placement, shone the golden-colored luminous spots.

Gold threads these golden-colored luminous spot connections, first appear(ance), are Golden Dragon Claw on his both hands, the pattern stack-up, Golden Dragon Claw reappear, golden-colored scales armor piece whirls around upwardly, has covered his both arms rapidly, side the a pair of small arm, respectively when three curving sharp knife blade, with One Word Battle Armor compares, curve of sharp knife blade is bigger.

Then is pauldron appear(ance), pauldron of stack-up rapid downward, breastplate covers.

When golden-colored armor covers the whole body, Tang Wulin aura rises suddenly, on Can golden-colored armor, each scales has the crest line slightly bulge, but in the crest line, has the halo circulation indistinctly. The chest protects the heart mirror is together diamond-shaped metal(s), is similar to huge scales is ordinary.

On the forehead golden light (Jin Guang) dodges, helmet covers, above the helmet both sides drills is similar to the dragon horn general sharp bulge, in the meantime, golden-colored mask along with it raising, covered his face together, only revealed shining eyes.

The Tang Wulin upper part bends the waist slightly, the back one inspires, the a pair of huge golden-colored wing behind is opening, this is seemed like to the wing by innumerable scales put together, after opening, the width amounts to about four meters, after the bend, covers his entire back completely.

When this to the wing appear(ance) instance, aura of Tang Wulin whole person rises dramatically once more, whole body has filled the flavor of strength and beautiful.

Dragon Moon, this is Tang Wulin gives the name that he this Two Word Battle Armor gives.

Golden Dragon King dragon, Gu Yuena moon/month.

Dragon Moon Tang Wulin!

Stands cracks into a chuckle in Tang Wulin Gu Yue, „I have, me also to have.”

silver light shines suddenly in her forehead place, making her forehead raise slightly, cosmetics as well as the hair color on face, in returned to instantaneously unexpectedly normal, revealed beautiful tender face.

What strange is, not other silver luminous spot sparkles on her, only then on the forehead that silver glow spreads. That is a oval silver gem, expands from the gem place outward, changes into Gu Yue is similar to imperial crown general helmet, similarly was silver mask falls, covers her moving tender face. silver armor is similar to the mercury flows swiftly generally „flowing” from the top of the head under.

oval dragon scales is the Battle Armor main key, center the chest is also together the oval silver gem, the interior has the seven-colored halo circulation faintly.

Compares is big and tall in Tang Wulin Battle Armor, Gu Yue Battle Armor appears slender nimble many, pauldron and close combat that equipment has not exaggerated specially, all over the body appears very slender magnificent, serves as contrast her is being similar to the goddess descends to earth general.

Back a pair of silver dragon wing(s) opens, compared with Tang Wulin dragon wing(s) small 1st, but on this Double Dragon wing, 18 silver gem ray of light is partly visible, after this Battle Armor appear(ance), various Element(s) in air obviously become active, and convergance naturally in her body surroundings, making her side many seven-colored halo.

Gu Yue this Battle Armor is not Tang Wulin and companion helps her manufacture, but when she sees Tang Wulin has completed own Two Word Battle Armor, excited under has as if remembered anything, has released Battle Armor directly, the people discovered that Gu Yue has completed Two Word Battle Armor unexpectedly, even had including the name.

Dragon Qilin, this is Gu Yue to the name that own Two Word Battle Armor gives.

Silver Dragon dragon, Tang Wulin large male deer.

Dragon Qilin Gu Yue, or is, Dragon Qilin Gu Yuena.

golden-colored and silver, Dragon Qilin enhances one another's beauty, as if dark, among them has the marvelous relation, after Gu Yue also releases own Battle Armor, Tang Wulin Battle Armor surroundings, take shape naturally [gold/metal] misty halo, not in part of ones duty strange.

Dragon Moon Tang Wulin, Dragon Qilin Gu Yuena. Two Word Battle Armor Master!

golden-colored halo and seven-colored halo contact mutually, their each other aura are sublimating unexpectedly still. In eye pupil that standing Excessive Love (passionate) Douluo looks at extraordinary splendor again and again. Without a doubt, cultivation of Tang Wulin and Gu Yuena for as well as Battle Armor, imagines him is much more formidable.

Tang Wulin Dragon Moon Battle Armor itself has used three alloy, Spirit Refinement Peak, amplification, is far from original One Word Battle Armor can compare.

However, what making Tang Wulin somewhat surprised is, after Gu Yuena releases own Two Word Battle Armor, in her right hand, were many handle long spear.

Silver Dragon Spear? Isn't this Na'er Silver Dragon Spear? Stated differently, Silver Dragon Spear peak lance point place, were many a oval silver bead, seemed did not have the lance point, when Gu Yuena wielded long spear gently, before that silver bead, meets naturally emitted together the ruler Yu Chang silver (spear|gun) glow.

Is the Tang Wulin weapon Golden Dragon Spear, the Gu Yuena weapon is Silver Dragon Spear?

While they release Battle Armor, they behind, companion also respectively released own Two Word Battle Armor.

Ye Xinglan is releasing the Battle Armor instance, the body shines ray of light is most, in an instant, as if she already incarnation Milky Way, stars.

The starlight combination, succinct Battle Armor appear(ance) on her, Battle Armor enters Two Word, Ye Xinglan Battle Armor itself presents is a strange incandescent color, metal(s) looks like Crystallized Body is all over the body ordinary, glittering radiant ray of light.

Her Battle Armor each design has is similar to the knife point general sharp feeling, like her own. Battle Armor seems is not magnificent, back pair of wings, is pair of petite flap, is quite sharp, even a little likely is the guidance wing of Mecha. But when whole body armor piece clothing on her, when mask falls instant, on Ye Xinglan take shape naturally soars to the heavens sword qi together.

Of sword qi, as if wants the wearing out vault of heaven.

Star Wisdom, this is the Ye Xinglan Two Word Battle Armor name.

Star Divine Sword star, Xu Lizhi wisdom.

Star Wisdom Ye Xinglan!

Chubby Xu Lizhi stands side her, Xu Lizhi Battle Armor somewhat strange, he originally when One Word Battle Armor is yellow, but actually turned into brown at this time. The color was profounder than before.

Battle Armor weighty, in all people, his Battle Armor is seems tallest and strongest, each is similar to the rock is ordinary, covers in which his body, the chest place is a gigantic circular yellow gem, helmet is the most traditional style. Back a pair of Wings also especially huge, Tang Wulin also wants to be bigger than several points, toward there station, gives people weighty such as the feeling of mountain.

aura that sends out, has to make the Ruin fluctuation of person palpitation faintly.

Defends Star, Xu Lizhi Two Word Battle Armor name.

The people were bringing joke makes him probably the Steamed Stuffed Bun name of own in Battle Armor, but Xu Lizhi said anything not to be willing. Finally has used the Ye Xinglan star character, defending is defending of protection. The people naturally understand his regard.

Defends Star Xu Lizhi!

Side Xu Lizhi, Xie Xie, after Xie Xie Battle Armor enters Two Word realm impressively, seems has the feeling of illusory, Light and Shadow glittering, evasive. Battle Armor presents the translucent shape, interior has the halo circulation faintly, looks like carves with Crystallized Body. On Battle Armor the pattern presents the dragon pattern(s) shape. Compares One Word Battle Armor time, were many many mysterious.

His Battle Armor seems even Ye Xinglan also wants the filament to be thinner , the back wing is not one pair, but is two pairs, is quite short, but actually very terse. Without helmet, but is an upper band style of trident, body surroundings as if there is cool breeze to surround.

His Battle Armor, all attaches, is promotes speed ability, speed and Soul Power dual promotion. Other defense strength people are more inferior, actually without doubt can make his speed promote Peak.

Dragon Night, Xie Xie Battle Armor name.

Double Dragon Daggers dragon, Yuan En Yehui night. This fellow when Battle Armor manufacture comes out has emitted the brave words, in the future must make own Battle Armor achieve Four Word, is called: Double Dragon night splendor.

Dragon Night Xie Xie.

#905: Ice and Fire Yin Yang Well

Yuan En Yehui Battle Armor, in all people are manufacture most complex one, because she is Twin Martial Souls, moreover two big Martial Soul mutually not subordinations, therefore, when manufacture her Battle Armor, only designs, initially had spent very many time.

At this time, what she releases was own Fallen Angel Martial Soul, Battle Armor after increasing third metal(s), turned into dark-purple, each pattern gave people one type the feeling of filling strength, the back a pair of black wing opened, in addition she restored the feminine look at this time, to human a surreptitious and mysterious attraction.

When she changes body Great Titan Ape, this Battle Armor style will have some transformations, in order to guarantees the amplification of Battle Armor to fighting strength, Yuan En Yehui Sacrifice flying ability under Great Titan Ape condition, as far as possible amplification fighting strength. Therefore, when Excessive Love (passionate) Douluo Zang Xin said that lets everybody prepares flying, she also can only release Fallen Angel Martial Soul, to prepare for flying.

Heavenly Double, Yuan En Yehui Battle Armor name.

Angel day, Double Dragon Daggers pair.

Original Yuan En Yehui prepares to own Two Word Battle Armor seven is called the peaceful day, Great Titan Ape and Fallen Angel, represent her two Martial Soul. Xie Xie good one to use both hard and soft tactics, was makes her join the own name finally. Therefore, he does not know that has made many table loyal pledges.

Heavenly Double Yuan En Yehui.

Xu Xiaoyan Battle Armor is in all people are most magnificent, after her Battle Armor is the Two Word degree, Battle Armor itself completely became transparent, looked like was carved general that became by crystal, complicated and magnificent, Battle Armor presented for the streamline that various circulars composed, in Battle Armor, as if some innumerable starlight. This design concept, was observing the stars stage from initially them comes.

That point starlight is Nucleus method releases, has strong in addition to hold the effect to her ability, can let her Star Staff Soul Skill, each release time reduces, affects the time enhancement. Simultaneously itself can also release Star Obstruction screen, the defense strength is strong, particularly in the night, with the aid of the star strength, the defense strength even can surpass above Xu Lizhi.

Star Universe, Xu Xiaoyan Battle Armor name.

Star Obstruction star, space of Le Zhengyu. Without a doubt, the latter came from Le Zhengyu.

Star Universe Xu Xiaoyan.

Le Zhengyu stands in Xu Xiaoyan behind, both hands are touching her pair of glittering and translucent carving very exquisite wing, own a pair of pure white wing opens in the back, when his Battle Armor one such as the One Word Battle Armor color, Battle Armor of pure white non- flaw is having the golden-colored trace, seems is full of the Sacred flavor noblly.

Sacred rune inscribe above Battle Armor, when Battle Armor itself seems compared with One Word Battle Armor weighty several points, the pattern is also more magnificent. On a pair of Wings completely was also covered by Battle Armor, in the top of the head had the royal crown, the whole body to fill Sacred aura.

At this time or the daytime, the sunlight shines the earth, shines on him, increases several points of might with his Sacred aura. What is just opposite with Xu Xiaoyan, during the daytime, has Holy Angel Martial Soul him, fighting strength will be more formidable.

Heavenly Words, Le Zhengyu Battle Armor name.

Angel day, Xu Xiaoyan word.

Heavenly Words Le Zhengyu.

Eight people, eight Battle Armor. When they had own Two Word Battle Armor, their cultivation to have promoted another stage.

When with One Word Battle Armor compares, besides Le Zhengyu, Battle Armor appearance Transformation of other people are big. This also Tang Wulin in the manufacture process desirably for it.

They likely cannot show with the true colors in very long time in the future, in this case, protects good own is most important. Although their beforehand Battle Armor reveal before the human are not many, but the person with high aspirations may know, the Battle Armor appearance transforms is bigger, is not on the other hand obvious.

But the Le Zhengyu situation is quite special, his Battle Armor rune is Holy Angel [lineage/vein] unique, if Battle Armor Transformation is too big, will affect his fighting strength to a great extent, after considering all the factors, maintained style originally.

Eight people, Dragon Moon Tang Wulin, Dragon Qilin Gu Yuena, Heavenly Words Le Zhengyu, Star Universe Xu Xiaoyan, Heavenly Double Yuan En Yehui, Dragon Night Xie Xie, Star Wisdom Ye Xinglan, Defends Star Xu Lizhi.

To Two Word Battle Armor, they had finally were the own title. Martial Soul and union of Lover name.

Zang Xin watches them to release Battle Armor in side, saw that a pair of double wing or is the wing opens, on his face reveals heartfeltly to smile.

Since Tang Sect and Shrek Academy bitter experience big disaster, such happiness of his first smiling. These young people judge him are more outstanding. Not only they cultivate for far ultra person of same age, this Battle Armor is also out of the ordinary, definitely is not for hasty work of short time promotion. Battle Armor foundation hits extremely reliably. Most suits them, moreover quality far ultra same step Battle Armor existence.

„Comes with me.”

At the same time was saying, Zang Xin swings body in a flash, arrived at sky over valley.

The Tang Wulin eight people also respectively flap pair of wings, flies into with him airborne.

Regarding flying, naturally had flying ability Yuan En Yehui and Le Zhengyu that most excels. Other people after having Two Word Battle Armor, flying practice are few, this flies into airborne, slightly appears some are unstable. But they are startled certainly colorful one generation of talents, but lived in the body of own on Control in a flash, pair of wings opens, Soul Power output, steady float in midair.

Excessive Love (passionate) Douluo waves, falls toward valley, at the same time, releases light golden light (Jin Guang) from him, changes into up the cover, covers the Tang Wulin five people completely.

Only covers the submersion, Tang Wulin they sees immediately, in this valley, seven colors mist, seems extremely magnificent.

But, when this only cover drills into that seven colors mist, they actually with amazement see, take cultivation of Excessive Love (passionate) Douluo as, his protects the body light to cover the surface to start the appear(ance) fierce energy fluctuation unexpectedly, moreover various places start appear(ance) pit pit.

„This is seven-colored poisonous miasma. In society most deadly poison one of the several toxin. Any thing, by its corrosion. For many years has condensed above this valley, had in surroundings forest, afterward this gate had spent the enormous strength, draws in them in this valley peak, has promoted the density. Even if Black Rank Mecha, drills into, clean that little while also corroded. At least wants Super Rank Douluo above cultivation to be, can protect the body by own Soul Power, withstands the corrosion of seven-colored poisonous miasma in short time.”

Without a doubt, this is in itself the Ice and Fire Yin Yang Well strongest protection. So deadly poison, in beforehand not clear situation, even if is really Super Rank Douluo, very possible move!

Luckily, the gas cloud is not too thick, after going through dozens meters, the line of sight suddenly sees the light, not too big small valley, presents in the line of sight of people.

Can see clearly the situation in valley, the people are shocked by the present strange scenery immediately.

First heaves in sight, is a strange lake, the lake assumes double-colored, is blue, while red, the double-colored lake distinguishes right from wrong, does not invade mutually.

Ice and Fire Yin Yang Well, should from this acquire fame.

In this double-colored lake shore, is growing all kinds of strange flowers and grass, even the big flowers from airborne look, is gigantic incomparable.

At the Tang Wulin Purple Demon Eyes eyesight, this looks, actually most vegetation he did not know. Without a doubt, these are Top Rank Heaven and Earth Treasure.

But also in their appear(ance) in the airborne next quarter, tyrannical thoughts suddenly flies high to sweep from, falls on them. These gods read obviously very bad appearance.

This is......

-----------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.